[ mac ]
aw, come on! This isn't fair.
You accidentally burn down
a building, and you get
120 hours of community service?
Now this says that
I gotta work with kids.
Yeah, me too.
I don't like kids.
I don't wanna work with 'em.
I don't have time for this.
Yeah, I have
248 hours of, uh--
interstate.
Inter-- interstate.
Sanitation. Jesus christ!
What is that--
what is that?
That's the guys with the orange
vests who pick up trash.
Orange vests.
Oh, my god! And then
what is this about the a.A.?
Alcoholics anonymous.
- for--
- oh, my god.
Six months!
That is so unfair!
What do you expect?
Why would you
tell the judge you were drunk?
'cause I was drunk.
But why would you say that?
I thought that
would get me off the hook.
That was dumb, wasn't it?
I would rather pay a huge fine
than have to give back
to the community.
Holy shit!
Look at this bill!
What?
Those mimosas were like
eight bucks a pop, charlie.
Are you serious?
Well, you had
like seven of 'em.
Uh-oh.
Bro, I'm not paying
for your mimosas.
No way!
I didn't even bring
enough money for those.
I don't have enough money.
You don't have any money?
What are you--
are you serious?
Ah! Ah!
[ chattering ]
[ frank ]
good. Good. Good.
Go ahead. Go ahead.
¶ [ asian ]
[ chattering continues ]
I know what it is.
We can't go back.
[ chattering continues ]
I fold. Deal me out. Hey.
Hey, gang, what's the action?
- what's going on here?
- asians love gambling.
- you know these guys?
- yeah. From 'nam.
You were in vietnam?
Don't get excited, mac,
all right?
He was in vietnam 10 years ago
on a business trip.
- beautiful country.
- dad, please get these guys
out of here.
They're really weird
and scary looking.
Yeah.
Hey, I own
half this bar too.
You can't just come in here
and start running our lives.
It's not fair.
Wanna bet?
What?
- would you like to bet on it?
- on what?
- whether or not it's fair?
- sure. Bet on whatever.
You know what? This is exactly
why I don't wanna work with him.
You know what I mean?
Yes.
Because you start doing crazy
shit like this all the time...
And making crazy bets about
absolutely nothing at all, dad.
If you don't go, me and mac
and charlie, we're gonna sell
our portion of the bar.
No, we're not.
No, that's
not happening.
Just back me up on this.
No, I can't really
back you up.
- why can't you just
back me up on this?
- [ shouts in vietnamese ]
- you guys--
- [ shouts ]
[ shouts in vietnamese ]
Screw this.
I'm out of here.
That just blew my mind.
That was incredible.
So today's speaker is david,
For those of you
who are new to the program.
I know a number of you
have heard david's story before.
But a few of you haven't.
I'm sure you'll find
david's story...
Has a lot of relevance
to your situation.
Uh, anyway,
I'm gonna go ahead and--
We have a late arrival here.
[ laughs ]
Hi. Do you want
to introduce yourself?
Me?
Mm-hmm.
Oh. I'm charlie.
[ all ]
hi, charlie.
- here. Have a seat down front.
- oh. No. Okay.
I knew this would happen.
I'm not an alcoholic actually.
Yeah, I'm only here
'cause I got a little drunk,
And I threw a flaming bag
of feces into a building and
I burnt it down a little bit.
You know? But I wasn't
trying to burn it down.
I was trying to make
the place smell real bad
and get rid of this guy.
So-- this guy knows
what I'm talking about.
Look, uh, charlie,
the first step to recovery...
Is simply admitting
that you have a problem.
I'm not an alcoholic,
so it's cool.
He was drinking a beer
when he came in.
Oh, my-- dude! Oh, dude,
how are you gonna--
Really?
[ scoffs ]
I thought you were cool,
man, like--
[ mac ]
I'm not gonna sell
my piece of the bar.
You're being
such a dick about this.
What do you want me to do,
get another job?
Well, try to think where
I'm coming from in all this.
I'm coming from a selfish place?
Just shut your mouth.
Can I help you?
We are here as part
of our community service.
- always a bunch of clowns.
- excuse me?
All right.
We need volunteers for our
Sunday basketball league.
You're gonna be coaching
the teams.
I got two positions left,
so I'm gonna have to put
two of you together.
Great. Dennis and I
will coach a team.
I think I'd rather
split you two up.
[ chattering ]
Charlie. Hi.
Hey. Wow. I didn't know
you were in a.A.
Yeah.
Where were you sitting?
I, um, kind of slumped down
in my seat when I heard your
name so you wouldn't see me.
Right.
Listen. I didn't realize
you were an alcoholic.
It actually explains
a lot of your past behavior.
Check this out.
I'm not an alcoholic.
See, I have to be here
'cause the court--
okay.
I threw this flaming
bag of feces--
okay, okay, okay.
You don't have to give me
explanations. I understand.
I've maybe been
a little too judgmental of you.
I mean, I know what it
feels like to have alcohol
run your life.
Doesn't run my life.
And I--
I want to maybe help you.
Are you saying you want
to go out on a date with me?
No. No, charlie.
No?
I don't-- I never want
to go out on a date with you.
Great.
What I'm saying is...
Maybe I could...
Be your sponsor.
Oh!
But you can't ever hit on me.
No.
Because that's
never gonna happen.
Yeah, I heard.
You said that.
Okay.
So, sponsor.
That's cool, yeah.
Okay. Okay.
Well, I wrote down
my phone number.
Wow.
Please. Please, charlie.
Please don't make me regret
giving this to you.
No, absolute--
absolutely not.
No, this'll be a platonic
sponsor-sponsoree
kind of a thing.
Great.
Oh. No shit!
I was so close.
All right, kids, kids.
Uh, why don't you line up on
this free throw line over here.
All righty. Uh, you,
You, you, you and you,
Come over here.
All right. Now the rest
of you kids can go with those
two losers right there.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What the hell's goin' on
over here?
Pickin' my team.
No. No, y-you can't--
you can't take all--
- I can't pick the--
- you can't pick all--
- what should I not pick?
- you know exactly
what you've done, sir.
- okay, everybody back.
- whoa, whoa, whoa!
That's my team!
No, we're startin' over.
All right. Fine.
But I pick first.
Fine.
You.
Uh, you.
Hey! Ho!
What's goin' on over here?
Pickin' teams.
The teams are already picked.
You two have the ducks,
and you have the wildcats.
[ laughs ]
ducks.
Are you kidding me? Are--
you guys are the wildcats?
Jesus chri--
Is anyone absent?
Anyone tall?
What are those, flip-flops?
Jesus, kid.
Did you not wear shoes?
You don't know?
Did anyone else not bring shoes?
All right, kids.
Everybody take a knee.
Go ahead and kneel.
Apparently there is
some confusion as to who
is the head coach here.
Yeah, it could be a guy
who's never participated...
In any kind of sporting
event ever.
Yeah, or it could be a girl.
That's enough said, right?
Mac and I are gonna play
a quick game to 21.
And the winner
will be head coach.
You guys might
want to pay attention,
'cause you could
probably learn a thing
or two from watching us.
Absolutely.
Try to remember
what she does wrong.
That's the first thing.
Terrible.
Take a lap.
God awful.
Get goin'.
Oh, that's a great shot, chris.
Come here. You're gonna be
the saving grace of this team.
Everybody try to be
a little bit more like chris.
What the hell is that?
I don't know.
It's diet.
Oh.
Do I look like I need
to be on a diet?
I don't know.
Terrible.
Take a lap.
This one?
Gonna get it this time?
[ grunts ]
See, kids, that's 18-0.
[ groaning ]
Fundamentals don't mean shit
if you got no strength.
- my knee hurts.
- we're almost done.
[ groaning ]
oh, god. You son of a bitch.
So this is your place?
Wow!
You know, it actually looks
a lot like my apartment.
Don't sit on my bed.
No. No. Wasn't gonna.
That's a good bed though.
That's a beautiful bed.
Nice and soft.
Charlie, are you here
to try to have sex with me?
I can't believe you could
ask me a question like that
in my time of need.
I'm sorry.
That's okay. We--
we got a history,
and you're suspicious.
I get that.
We got a crazy history,
you and me. Oh, well.
You know, maybe I'll just--
maybe I'll just get
a little comfortable,
And I won't talk,
and you can just kinda--
- just watch your feet on the--
- tell me about--
- I'll take my shoes off.
- no. Just don't take
your shoes off.
I'm really more comfortable
if I take my shoes off.
Charlie.
So tell me about you.
What kind of music are you into?
What's your favorite color?
You ever-- you ever owned a dog?
Do you want a dog?
This thing is cozy.
Just ice it
and it will go down.
I know what you do to it!
Hey, what's the action?
Oh, jesus christ!
Are you gonna keep saying that?
Is that your catch phrase now?
- dad, can you please
get me some ice?
- what happened to your eye?
Well, mac plays basketball
with his elbows.
That's what happened.
Youse were
all playin' basketball?
Yeah. It's a part
of our community service.
Gotta coach kids.
It's part of our, uh, sentence.
Like two teams playin'
against each other?
Yeah, that's generally
how basketball is played.
Basketball, huh? Here.
And go! Very nice.
Lot of tight footwork.
That's it. Very good.
Chris, doin' really good.
You got some good moves.
Dad, what the hell
are you doing here?
Oh, well, I just came
because you were late.
I volunteered.
Hey, do some ball work.
Why are you
doing this to me?
I figured maybe you and I
could do a little father-son
bonding.
I don't wanna bond with you.
Go back to bonding with charlie.
Charlie's with a girl.
What girl?
You know, the waitress girl.
The waitress
hates charlie.
How do you know that?
Because he's obsessed with her
and won't leave her alone.
Quite frankly, I don't see
what all the fuss is about.
I banged her. I don't get it.
Dennis, you shouldn't
be sleeping with your friends'
girlfriends.
What, are you handing down
life lessons? Get the hell
outta here! Get off my court!
What? Your court?
Yeah.
Wanna shoot for it?
Free throws?
Shoot for what?
Throw me the ball.
All right.
Well, best out of three
gets to be the coach.
Dad, you don't wanna shoot me
for it, because you'll lose.
You wanna bet?
Okay, kids, keys to the game.
Elbows. Knees.
Say it with me once. Ready?
[ together ]
elbows. Knees.
Excellent. Excellent work.
Now you're gonna want
to utilize both of those...
Over the course
of the season, okay?
Because the referees in this
league aren't gonna call 'em.
But they might, which is why
you have to be very careful.
Fouls can lose a game for even
the most dominant of teams.
Yeah, kids, could you excuse
the assistant coach and I
for a second?
We'll be back.
Don't you ever contradict me
in front of my team like that.
These kids need to know
who their coach is.
Well, I can see how
they might be confused.
Are those combat boots?
Don't get all high-and-mighty
because you got a pantsuit.
You look like big bird!
- [ whistle blows ]
- I got the season schedule
right here.
Get back!
I can handle this.
I have to see.
- what's up?
- why are you here?
I'm coaching dennis's team.
Not coaching my team.
You lost fair and square.
Don't give a shit.
Oh, it is on!
We play you guys first!
We are gonna school
your sorry-ass team!
Wanna make it interesting?
Dad, you don't wanna do that.
Our kids are terrible.
- that's what
a bad coach would say.
- a hundred bucks says we win.
You're on. I'm gonna coach
the shit out of this team.
Well, assistant coach.
- let's make it 200.
- how about five, bitch?
What are you doing?
You scared? You wanna quit?
You can back out.
'cause I can coach
this team better than you
or dennis or dad...
Or any other goddamn man
any day of the week.
Whoo! Whoo!
That's it! Gambling!
[ grunting ]
Oh, I can't tell you
how great I'm feeling.
I haven't been this healthy
in, like, a crazy long time.
It's having amazing effects
on my body.
That's probably
the best thing about it.
Yeah. Wow.
So you can probably
stop coming over here
all the time then, huh?
Uh, well, I don't know.
I just don't know
if that's safe.
- yeah, I think it's safe.
- maybe if you think it's safe,
I'll consider it.
But whoo--
Hey, um, how's
your friend dennis?
Hmm?
I haven't seen him
around much lately.
What--
what's he up to?
He's, like, working at some
stupid youth center thing.
- he works with kids?
- yeah. But he has to.
That's why.
Oh, my god.
That is so sweet.
Do you think maybe we
could go down and see him?
Why don't we roll
down there today?
You know, you and me.
Celebrate the three days sober.
Great.
I'll get changed.
So get out.
Actually I probably
need to take a shower, 'cause
I'm crazy sweaty from those.
Charlie.
I'm an alcoholic
trying to get better,
And I'm getting
kicked out on the street.
All right. Jesus.
You can start.
[ mac ]
these are wristbands,
And these are safety pins.
I want everybody
to insert their safety pin
into their wristband...
Sharp side out.
All right, if you come down
right on the top part and
smash down with all your weight,
You'll break the kid's foot
in three places.
What if I get hurt?
That's a good question.
Now as long as you hurt
the other kid...
As bad or worse
than he hurts you,
You'll have done your job,
and I'll be proud of you.
Look how good he is
with those kids.
You like that, huh?
[ sighs ]
Tell you what.
I'll be right back.
Okay, here we go. Lay it up.
[ groans ]
Shoot it up. Let's see.
Whoo. Very nice.
Okay, everybody take five.
Chris, come on over here
a minute. I'm gonna talk to you.
Let's see.
Go on over there.
You go-- you guys go.
Now listen. Clearly, you're
the best player on the team.
All right? Now I wanna
give you a couple lessons...
That maybe coach dennis
hasn't covered with you.
Lesson number one:
winnin' ain't everything.
Lesson two:
do you own a bike?
Hey.
Dennis, hey.
[ laughs ]
I haven't seen you in a while.
You haven't come by
the coffee shop.
Uh, yeah.
Um, so I know
that it was kind of--
it got weird after the--
Right.
When we--
Um, anyway,
I thought maybe we could spend
some time together again.
Um, haven't you
been spending a lot of time
with charlie lately?
I'm helping him
get sober.
Right. Well, good.
That's a good thing.
Thank you.
Yeah.
So I don't want to get
in the middle of that.
Oh.
So we shouldn't talk at all
while that's going on.
Oh.
Good. All right.
I'll see you.
Wha-- you will see me.
Yep, yep, yep, yep.
Charlie,
this isn't working out.
Huh?
I don't wanna be your sponsor
anymore. It's starting to get
in the way of my personal life.
[ scoffs ]
what are you talkin' about?
I only offered
to be your sponsor...
So I could get closer
to your friend dennis.
What? Dennis?
Yeah.
Come on! That guy, he's
like one of those cheesy--
Oh, he's so phony.
No. You know what?
We can't do this action.
You gotta-- 'cause what
if I start drinking again?
That's a risk
I'm willing to take.
I hope you guys
are ready for the pain.
Oh, we'll be bringing
a little pain of our own.
You guys are goin' down.
We'll see.
All right, kids,
how are you feelin'?
[ together ] good.
Good? Doesn't sound good.
Are you drinking the red bull?
Come on.
Chug 'em down.
I feel sick.
That's the vitamins ripping out
the inside of your stomach.
That's a good thing. Trust me.
Flop, come here
for a second.
All right.
These are for you.
And there's
a steel toe in there.
Don't be afraid to use it.
Thanks, dad.
I'm not your dad.
All right. Let's get
this show on the road.
All right, team wildcats!
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
All right, boys. Now listen up.
This week-- where's chris?
- uh, I don't know.
- you don't know? You guys
know where chris is?
[ together ] no.
Ah, it's no big deal.
We don't need him.
It is a big deal.
We can't play without chris.
I got 500 bucks on this game.
Are you crazy?
[ stammering ]
well, let's--
I gotta find him.
We can't play without him.
No. You can't go.
He lives a block away.
I'll be right back.
Dennis, where--
Let's go. Get ready.
Put your shoes on.
Hey, chris, you in there?
Chris, come on, buddy. Let's go.
- [ bell ringing ]
- hey.
What the hell are you doing?
The game's about to start.
I got a new bike.
So ride your bike
after the game.
I'm not supposed to play.
What do you mean,
you're not supposed to play?
You know what? I don't
have to talk to you, shithead!
You bought chris a new bike
to throw the game.
The bet's off.
Whoa!
You can't
call the bet off.
- dad's up to something.
- I'm not up to nothing.
Excuse me.
Hey, dennis.
Yeah?
Hey, um, just-- I want--
just good luck out there.
Okay, yeah.
What are you talking about?
I just wanted to say
good luck.
All right. Great. Thanks.
Um, why don't you have
a seat on the bleachers? I'm
in the middle of something.
No way.
I'm not sitting up there.
It's way too smoky.
[ all shouting in vietnamese ]
[ sighs ]
you cheating piece of shit.
- [ whistle blows ]
- oh, let's go!
Let's-- let's play
some basketball, all right?
- charlie, what are you doing?
- I volunteered.
- let's play some ball.
- oh, my god.
You know what, man?
You gotta call this game off.
Oh, you're dead to me.
There's a dead man speaking
to me right here.
Great.
You're drunk.
I'm dead to you?
Yeah, I am drunk.
You know why?
I don't have
a sponsor anymore!
Whatever, charlie.
Let's play basketball!
You gotta call
this game off, charlie!
Let's have the teams!
Let's play ball!
Let's play.
You're not gonna get away
with this, dad.
- I haven't got a clue
what you're talking about.
- [ whistle blows ]
[ grunting, shouting ]
[ whistle blowing ]
- get him with the elbow!
- [ grunts ]
[ whistle blowing ]
[ whistle blows ]
[ indistinct ]
- [ shouting continues ]
- [ whistle continues blowing ]
[ mac ]
what the hell are you doing?
[ whistle blowing ]
[ grunts ]
Hey, hey.
Right?
[ grunts ]
[ whistle continues blowing ]
[ no audible dialogue ]
- [ whistle blows ]
- all right, charlie, that's it!
You call this game!
This game is over!
You got a problem?
Button that lip!
Don't tell me to button my lip!
Is that a threat?
Yeah, that's a threat!
You're outta here!
Charlie,
what are you doing?
I call 'em like I see 'em.
Come on, man. Calm down.
You're outta here!
Oh, my god!
- yes! I'm head coach!
- this is your fault, dad!
Why is it my fault?
Because you fixed the game!
You fixed the game?
[ dee ]
what are you talking about?
Yes, he fixed the game!
What are you talking about?
How do you do
something like that?
[ shouting continues ]
do you see what you've done?
[ dee ]
get out of here!
You're in the showers!
[ shouting continues ]
[ voices speaking backwards ]