♪ Bah-hoo-yeah
Bah-hoo-yeah
Bah-hoo-yeah. ♪
Welcome back from the
dead, Chief Lazarus!
I only got one
thing on my mind.
Revenge!
What exactly are you here
for?
We need $40 million.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
So we've shot a great deal of
the movie, and we're gonna show
it to you.
We just need a little
money to finish it.
Yeah, see, we had a little bit of
a falling out with our financier.
He's also playing Chief Lazarus.
Just, we had some creative
differences with him, you know,
which is why we're coming to
you, but, look, that's neither
here nor there.
Don't worry about that.
The guy wanted to
shoot a full penetration sex
scene and show it.
But, to be fair, I don't have a
problem, as much, with the act
itself as I do with the
man who's performing it.
Don't get into that.
It's, like, more specific
than she needs to...
Let her know. I think she...
Look, I just, I think that no
one wants to see Frank smashing
genitalia with a woman, but if
it were me doing it, you
know, imagine that.
Wouldn't that be nice?
Imagine all the positions
that I could get into.
You know, reverse pile driver,
seated scissors, wheelbarrow,
reverse cowgirl.
I know all the positions.
Whatever you like.
He can do 'em all.
I can do 'em all, yeah.
So imagine that.
Do you see the difference?
We don't finance movies here.
Let's show her
more of the movie.
Get into the story a little bit.
Okay, that's exactly right.
Keep watching, and then see the
big picture, know that there
are budgetary and time limitations
and ignore them, please.
Yeah.
- In your face, sucker.- ♪
Oh, shit!
Riggs, what the hell are you
doing here?
Our relationship is strained.
Thought I'd give you some
pointers on your jump shot.
Noticed you weren't squaring up
on the basket.
Schooling a black man on
basketball.
You must be crazy.
Crazy enough to want to know why
you never RSVP'd to my wedding.
Gee, do I want to see my
ex-special forces ex-partner
marry my baby girl daughter?
Thanks.
I respectfully say, "No."
I tell you what, Sarge.
Let's play a quick game of
one-on-one.
You score on me, you don't have
to come to the wedding.
If I score on you, I don't
have to come to the wedding?
That's right.
So all I do is score once,
and then I don't come to the
wedding?
Yes. Well, this is gonna be...
a slam dunk! ♪
Break a leg.
Hell, break both of 'em.
Heavenly Father, we thank you
for your glories.
We also thank Martin for his
lovely sax solo in lieu of vows.
- Rianne will now recite hers.
- My
love, when I look deep in your
eyes, I find my own destiny.
I find that I want to love you
for the rest of my days, and I
will.
I will spend every day of my
life trying to make you the
happiest man in the whole world.
That was lovely.
If anybody has any objection to
this union, you speak now, or
forever hold your peace.
I object.
What?!
I need to do something
first-- get your father's
blessing.
I came here for my daughter,
not you.
I love her, Rog.
Yeah.
I know you do, pal.♪
No!
I love weddings.
They always such a blast!
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!
Got to get out of here!
Oh! Oh, let me out of here!
Let me out of here! Oh!
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!
Um... I don't get why you're
making this.
Oh, I mean...
Oh...
God, the bank didn't get it
either.
Why make anything, you know?
For the money, for the glory,
for the fame.
Absolutely.
All-- the whole thing.
Yeah, and-and clearly the
movie's pretty kick-ass right up
until we get to the special
effects snafu.
Our ex-backer liked to cut
corners, but we feel like, with
your technical expertise, being
from a dot-com company and all,
and your money, we could really
make a kick-ass movie.
Yeah, now, the next scene is,
um, the next scene is bad.
The next scene is a little bit
of a disaster.
It's got some problems, too,
but then, once we get past that,
it's pretty good, but let me set
this up for you so you're not
totally confused.
Somebody released some kind of a
biting bug, the likes of which
I've never contended with.
Frank and I got them from
China, and they just went crazy
in the bar and bit us up like...
What do you mean you "got
them from China"?
You ordered them?
Don't worry about where we
got them or why we were getting
them.
Oh, my God, Jesus Christ.
We just released them, there
was an issue...
All right, so you're gonna
enjoy this part.
Go ahead and push play.
Yeah, yeah, keep it going.
Hey, Chief, I'd like to trade
in...
...these flowers for a badge.
Well, I just happen to have
that gun.
Welcome back to the force,
Riggs.
Murtaugh.
Murtaugh!
It's great that you're a cop
again, Rog.
We'll n-need it.
Well, I had to come back
because they killed my baby girl
as you was getting married to
her.
Yeah.
Looks like I'm not the only cop
with a death wish now.
Ha!
Chief, I think I found some
clues.
What the hell does those
things have to do with Chief
Lazarus?
Well, I've got a hunch.
Chief, I've got a hunch.
See, feathers were usually used
in Indian resurrection burials,
which could only mean one thing.
Damn!
Well...
That Lazarus is back from the
dead.
Damn!
You think?
So he's probably planning an
elaborate rain dance to drench
L.A. so bad that it ends up in
the ocean.
Making his Indian reservation
the only thing left standing and
very valuable beachfront
property.
That's could be the only answer.
Yeah.
Oh, oh. I'm just gonna fast-forward
for a minute. Uh, but this...
Yeah, this is important...
That-that-that's okay, I'll,
uh, I'll play it here.
Beachfront property on his
Indian reservation.
No, you're still going on
about the whole...
No, just keep going.
Yeah... yeah, yeah.
Well, you got to explain
every aspect of the movie.
That's crazy.
Well, that's because when you
go to the movies, you know, you
can't follow what's going on.
No, you can't follow what's
going on.
Yeah, yes, you can.
No, no, you're like, "Who's
that guy?
Is that the good guy, is that
the bad guy?"
Everybody knows!
I'm sorry, guys, um, but
maybe it would help if I saw the
original Mel Gibson version
first. W-What do you mean that
you've not seen... Wha...? How...?
You've never seen...
Lethal Weapon?
No, I mean, I've heard of it.
I think what's happening here
is the fact that you're a woman,
and our demographic skews male.
Well, um...
It does-- we are a male-
driven, uh, you know...
We are testosterone-driven.
We're a male-driven entity.
I-I got, I got that.
Oh, oh, oh, the next scene.
Oh, yeah, yeah, right, right,
right, right, right, right.
Oh, the next scene.
That's right, there's stuff
for the... the ladies, I guess.
Oh, for the ladies.
Yeah, we shot this for the
ladies.
This is all for the ladies.
You're gonna love this.
Well... yeah.
You're gonna dive right in,
right here.
("Playing with the Boys" by
Kenny Loggins playing) ♪ I'd say
it was The right time To walk away
♪ When dreamin' takes you
Nowhere
It's time to play
♪ Bodies workin' overtime
Your money don't matter... ♪
Yeah...!
♪ Time keeps ticking
When someone's on my mind ♪
♪ Playing
Playing with the boys
I'm staying
Playing with the boys... ♪
Yeah.
All right. All right, blokes,
let's hit the showers, huh? Yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
I don't know about you, mate,
but I'm sore.
I'm really sore.
I really needed this.
Oh, I needed it, too, mate.
All right, buddy.
Now that we know what Lazarus'
plan is, what are we gonna do?
We got to track him down and
fight him, you know?
Sure do.
We got to track him down and
punch him.
We're gonna track him down
and we're gonna...
We're gonna go to the strip
club, which I'm excited to do.
I love strip clubs.
Oh, baby, I love me a good
strip club.
We're gonna...
I mean, this is crazy, right?
Wha...?
I miss her, Riggs.
Nothing's ever gonna make me
forget her.
I know, buddy.
Lazarus has taken everything
from us, but we're gonna take
what he loves most: his life.
Yeah?
Well, we'd better do it right
this time, baby.
We ain't getting any younger.
That's for sure.
I'm starting to think even I'm
getting too old for this shit.
Say what?
Oh...
That's what you always say.
I know.
I brought it back.
That's your...
Yeah, I got that.
Whoa, shit.
Come here, you rascal.
Whoa!
You want to wrestle, you...
You want to go, old man?
You young, but you ain't that
strong, baby.
You want to go, old man?
You too young for this...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, what is
this?
What are you showing me here?
We're showing you a
testosterone-driven, male-
skewing action melodrama.
Yeah, you're gonna love this
stuff.
And, by the way, as a hedge
fund manager, you're used to
this kind of high-stakes,
adrenaline-pumping action, so
this should be perfect for you.
I'm a little confused.
Oh, is it the character-
switching?
'Cause, just move past that, all
right?
Trust me, our audience has come
to expect that kind of thing
from us.
No, no, no, I'm confused
about what you want.
Uh, you need money to fund your
gay yasak movie?
Oh, goddamn it, Mac.
Gay yasak movie?
What are you talking about?
See? See!
You even watching the movie?
Yes, in a lot of ways this is a
love story between two men.
No, it isn't.
Okay, yes, in a... most ways.
All right, but this is about
as masculine as it gets.
It's not, it's not, I mean...
No, it isn't, no, it isn't.
You had a butt-double.
Oh, of course I had a butt-
double.
You think I'm gonna show my butt
on camera, Charlie?
Oh, my God, I was
uncomfortable filming the scene.
It's not up to the par of
Murtaugh, okay?
If you play the movie, you'll
see...
It gets way straighter, I
promise.
Push play, you're gonna love
this next part.
We'll cut that stuff out.
See, nobody wants that...
I sure am glad we came to
this strip club, Riggs.
I do like looking at
beautiful naked women.
That's because we're not gay.
Right, right.
Up next is Lady Starship.
She's gonna blow you away with
her celestial body.
Lady Starship--
I like the sound of that.♪
Man, what the hell!
Oh, what the f... ♪
That's more like it.
Yeah. You like that?
I do, yeah.
What are you looking at, man?
Shit.
Frank, will you pay
attention, man?
I mean, come on, we've been all
over town.
We went to a hedge fund guy, a
dot-com girl, we went to banks.
No one's gonna fund this thing.
No, we need to finish the
movie, Frank.
All right, I'll give you the
money.
But we do the movie my way.
I want... what I want.
And you know what I want.
That's not cool, man.
We can make it work, we'll
just have to add some
exposition-- a whole scene
of it.
What needs to be explained?
It's gonna be perfectly clear!
It's gonna be way too clear
what's happening.
Frank, it's gonna ruin the
movie, Frank!
It's gonna be so confusing...
It's not gonna be... it's not
gonna be confusing.
We got a deal or what?
Ah! Damn.
Damn! They found us!
We got Lazarus trapped in his
own umbrella factory.
Yeah. He gonna do a rain dance
and then make some money on some
umbrellas, man.
He a dirty bitch.
Come on, let's go get him.
I'm gonna jump over this!
Get over it!
I got you, Riggs! Hurry up!
Oh, I'm getting too old for
this shit.
Come on, man!
We're pinned down, Rog.
This could be it, good buddy.
This could be the end.
Okay, Rog, if this is the
end, we should be the ones to
end it.
You know what? I got this.
I got that weird Danish twin.
Oh, shit!
Aw, damn! He got away.
Oh, hey, you know what?
We got to also remember to get
that shaman priestess from the
beginning.
We don't want her bringing him
back from the dead...
again.
That's a good point.
Where's Mac?
He's in the bathroom.
Well, that's not gonna work.
I mean, we can't...
It's fine, just go, let's go.
He's in the bathroom.
Charlie, it's not... we
can't... I mean, it's...
Oh, shit!
Rog, I'm out of bullets!
You are? Oh, I'm out of
bullets, too, Riggs. Oh, no!
Time to kiss L.A. good-bye,
suckers!
'Cause tonight the forecast
calls for rain!
Riggs, there's a basketball
right there.
You should use it.
I know.
Wha... Oh!
Oh, shit, Rog.
If you make this shot, you will
have redeemed yourself with the
item that you failed with in the
beginning.
That is right.
I can do it, Riggs.
Ho-ho-ho-ho.
In your face, sucker.
Yeah, buddy, you did it!
You did exactly what you said
you were gonna do, and now he's
dead.
And now we have to kill that
shaman woman so that she doesn't
come back and reanimate him
again.
Wait.
I got a better idea first.
What is it?
Let me just show you, man,
will you?
We don't have to say everything,
man. Shit.♪
You know you always have my
blessin', partner.
That's my partner right there.
Yeah.
And that's a callback.
From the beginning-- so it's
come full circle.
We know.
And then we brought you back
from the dead.
Well, the shaman did it.
And then we killed her.
Because we didn't want her to
bring back Lazarus.
Okay. We get it.
Go ahead.
Kiss her.
Kiss her, man.
Yeah.
Come on, man.
One last thing, in case I die.
Oh, my God! Oh!
S-So again, this is what we
were trying to avoid by coming
to you in the first place.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com