Ripped By mstoll
Happy New Year 2016 - New Year, New Color ;-)
Oh, yeah.
These are going down real smooth now.
Dee, slow down.
You're on pace to drink 130 beers.
Don't ruin this for me, Deandra.
This could be the last chance I got
to do something great in my life.
You jerks are just all mad
'cause I'm gonna be the one...
to shatter Boss Hogg's drinking record.
Dee, Boss Hogg was a big, fat redneck
from The Dukes of Hazzard.
Wade Boggs is a Hall of Fame
third baseman.
Yeah, it's Wade Boggs's drinking record, okay?
The man's a legend.
He drank 50 beers
on a cross-country flight...
and then absolutely destroyed the Seattle
Mariners the next day, okay?
- Ugh. - That's why we're doing
this, to honor his memory, okay?
May he rest in peace.
First off, Wade Boggs is very much alive.
Secondly, the number of beers
is actually highly disputed.
Some say 50, some teammates said 60...
some said as many as 70 beers.
Which, to be honest,
is an absolutely insane amount of beer.
- Nobody can drink that much.
- Not with an attitude like that.
Perhaps we're taking
this a little bit too seriously?
Absolute...
We're not, okay? The man is a legend.
That's why we're doing this, all right?
To honor his memory.
- Rest in peace, Wade.
- Again, he is still alive.
Always sticking me
with the nerds.
- Yes, ma'am?
- Uh, actually, I can, uh, handle this one.
We'll be sharing the in-flight
call system today.
- Excuse me?
- Oh, sorry. Let me explain.
We're doing
a Wade Boggs-type thing...
and that makes me sort of...
the Commissioner Bud Selig of the group.
Oh, you're the commissioner now?
Well, somebody's gotta keep the game fair...
And everybody invested, okay, Dee?
He didn't win the chugging contest.
Two more beers, please.
Actually, ma'am, we're about to take off...
- so I'm gonna need you to stow your tray table.
- Ooh.
- Okay.
- I can take that and throw it out for you.
Yeah, but just give me a second. Okay?
Just give me a second?
- There you go.
- Great.
Hold on. Hold on.
Ugh! Ouch!
It's... really cold.
Damn, Dee.
Oh, God.
You really have to slow down a little bit.
Can I get you something to drink?
Hey, I'll just get a beer, please.
- Thanks.
- Mm-hmm.
I'm a little concerned about
this frat boy here.
- There's only so many beers on the flight.
- I'll take care of him.
- For you, sir?
- Excuse me, miss?
Um, actually, yeah. How many beers are
we allowed to order at once?
I'm not sure.
No one has ever asked that before.
Great, so there's no rule on that.
Uh, why don't you give me six then, please?
How about you make it an even dozen?
How about I start you with two apiece,
and we just take it from there?
Sure, if you want to be lugging beers
back and forth the entire flight.
I guess that's, uh, up to you.
I'll be taking care
of everybody on the Boggs account.
Oh, and by the way, do you sell condoms?
No, I'm afraid we don't.
- Ooh.
- Yeah.
I'll have to figure something else out.
- Got it.
- Thank you so much.
- Hey. Frank.
- Hmm?
What's with the condom thing?
You think the Boggs record
is the only one I'm going for?
I'm gonna become the first-ever member
of the Air Sex Society.
Okay. What is that?
That means I'm gonna be plowing somebody
in the bathroom before this plane lands.
Do you think you made that up?
Because that's already a thing.
It's called the Mile High Club. People have
been doing it since planes have been around.
That name sucks.
I'll tell you what though.
I will make you a bet
that I plow somebody on this fight...
somewhere other than the bathroom,
before we hit the Great Lakes.
- I'll take that bet.
- Yeah?
Whoa, whoa.
Did I hear you guys talking about a bet?
There's no betting, okay?
That compromises the integrity of the game.
It's got nothing to do
with the Wade Boggs thing.
It doesn't matter, okay, guys?
That's a rule.
And as commissioner, you have to obey me.
Right, Commissioner. Go get me another beer.
Okay, I will, but not
because you told me to...
but because I'm commissioner
and that's my job.
Yeah.
You're on.
Pathetic.
Twenty... nine... beers.
- How can I help you?
- Hmm? Oh.
Hey-oh!
- This is my guy.
- Yeah.
- I got a couple more for you. Grab that.
- Great.
Actually, while you're here...
could I have a rum and Coke, please?
Uh, oh, uh, hold on one second.
It's a beer-drinking contest, Charlie.
I'm still doing the Boggs thing,
but you know what?
A stiff cocktail would go good
with my chicken, so...
Why are you filling up with chicken?
Do you know anything about Wade Boggs?
The man ate a chicken before every game.
That's why they called him
"the Chicken Man." Man batted.328 lifetime.
I'm sure he ate some
rum and Cokes too, all right?
You just said "ate rum and Cokes."
You're getting buzzed.
- You shouldn't be drinking hard alcohol.
- I said one rum and Coke.
One, please. Make it a double though.
Hey-oh!
Mama needs another pop, pop.
- Pop-de-pop, soda pop, soda pop, soda
pop, soda pop... - What are you doing?
- Why are you dancing around like a jackass?
- Soda pop, nah.
Wade Boggs would roll in his grave
if he could see your behavior.
- Wade Boggs is alive.
- Huh?
He lives in Tampa, Florida.
He's in his early 50s.
You, where did you come from?
You were passed out two minutes ago.
I know it, I was,
and then I popped a couple of these babies.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- What the hell are those, Dee?
- Greenies. Uppers.
Feel like I got a rocket up my ass.
If these guys find out that you're taking
performance-enhancing drugs...
the integrity of the game
is completely compromised, all right?
Oh, shit.
As the Bud Selig of the group...
it's my job to quietly sweep this under
the rug before anybody finds out.
- You know, Commissioner, you just...
- Go.
- Lost the chugging contest.
Hey!
You know, I actually went to school at the
same college, your alma mater, in 1966.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, here, have a beer, huh?
- It's like...
- Oh, that's nice of you.
Yeah, yeah, good, yeah. Drink up.
Frank?
Did you just buy frat boy a beer?
Don't worry about it.
I laced it with sleeping pills.
He's gonna be out like
a light in two minutes.
That is some diabolical shit, dude.
Down.
What's going on with the sex moves?
I've been laying chum
up and down this plane.
Yeah, I-I know. I've noticed.
Yeah, I've got my prey picked out.
I'm just waiting for
the right moment to pounce.
What are you talking about? You haven't
moved an inch. You're just drinking.
- Oh, is that what you think?
- Mm-hmm.
Frank, of the 206 passengers
on this flight...
98 of them are women, but only one of them
is a suitable candidate...
44G.
Notice how she glances forlornly
at the empty seat next to her.
It was meant for someone special.
And the tan line on
her ring finger suggests...
the wound is still fresh,
leaving her vulnerable.
Furthermore, when we hit
turbulence earlier, she giggled...
telling me she's a bit of a thrill seeker.
You think she offed the guy
and went on the run?
Pretty tough to lay low
in a dress like that.
Granted, it's not a particularly
remarkable garment.
It's from the J. Crew Spring 2012 collection.
Although, it is a bit much for an airplane.
Furthermore, if she were standing, you'd
notice she's got no panty line...
giving me about five extra seconds
to enter her swiftly...
before she realizes
I am not the answer to her problems.
I'll tell you my tastes
lie a little bit more in 39F.
No. No, thank you, Frank.
No, her blouse is covered
in cigarette burns.
And I imagine underneath that blouse,
you'll find copious amounts of road rash...
probably sustained in some sort of
off-roading accident...
which would also explain her limp.
Although something tells me
the two are unrelated.
Either way, she's North Dakota trash
through and through...
and far beneath a gentleman such as myself.
Uh, miss? Six more beers.
Oh.
Hey-oh! Ah, there we go.
- Yeah.
- Hey, listen, Charlie?
I need you to start
a McGwire/Sosa-like rivalry with Dee.
Look, I think you're getting, like,
too worked up about this thing.
Can we just drink the beer and hang out?
Here's the thing.
The game seems to be getting off the rails.
Frank and Dennis are super distracted
and Dee is kind of running away with it.
Boggsy didn't drink six gallons of beer...
because he was obsessed with,
like, breaking some record.
You know what I mean? He did it 'cause he
was just, like, thirsty, you know...
and looking to pass the time.
Yeah, but I can sell a rivalry, all right?
What I can't sell is... 27 beers.
What am I gonna do with 27 beers?
Who-Who cares about 27 beers?
We're not selling anything. Like, I think
you're taking the commissioner thing way...
- You lost the chugging contest.
- Why did you make me Bud Selig if you didn't...
Nobody did. You just started saying that.
Look, I got empties for you.
- Take those and don't put pressure on yourself...
- I got the empties. Listen.
Attention, passengers.
This is your captain, Boss Hogg, speaking.
And this cold slice of heaven
is my 40th beer of the afternoon.
So any of you dick-nips
think you can slug it down faster than me...
you're welcome to get
your fat asses up here to try.
- Mm-mmm.
- Yeah. No.
- Mm-mmm! Mm-mmm!
- Put your...
- Oh, I'm gonna need that.
- Ah.
- You ruining everything.
- Okay.
The Boggs group is cut off.
- Oh.
- What? Aw, dude.
That's not good.
I can't stop drinking now.
- I'll probably die, dude.
- Damn it!
I'm running low too. Shit.
Okay. Luckily, I came prepared.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
Charlie, we're not
on a wide-body DC-10 for nothing.
Right. We bought tickets.
Well, yes, but we chose
a wide-body DC-10 on purpose.
- That's what I'm...
- To get up in the sky.
Let me walk you through it.
I got 100 extra beers
in a checked bag, okay?
Now according to movies
like Executive Decision and Passenger 57...
there is a secret hatch on every plane...
- that allows me to travel freely throughout
the aircraft. - Everybody knows that.
Yeah, so I just gotta
find my right time to get down there.
- I think you can probably go anytime.
- Go right now, right?
- This stewardess is not on the ball.
- Okay, yeah.
- Oh!
- Hey-oh!
- Why isn't the door locked, Frank?
- I'm posting up.
Half the battle is getting them
to follow you to the bathroom.
This way, I'm sitting here.
It's like lambs to the slaughter.
Aaah! What's happening to me?
Some-Something is wrong.
- - Ladies and gentlemen,
if there's a doctor on board...
please press your call button.
Something is wrong with me.
Dude, how many sleeping pills
did you give that kid?
- I don't know? Seven, 12?
- Twelve?
- Yeah! You told me to take care of him.
- I didn't tell you to kill him.
You better do something. Otherwise they're
gonna have to make an emergency landing...
and this thing's gonna be screwed!
Ah, shit!
Uh, what seems to be the problem here?
Are you a doctor?
Mantis Toboggan, MD.
You want this young man to live,
you're gonna have to give me some aspirin...
a roll of duct tape,
a bag of peanuts and four beers.
Jackpot.
All right, this way. Shh.
Nice.
All right, here we go.
- Speed it up a little bit, hon?
- Okay.
- Ooh. Wow!
- Ooh-hoo-hoo. Yeah!
Ugh.
Oh, you really know your way around.
If I've learned anything from films...
like Executive Decision or Passenger 57...
there's always a way into the cargo hold.
- You're weird.
- You have no idea.
- Oh.
- Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Nothing with my lips, all right?
- Okay.
- I don't want to do that with you.
- Mind if I take a pill?
- Yeah, sure, take a pill.
All right, well, that's happening.
Now just do that. That's a boy!
Is it really necessary
to restrain him like this?
You can never be too careful
with altitude sickness.
One time, this broad chewed through
the fuselage of a 747.
Luckily, I'm a pilot too.
I inverted the bird
and landed her safely in an open field.
- Ah.
- Okay, I'm sorry.
I'm gonna need to see some identification.
You don't think I'm a pilot?
I don't think you're a doctor.
That is a serious accusation.
You've had 14 beers.
- You don't know that.
- It's written on your shirt.
How'd you like to go
to the bathroom with me?
- I gotta go.
- You and me?
Well, Frank...
I have single-handedly pushed the limits
of high-altitude eroticism.
- You banged her?
- Yeah.
- What happened to the classy broad?
- Oh, happily married. Yeah.
Turns out she takes her ring off
when she flies 'cause her fingers swell.
Yeah.
But it-it's all good, Frank.
You know, hey, turns out Boggs...
he didn't hit it out of the park
every time at bat.
- Mm-hmm.
- He tried to get the ball in play...
and hope that he could squeak it
through the hole.
I just squeaked it through multiple holes,
if you know what I'm saying.
Don't, you!
Ladies and gentlemen,
please fasten your seat belts...
as we begin our initial descent
into North Dakota.
Oh, shit.
Well, you know, you heard the captain.
- On your bike.
- I wish I could just sit with you.
Yeah. Hmm.
- But, you know, there's already
a guy in the seat, so... - Oh.
Excuse me, Mr. Person...
would you mind switching seats so I could
sit with my boyfriend?
Thank you.
Hello, Charlie.
Oh, shit!
You're the ghost of Wade Boggs!
I'm not a ghost, Charlie.
You're just hallucinating.
You've had over 30 beers, dude!
Uh, you did? Nice, man.
- You know, your friend Mac is right.
- Oh, yeah?
- I didn't win five batting titles because it was fun.
- Right.
I won it because I wanted to be the best.
- Do you see what I'm saying?
- Nah, not really, man.
There's nothing more fun than winning.
So, come on, drink up.
- All right.
- I'll have one with you.
- Nice! Let's do it, Boggs.
- Yeah. All right.
- Let's drink!
- Cheers!
Howdy, Dee.
Well, what do you say, Boss?
Now, I know you're not quitting on me.
I need you to keep drinking those beers...
so you can help me stop them Duke boys...
from spoiling all my crooked
Hazzard County schemes!
You got it, Boss Hoss.
All right!
Well, here we are, beautiful North Dakota.
Hope you brought a coat
'cause it looks cold as shit out there.
I don't live in North Dakota.
You're going to LA?
About 200 miles inland, the Salton Sea.
My family has a tilapia farm there.
Goddamn.
Good. Good for them.
- Will you excuse me for a minute?
- Sure.
Dennis. Dennis!
- Huh?
- Where you going?
Oh, I mistook that
girl for Great Plains trash.
She's actually desert trash.
I should've picked up on
the multiple gecko tattoos...
so this is kind of on me.
Either way, I'd rather stay in this
barren wasteland of a state...
than spend one more minute with that filth.
- I'll see you back in Philly.
- Wait, wait, Dennis. Don't go.
Now you can go.
Come on! Drink!
You can do it! You guys are gonna make it!
I can't believe what we are witnessing here.
We are making history here, people!
We're making history!
- Beer me, baby.
- You're 40 beers back, bitch!
Just sit back and enjoy the show.
Well, I'm tired of people
telling me what I can't do.
They say I can't drink on a plane.
They say I can't bang on a plane.
They say I can't be a pilot.
I can't be a doctor.
I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna do it right in front of your face.
I'm gonna chug 15 beers right now.
Oh, that's so cold.
Beer's so cold.
There's a...
Instant rebuff.
Just leave me here.
Okay, guys, here we go. Almost there!
Almost there! Wake up! Perk up! Perk up!
Guys, we're at 70 beers.
That means one more to break the record.
- Come on.
- Come on. You can do it!
Go! Chug it! Chug it!
Come on, come on, you can do it.
You can do it! I believe in you!
- Yeah!
- Yeah, Dee, go!
- I did it!
- Seventy-one beers!
- Holy shit!
- I'm the king, Boss Hoss.
- But you're not done yet.
- Ah.
Yeah, no. Uh, Boggs didn't just drink
enough beer to kill a horse.
He also suited up the next day
and went three for five...
so you're gonna have to do that.
Yeah, totally.
All right, uh... Where's Dee?
What?
Okay, here we go, Charlie.
You gotta go at least
three for 10, all right? You ready?
I'm gonna put a little mustard
on this one, all right?
All right.
Holy shit, dude! You roped that!
- Wow!
- All right, give me another one.
That's the only ball I have,
and I didn't expect you to hit it that far.
I don't feel like going to get it.
So, I'm the commissioner.
I say you did it!
Yeah! One for one.
That's batting a thousand, dude.
Yeah!
- Whoo!
- Nice work!
Yeah!
- Hey, man?
- Yeah?
- It's kind of gloomy, huh?
- Yeah.
If we hurry up, we get back to the airport,
get a red-eye back to Philly.
They got chicken, yeah!
- Let's go grab a beer.
- Ah, yeah.
Ripped By mstoll
Happy New Year 2016 - New Year, New Color ;-)