[ frank ] dennis,
stop acting like a child.
I don't want to hear it, dad.
Deandra, move the pool table
so you and your brother
can lay some grout.
I am not laying grout.
You guys are
being babies.
Babies.
We're being babies, mac?
Why don't you go work
for your dad all day?
- my dad's a meth dealer.
- [ mock crying ]
oh, oh, no!
My daddy's in prison!
My daddy used to give
hot shots to prostitutes.
- [ dennis ] feel sorry for me!
- I got the grout.
- dad, you're not
even listening to us.
- are you really leaving?
- yes!
- later, bitches.
- yeah, have a good life now.
- all right, look.
I know what you're doin'.
I can play this game. Mac and me
and charlie can run the bar.
Great. Terrific. Good idea.
Great. We got
better things to do.
Please. What are
you two gonna do?
Dee and I have a little
something we like
to call "goals."
Weird, right?
We have aspirations
outside of this bar.
We got big dreams, mac.
We're gonna go follow 'em.
You guys have nothing
without this bar.
Don't worry about us, mac.
We'll be just fine.
[ dennis ]
so what are your dreams?
[ dee ] hmm?
Your goals.
What are your aspirations?
Were you serious about that?
Yeah! What are you doing?
Signing us up for
unemployment benefits.
Unemployment? No.
Dee, that's for deadbeats.
Come on. We got
a golden opportunity here.
You know? We can do
anything we want if
we put our minds to it.
Well, I guess I could
use this time to get
my acting career off the ground.
And I fully support you.
You do?
Absolute-- the old dennis would
have said, "dee, your sad little
acting ship sailed a decade ago.
It's pathetic." but the new
dennis says that it's not my
place to kill your pipe dreams.
- you should go for it.
- really?
Yes! Come on. This is america!
We're gonna go for it!
We're gonna work hard!
We're gonna reach for the
stars! We're gonna become more
successful than our parents.
- we can shove it
in their faces.
- make 'em eat shit!
[ laptop chimes ]
oh, look, we qualified.
Really? How much?
400 a week.
400-- that's more
than we made at the bar.
I know.
Okay, new plan.
We're gonna go
on unemployment.
Yeah.
- that's what it's
there for, right?
- in the meantime...
We will focus
and work hard and keep
our nose to the grindstone.
Right?
Absolutely.
[ charlie ]
ready?
[ mac ] yeah.
One, two, three.
[ straining ]
Goddamn it!
Wha-- why can you
not lift your end?
-I don't know, dude. Let me
figure out what is happening.
-are you lifting with your back?
Of course
I'm lifting with my back.
I think your end is lighter.
The balls have
rolled down to this end.
No! You got to snap
your back up and lift.
I'm jerking my back up!
What do you want from me?
Hey, what's the ruckus?
I'm trying to conduct important
business back there.
We finished with the tile.
Now we're trying to move
the pool table back.
All right, all right, all right.
Have you done the urinal?
Because the urinal,
you flush it, and it sprays
all over the place.
Yeah, I know.
Look, bro. You gotta stop
bossing us around, okay?
I mean, look at charlie.
You're breaking his spirit.
Look at me.
I'm broken, dude.
Look, I'm--
You guys need a father figure.
And I'm trying to be
that father figure,
And someday you're
gonna thank me for it.
And that's all there is to it.
Trust me.
Trust me on that one.
You're gonna
thank me for it.
[ door closes ]
I don't want a father figure.
[ both singing
with boom box ]
oh, baby, you
you got what I need
but you say
he's just a friend
oh, baby, you--
come down
just a little bit.
He's not hitting it
that high, you know?
oh, baby, you--
now you should split
the difference.
You got to split
Yeah, split the difference.
What the hell is this?
Oh, living the dream, bro.
Living the dream.
[ turns off ]
I thought you two
were out looking for
careers or something.
We are. We're just getting
a little bit of assistance
to help us out over the hump.
And this unemployment thing
is so great, because we've
made really big plans.
[ laughs ]
I'm gonna be a veterinarian.
Yeah.
And I am gonna move to new york,
and I'm gonna be on broadway.
Mm-hmm.
What?
It's 1:00 in the afternoon,
and you're piss-ass drunk.
Well, it's a slow process,
man. It takes a little time.
But we trust the system.
Is that a new watch,
dude?
It is. It's awesome.
And I got
a jesus chain.
It's good. Look at it.
All right, look, guys.
We want you to come back
to the bar, okay?
Why in the hell
would we do that?
You're not even listening to me.
Did you see my jesus chain?
I'm busting my ass
in that bar,
And you guys are
sitting on the stoop
getting drunk all day long?
[ mock crying ]
what, this again?
What, this again?
I have to work!
Cry for me.
I don't know how
to take advantage
of government programs.
Unemployment runs out.
And once it does, you guys are
gonna be back out on your asses.
Once it runs out,
we're gonna go on welfare, dude.
Yup.
Welfare?
Mm-hmm.
You guys can't
go on welfare.
Oh, really?
It's reserved for people
who need it, you know?
Like poor people
who need some help thr--
[ turns on ]
It's set up
to continue--
oh, baby, you
It's not for overprivileged
pieces of shit who want to waste
millions of dollars in tax--
You want to play this game?
We gonna play this game now?
but you say
he's just a friend
goddamn you!
oh, baby, you
goddamn it!
got what I need
Charlie, sign here,
here and here.
So, you're giving me
all your money.
Charlie, for the 500th time,
I'm not giving it to you.
It's not yours.
I'm just setting up
a temporary account
in your name.
What my wife can't find,
she can't get.
Right. This is good.
This is shady, frank.
I like this kind of stuff.
But you will be handsomely
rewarded if you just keep
your hands off this money.
Right, right.
So what's the vig?
The vig?
Yeah, man.
You know, what's--
what's the vig on
this action here?
Do you even know
what "vig" means?
Hey-ohh!
What's up, bitches?
- get your gloves. I got a lot
of grout work for you to do.
- forget the grout.
I have been doing
a little research that will
change our lives forever.
Turns out there's
a little program called
work for welfare...
In which businesses
hire potential
welfare recipients,
The government
subsidizes their wage,
And the I.R.S. Affords
thousands of dollars
in tax relief.
Oh, I don't know
what you're saying.
Dude, is that a question?
I don't understand.
What's going on?
Don't you get it?
We will never need
dennis and dee again.
We hire a couple people,
pay them nothing, and get them
to do all of our work for us!
- we just pay them nothing?
- we pay them nothing!
That's incredible.
It's incredible!
- what do you think, frank?
- well, if we're gonna do
something like this,
We got to make sure
we don't abuse anybody.
No. Oh, my god!
I know what it's like
to grow up poor. We got to
treat people with respect.
Respect is the name of the game.
Respect is number one!
It's the name
of almost every game.
Absolutely.
Because we understand
the plight of the worker.
The plight!
Respect.
Respect the plight.
What do you think, frank?
I'm good.
Go get us some slaves.
[ phone ringing ]
No, dude.
That's not what I'm saying.
All I'm saying is that "slaves"
is not a racist term.
Shh!
Look, dude, I'm-- okay, look.
I'm saying over the history
of time, right?
There have been slaves
of many different races.
There's been jewish slaves.
I mean, uh, italian, uh--
I recognize that,
charlie.
But in this country, we have
to understand that it is
a sensitive issue, okay?
I understand that.
What about that one?
He seems strong.
Look at those
massive thighs.
Yeah, those are good thighs.
But you're gonna have
a problem with work ethic.
That's what I'm talking about.
You can't be saying
things like that.
No, dude.
I'm not saying that because he's
black. He's asleep in his chair.
That's true.
[ sighs ]
what about that one?
Don't just do that.
Why not?
I knew you were gonna do that.
Why are you going to him?
[ mutters ]
that's like reverse
affirmative action, dude.
You don't want to do that.
You could cheat yourself
out of a good slave here.
Well, how do you know he's
not gonna be a good slave?
Come on.
You know what? This is so
complicated and confusing.
I don't even understand.
Let's look at this guy.
We got to talk to someone.
Let's just talk to someone.
Hello. Hi.
We are here to sign up for
the work for welfare program.
My associate and I were just out
on the floor. We're looking for
a suitable candidate.
But the problem is it's
really tough to tell just
by eyeballing these people.
So we were wondering, like,
do you have, like, a face book?
Yeah.
Or anything that we can go over,
like their physical stats
and some kind of numbers--
Excuse me?
Like weight, power--
Something to just
"expediate" the whole process.
It doesn't work that way.
Why don't you read up on some
of the program's stipulations?
Ooh, that's big.
The face book?
No. Rules and regulations.
It's, uh, sort of
a legal document.
Now, is there any way
around this?
Ohh, you're right.
None whatsoever.
Okay.
All right, well--
thank you
for your time.
We got this,
so we'll read it.
Have a good one.
I'm not reading that.
No, I'm not
reading this either.
We'll get frank to do it.
Maybe get a slave
to do it.
Look what the cat
dragged in.
Oh, come on.
Oh, well, look here.
I see you've decided
to steal our welfare idea.
I can't say I'm surprised.
We're not stealing
your idea, okay?
Let's all recognize that this
is a little awkward situation...
Between friends
at the welfare store.
Let's go our separate ways,
okay?
You guys can't get welfare!
Uh, yeah. We can.
No, you can't!
They don't give it to
any jackass that walks in here.
It's reserved for people
who need it.
That's true.
Drug addicts, mentally disabled,
people with dependents--
that sort of thing.
Mac, we've got it covered, okay?
Dee, your bicycle helmet.
Later, boners.
[ sighs ]
that is an awesome helmet.
What--
go! Out!
Hello.
Hi. Um, I'm
a recovering crackhead.
This is my retarded sister
that I take care of.
I'd like some welfare,
please.
You're a recovering
crack addict?
Yep.
Mm-hmm.
And she's mentally retarded?
Oh, most definitely.
You have the proper
medical paperwork?
Medical paperwork?
We're gonna need
a physician's report to confirm
your sister's mental illness,
And your blood work
to confirm your...
Crack addiction.
Well, can't you see
how retarded she is?
[ grunting ]
[ sighs ]
lose the helmet, sis. We can't
prove that you're retarded.
I want that welfare, dennis.
I know you do.
So do I.
No, you don't understand.
I got a taste of my dream.
I can't go back.
I got to get to broadway,
and welfare's the key.
What do you want to do?
Oh, they want to play rough?
We can play rough.
Let's go buy some crack.
Okay, thank you.
We're all set. Friday, 3:00.
Full blood work.
Okay. We'll just
smoke a little bit.
A little bit.
Just enough to get
into our system.
Then we'll go to the doctor,
we'll get all of our paperwork,
and we'll get full benefits.
Then we'll collect
for just a little while
until we get settled.
Then I'll take the mcats.
And I'll move to new york.
Perfect.
[ gasps ]
oh, my god!
Oh, jesus!
Ooh, wow, you scared us.
Oh, not 'cause you're black.
No, we're not racist.
No. God, no.
It's just that
the neighborhood is scary.
If you were another ethnicity--
You really did pop up.
But it's a nice neighborhood.
No, the trees are--
it's the nature of this--
Roll your window down.
Okay.
What you need?
Uh, one, please.
One what?
Uh, one rock of crack.
One crack--
A crack rock.
Is that enough?
Is one crack rock enough?
See, I don't--
how much would you recommend
for a first-time user?
Tell you what.
I'll make you a deal.
Two for the price of one.
Really?
Oh, that sounds good.
Oh. Well, that's
very nice of you.
How much?
Uh, $200?
Okay. Uh-huh.
Sounds reasonable.
Great.
Okay. Let's see here, uh--
That should be about 200.
Thanks for being so kind.
Mm-hmm.
And patient.
Pick it up down there.
Wait. Where?
Wh-which--
This one.
It's got to be that guy.
Don't say "this one."
Now, maria, after you're
done in the bathroom
you come look for me,
Because I got some boots
to be shined, all right?
Tony, go chase that leak
down in the basement,
all right?
Okay, boss.
Okay.
[ exhales ]
Mac, I got to hand it to you.
This is brilliant.
That's how I roll.
Charles?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I'm gonna get nice and drunk,
play some video games
until my eyes bleed.
Amen to that, brother.
Me too.
I want to play charlie.
Uhh, don't you have, like,
some stuff that you need to do?
Yeah. Yeah.
No.
Yeah, managerial stuff.
Managerial stuff!
No, I got that
all cleared up.
And then I thought after
we played a video game--
uh-huh.
The three of us go outside,
throw the pigskin around,
play some two-hand touch.
Ooh, ooh.
Hey, that's not gonna--
that's not gonna work out.
- I'll teach you how to play.
- I already know how to play.
Not properly though.
Kind of properly.
Right. Uh, oh, charlie.
You know what?
We got to get into
the bathroom to show maria--
The mixing!
Charlie has this thing--
the scrubbing.
Scrubbing!
Charlie has this scrubbing thing
with the brillo.
I have a brillo.
He has a method,
and we gotta show her.
And make sure she's got it down.
All right.
I'll get myself a beer.
Yeah!
Yeah, get a beer.
We'll work it out over here.
Well, this is a development
I did not expect.
It's like he's really
trying to become our father.
I know how to play
football, charlie.
I know you do, bro.
I know you do.
Do you want me to leave?
Huh? No, you're good. Just--
actually, make sure you really
work that sponge in there.
Because otherwise,
that stain,
like, it'll--
It's not gonna get clean
if you don't.
Yeah. It's gonna get worse.
- what are we gonna do? We gotta
ditch him or something.
- tell you what.
How about you and me,
we go out on the town?
You know what I mean?
We celebrate this whole--
[ whispers ]
slave situation.
I'd love to, charlie.
I really would.
But we don't have any money.
- what are we gonna do?
- oh, I got money.
- what?
- yeah, I got a whole bunch
of money, bro.
Frank's been hiding
all of his money in my account.
And why was I not made
aware of this before?
Uh, it's got something
to do with the vig.
What's a vig?
Well, you know how gangsters,
they talk about a vig?
Yeah?
And it means--
Yeah.
Oh, a vig!
A vig.
Yeah. Well, you
should have a vig.
I should have a vig, right?
And frank didn't give me one.
Oh, that's bullshit!
You deserve a vig.
I do.
I'm a good guy, right?
You're a great guy.
I'm a great guy!
We're all great guys
who deserve vigs.
We're good people.
All right, here's the plan.
We're gonna slip out of here.
We're gonna hit an a.T.M.
We'll take out just
a little bit of cash.
Just a little.
Just enough.
He won't even notice it.
Just enough to have
a quiet night out.
[ whooping, laughing ]
Here's some for you!
And here's some for you!
[ rooster crows ]
[ alarm clock rings ]
Oh, god.
Oh, shit!
Dennis!
What happened?
- it's 4:00.
- [ shuddering ]
I'm freezing and I'm sweating
all at once.
I think I may
have peed in my pants.
We missed our
doctor's appointment.
Well, only by an hour.
If we hurry,
maybe they'll still see us.
It was yesterday.
We missed our appointment
by an hour and a day.
We slept through a whole day?
- I feel awful.
- I feel like I'm gonna die!
- I don't want to feel
like this anymore, deandra.
- mm-mmm. Me either.
Okay, listen.
Maybe if I make
a phone call right now,
We'll be able to make
another appointment.
- you think he'll see us
on such short notice?
- we have gotta try.
Hey, man. Thanks for seeing us
on such short notice.
That's what I do, baby.
Two more, please.
That guy.
Yeah.
No, these are old,
and I need to get
new head shots.
Because you can't have an--
an agent without head shots.
Dennis, when you become
a veterinarian, will you
buy me some new head shots?
Please? Dennis?
Hey! Dennis!
Hey, dennis.
Wha-- what?
When you become a veterinarian,
will you buy me head shots,
please?
Hey! Hey, get out of here,
you piece of shit!
Yeah, I'll buy you stuff.
I'll buy you lots of things.
I'm definitely gonna buy
a bunch of crack.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
[ all laughing ]
Hey! Hey, that's
dennis and dee!
Driver, pull over!
Hey, dennis! Dee!
Oh.
Hey.
Guys. Hey.
Hey. Hey.
- hey, how's it going?
- good. Real good.
It's good on our end here.
We're putting a couple things
together lately.
- hey, uh, are you guys holding?
- holding what?
Holding--
do you have any money?
Please?
Oh, um--
I just need a little bit
of money. Wait!
Charlie, wait!
[ dee ]
charlie, wait!
No!
Driver, we're done here.
[ all laughing ]
That's enough whining,
for crying out loud!
I think it might be broken.
I told you not to act like
such a nancy boy out there.
Something was bound to happen.
I didn't think
it was full contact.
Well, how do you expect
to become a better player
if nobody pushes you?
Maria, go get us
some ice and three beers.
I don't drink.
Me neither.
You don't drink? Jesus christ!
You two are a couple of downers,
huh?
You work hard, you don't drink--
how'd you end up on welfare?
Well, it's a vicious cycle,
mr. Frank.
One cannot support a family
on a minimum-wage position.
[ cell phone rings ]
Oh, shh-shh-shh-shh!
Y'ello?
This is pam
from first national bank.
Charlie kelly, please.
Yeah,
this is charlie kelly.
Hi. I'd like to speak with you
about some recent activity
on your new account.
Some recent activity
on my new account?
We got a big problem here,
buddy.
All right. Try it again.
I've tried it three times.
It's just not working.
The services have
already been rendered.
We gotta pay these girls.
He cut us off.
Is there a problem?
No. Not a problem here.
No problem.
I'm calling hector.
No, no.
Don't call hector.
- I'm calling wallace.
- we shouldn't be calling
hector or wallace...
Or any other large pimp.
No.
Charlie and I are gonna handle
this situation just like
we handle every situation.
We are gonna--
Well, you know,
we'll just go back
to work for a little while.
Just for a little while
until we have enough money
to buy some more crack.
Then we'll go on welfare,
and I'll go be a star.
Then I can be a veterinarian
of some kind.
Maybe we should
think about rehab.
We should hit rehab
as soon as possible.
Pretty soon.
In a couple days.
Yeah.
Not now.
[ shouting ]
- ahh, jesus christ!
That was close.
- ohh, look who it is!
What the hell are
you guys doing here?
We're getting
our jobs back.
Yeah.
You can't have em!
We might have a little bit
of a drug problem.
I might not really care.
I don't give a shit.
Your positions
have been filled.
So we're gonna take yours.
-you're not gonna take our jobs.
-my dad called and said
that we could have your jobs.
We need money to pay
our hookers, okay?
So you can't have 'em.
-but we need money to buy crack.
-oh, I'm sorry.
Did you get addicted to crack?
[ blows raspberry ]
did somebody get
addicted to crack?
[ mock crying ]
I sweat uncontrollably!
I can't get somebody
to have sex with me
unless I pay for it!
Children, children.
[ indistinct ]
...With me.
- what's all the fighting about?
- did you tell them that
they could have our jobs?
Why don't we go on inside where
it's nice and warm and we can
settle this like a family?
Come on.
Yeah, what about the slaves?
Slaves are gone.
They were bringing me down.
Plus, you know they don't drink?
Drink?
I want a drink.
Wait, wait, wait!
Stop a second. There are
gonna be some changes made.
Okay.
All right? First of all,
you two from now on are
gonna do all of charlie's work.
- I hate charlie's work.
- no. Not his.
Stop! Charlie, you got a lot
of balls stealing my money.
This shows leadership.
I am promoting you
to management.
That's why I did it.
That's fantastic!
That's why I did it too.
I stole lots of your money.
What do I get?
You get dick, because you
are a follower and a thief.
But how come charlie?
Not fair.
How come charlie?
Why would you
do this to us, dad?
Because you are crackheads,
children.
Yeah.
Crack.
Crack. Crack.
[ voices speaking backwards ]