Ripped By mstoll
Happy New Year 2016 - New Year, New Color ;-)
- This is so exciting.
- Is this the greenroom?
Yeah. A game show. Can you guys
believe we're gonna be on a game show?
- All right, all right, relax.
- Awesome!
Guys, the greenroom of Family Fight.
I've got goose bumps.
Yeah, all right, calm down.
Don't start acting like an animal here.
All right, listen, this is Family Fight.
This is a nationally televised program.
This is a very big deal for us, okay?
We're talking... What are you doing?
- Are you stealing an ashtray right now?
- Yeah.
Why? We have ashtrays,
and you don't even smoke.
This is a perfect place for me
to lay out my political agenda.
No, no, no. No politics, man.
- Why?
- Because it's too polarizing, okay?
And don't be misogynistic and
please don't be gross. I mean...
Guys, let's... let's be smart about this.
Let's be right down the middle.
Right down the middle sounds so boring.
That's not what the audience
wants to see.
Thinking I'm gonna do
a Jenny McCarthy thing...
where I'm, like, super sexy,
but I got a potty mouth.
Ah, no, no.
Dee, you are never going to be sexy.
And do not do a potty mouth thing, okay? We
don't want to come across as lowbrow animals.
Now, have some veggie platter and have some
fruit, okay? That is brain food.
Mm-mmm, no way, not me. Haven't eaten in
three days. I don't want to be puffy.
J-Mac's face, it's never puffy.
Yeah, because J-Mac's face
is stapled to the back of her head.
Now eat some food.
You look emaciated and sick.
- What is that?
- Fart noise key chain.
- Dennis, what is this enticing bowl of white?
- This?
Charlie, that... that's cottage cheese.
Cottage cheese?
Like... cheese from some cottage?
Whose cottage? Well, what is that exactly?
How do you not know what it is? Aren't you,
like, a cheese guy?
- I'm not a cottage guy.
- You are gonna make us lose this game.
Here comes the other family.
Hello.
You must be the Reynolds family.
I'm Janet, and we are the Barretts.
Oh. Okay.
Hey, guys! I'm Lisa. I'm the stage manager.
Both teams ready?
Let's play Family Fight!
Let's give it up for your host...
- Grant Anderson!
- How you doing, man?
Hi! Ah! Hello!
All right! Thank you for coming out,
everybody, and welcome to Family Fight.
I'm your host, Grant Anderson.
Today, we have the Barrett family!
Oh, all right. Versus the Reynolds family!
And they are here for a whole lot of cash,
so let's get it on!
Give me Janet, give me Frank.
Here we go.
Oh, whoa!
- Oh, I didn't get a good look at
you before backstage. -
Sha-booyah, roll call. Whoo!
Okay, all right, we got
some... some sparks flying already here.
But let's get up here and do this.
- Come on, Frank, you ready?
- I'm ready.
All right, man.
Top four answers on the board here.
Name an animal that we eat
but doesn't eat us.
- Frank!
- Pig!
Show me pig!
Oh, all right!
All right! Oh, Frank's doing
a little dance there. Ha!
- Now, Frank, you want to pass or
play? Pass or play? - Oh, we...
Play, play, play. We're gonna play.
All right, so, Frank...
You want to tell me...
- a little bit about your family?
- Yeah.
- Well, yeah, you know, uh, Grant?
- Yes, Grant.
I want to... I want to change my answer.
- What?
- What? Why?
I have realized it's-it's
not totally accurate...
because I've seen a pig eat a man.
In fact, I've seen many pigs eat many men.
It was a bloodbath.
Well, okay, well, we can't do that.
I'm gonna move on though
'cause you're losing me.
Yeah. Oh, Grant.
- A lighthearted barb, if you will.
- Sure, uh, sure.
His talk of pigs and man flesh is confusing
as it is frustrating.
Right.
- Don't you just wanna...
- I hear you, I hear you, Dennis.
- You have these people in your life
and you just wanna... -  Yeah.
Now, Dennis, why don't you
tell me something? What do you do?
Me? Oh, well, I am the proprietor of, uh...
- one of the most charming pubs in all
of South Philadelphia. - All right.
- Paddy's Pub.
- Paddy's Pub!
Yeah. Yeah, but listen,
I am so much more, Grant.
- Um, I'm kind of a jack-of-all-trades, if you will.
- Okay.
So the question really isn't "What do I do?"
It's "What don't I do?"
Wow. Now, there's a lot
of confidence right there. I like that.
- I like that, Dennis. All right.
- What a guy.
Buddy, can you name
an animal that we eat but doesn't eat us?
Ah, easy. Uh, sea urchin.
- Uh, what now?
- Sea urchin.
- Yeah.
Okay. Show me sea urchin!
Ooh, one strike.
- Oh.
- One strike for the Reynolds here.
Wow, that, uh...
that buzzer sounds... It's awfully loud.
- It is loud.
- Pierces you right down to your soul, doesn't it?
I don't like it.
I'll be fine though. It's cool.
- You're right. All right, thank you.
- Okay.
- Who do we have here?
- Hi.
Hello, Deandra...
- Yep.
- Reynolds.
Deandra, help me out. Name an animal...
that we eat but doesn't eat us.
Well, Grant, I'll tell you what...
- Mm-hmm.
- I like to eat cock.
I'm sor... Whoa, no, no, no, no, no.
- No, we can't say...
- Yeah.
- Lisa, are we gonna...
- See what I did there?
It's a little bit
of a double entendre type of thing.
I was talking about chicken,
but I said "cock."
Yeah, don't say that word.
Please, I'm-I'm... Just, it's a family show.
So we're just gonna go with "chicken," okay?
Show me chicken!
There you go.
- Okay. Ronald Reynolds.
- Yeah!
- Hello, sir.
- Hey!
- How you doing today?
- I'm great, Grant.
I'm just really excited to be
here with my new family.
- Oh... Your new family?
- Yeah.
- Oh, a little bit of background.
- Yeah, yeah.
Uh, actually, just for... for clarification.
Um, he raised them, but he didn't sire them.
Now, he may have sired him...
we're not exactly sure...
- but they do live together in squalor.
- Yeah, yeah.
I brought my blood bucket in case you guys
want to run his blood and see if it checks out.
- It'd be good to know. - Yeah, if we
want to do a quick DNA sequencing...
at the commercial break, that actually would
clear things up for everybody.
- If we could.
- It would set the record straight.
Either way, I was always
the odd man out, you know? I mean, you know.
And then Frank here adopted me.
And now I'm a part of the Reynolds family!
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Okay, well...
We don't... I'm-I'm just...
- I'm not even gonna try to figure
that one out, so... -
Okay, here's the deal, guys. From now on...
- I'm not gonna ask you guys any
more questions at all... - Yes!
Other than the ones
that keep the game moving.
- Great! Yeah!
- All right?
Great!
Show me cow!
Nope, that's me. I say that word.
I say the "show me" part.
You just give me the answer.
- Okay, Ronald?
- Right, I'm sorry. Show me co...
- Don't say "show me." Don't say it.
- You just said that.
- Just say the answer.
- Show... "Show me"  is the part I say?
Here's the one thing...
There's only one thing in the whole world...
"Show me."
So just give me the answer,
and then I'll say sh...
You know what, go ahead and do it.
Just go ahead and do it then.
- Do what?
- Mother of...
Show me cow!
Cow!
- Okay, well?
- Good answer.
So, sadly we gotta stay here. Okay.
- Charlie.
- Yeah?
- Just need you to name an animal...
- Yeah!
That we eat but doesn't eat us.
"Doesn't eat us." That's easy.
Dragon!
- Charlie, do you eat dragon?
- No! I don't eat dragon...
'cause, uh, it's-it's
not a meal for peasants...
it's a meal for kings,
and I'm sort of a common man.
But they don't eat us.
They, uh... It's, like, a misconception.
They actually eat gold and treasure.
- That's why they're always sitting on a
big pile of it. -  Bad answer.
- Bad answer.
- That's a bad answer.
Okay, show me dragon!
- I told you!
- Oh, my God!
Well, astonishingly, uh,
one person surveyed...
gave the answer "dragon," so...
What a world! All right.
The Reynolds family has won round one!
There you go, all right.
- Sha-booyah! Sha-booyah!
- All right.
But we got a lot more show to go!
It could be anybody's game.
We'll be right back after this
with Family Fight!
That's commercial, guys! Back in three.
Yeah!
- We nailed it.
- Yeah, that was, uh... that was terrible.
We're bombing out there. This-This is
exactly what I was trying to avoid, guys.
What are you talking about?
We won that round.
Yeah, but you were being
lascivious and disgusting.
Dee was making sex jokes
that were going over like a lead balloon.
- At least we got all of our answers right.
- Yeah, that's utterly ridiculous.
I mean, how is dragon an answer
and sea urchin isn't? Everyone knows...
I don't know, but there's always a weirdo
or two in those panels...
who's gonna give a stupid answer, and
Charlie's always gonna get those, right?
- So...
- Yeah, I'll get the steal.
- Yeah. - Plus, people don't even
really eat sea urchin, Dennis.
Most people don't eat dragons.
- Well, dragonflies.
- People don't eat dragonflies.
Don't make that noise. I don't like it.
Just relax, would you, Dennis?
If we make asses out of ourselves, they just
won't air the episode.
Okay, first of all, you don't know that.
And secondly, don't tell me to relax.
All right, don't you start making that noise.
It's not funny when they do it.
It's definitely not funny...
Oh! Ooh!
Oh, goddamn it!
And welcome back to Family Fight.
We got the Reynolds family
over here with 100 points.
We got the Barretts over here with zero.
Give me Bobby, give me Dennis!
Here we go!
Okay. Oh, hey, Bobby, all right.
All right, somebody got
a little... a little lead in his shoes.
No.
No. No,
my shoes are fine. I assure you.
They're made of the finest Italian leather.
The fit is perfect.
Therefore, there would be no room for lead.
All right.
Top four answers on the board.
We asked a hundred people on the street, "Name
something people groom themselves with."
Dennis!
- Laser beams, Grant.
- La-Laser beams.
Yeah, laser beam. It's the only way to
completely obliterate the follicle.
Show me laser beam!
- Ooh!
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
That noise, it's too loud.
Can we... Can we just turn it down a touch?
We cannot, we cannot.
Bobby, you got an answer?
- I got an answer.
- All right.
- Hair brush!
- Show me hair brush!
Okay, we want to play!
Hair brush, that's so obvious.
God, that buzzer noise!
Isn't that just irritating as hell?
- We gotta think of a steal here.
- I got one!
What about bleaching cream
for your facial hair?
- What the hell?
- No, no.
- I-I got it... Drakkar Noir.
- Mmm, too specific.
You know what it is? I think it's a bride.
A bride could be a good answer.
- Show me clippers!
- What?
You can't become a groom
or get groomed without a bride.
- Oh, no.
- Right, right.
That's not the kind of grooming
they're talking about.
- I don't know. Charlie could be right.
- Yeah. I got dragon.
No, he's not... He's not right.
Because nobody else is that stupid.
Show me pumice stone!
All right, here we go.
Reynolds family for the steal!
- No, no, we're not gonna say that.
- The comb, a comb!
I'm gonna go with...
toe knife.
Wi-With what now?
With a toe knife, 'cause I... I use a-a...
a sharp blade to dig the scum
out of my toenails.
Once in a while, I cut myself...
but it "puses" up,
and in three days, it's good as new.
- Sure.
- Toe knife!
- Way more information than we
needed, but, uh... -
Show me toe knife.
The Barretts win the board!
There you go! All right!
Okay, let's see what...
see what that last answer was.
Bride!
- Charlie was right.
- I knew it.
Do you... Do you groom a bride, Lisa?
All right, hey,
let's get on to that last round now!
I need some Dee, I need
a little bit of Lester! Come on down!
- Okay.
- Come on, Dee!
All right.
- Okay, here we go. Top six answers
are on the board. -
Name something that people are afraid of.
- Oh!
- Whoa! Oh!
Oh, oopsie-daisy!
Looks like I... I broke it.
- You think?
- Oops.
Can't believe... Ain't never seen anything
like that in my life.
What, do you got hands made of anvils?
You want me to answer that
or answer the... this one?
- I don't want you to answer either
of them, okay? - Yeah, sorry.
Because I don't know who won
because you broke the machine.
- That makes sense. It makes sense, yeah.
- Right? Okay?
Okay. Everybody, we're gonna
take a couple seconds.
- We'll be right back after this.
- Okay.
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh!
Start thinking of a steal,
because if we get this one, we win the game.
- All right, all right. What's the question?
- Things people are afraid of.
- That's still the question? - Yes. How do
you not know how the game works by now?
Okay, I'm afraid of game show rules.
- You guys, I know what it is.
- Yeah?
- It's failure.
- That's too pathetic.
Liberal yahoos taking my guns.
That... That is a political
firestorm, Frank. No!
Oh, oh! The Nightman.
All right, guys,
these are terrible answers, all right?
Now, normally I would've said the crust on
a crème brûlée burning the top of your mouth...
but I'm thinking like a commoner now,
and I really do think...
that the right answer is probably... clowns.
- That's a good answer.
- I know.
- I feel it could be Nightman.
- No, I feel like it isn't the Nightman...
He could be right, dude.
Show me dogs!
God...
No.
Okay, Reynolds, you get a chance to steal...
and win the whole game right here.
- Okay. All right.
- Name something that people are afraid of.
We're gonna go with...
Wait, wait, Frank. You have to say it
in the form of a question.
- What is it...
- No, you don't, you don't...
You don't have to do that
'cause it's not Jeopardy!
- Ah, it's not Jeopardy!
- All right?
Say "show me," Frank.
Don't say "show me," Frank.
Just say the word. Just say the word.
- Show me clowns.
- Show me clowns!
We did it! We did it!
And the Reynolds win the game!
The Reynolds win the game!
Sha-booyah, sha-booyah,
sha-booyah, you lose!
sha-booyah, you lose! Woo-hoo!
All right, okay. So, anyway...
Let's take a look
at the last one, everybody.
Nightman. Don't know what that is.
- Just don't know what it is.
- What is happening?
Pretty strange answers today!
All right, man. We're gonna come right back
and play some Fast Money.
- How the hell was "Nightman" an answer?
- Right.
Dude, I think I'm remembering what happened.
I took this survey.
I got interviewed at a mall and I thought it
was, like, a government thing.
- Okay, all right.
- That makes a lot more sense.
- That's actually the only thing that makes sense.
- Right? Okay.
So I should play Fast Money,
because I'm gonna know all the answers.
No, no, no, you're only
gonna know your answers.
And that's only gonna
get us one point for every question.
- We need to get all the top answers to win
Fast Money. - Right, totally, totally.
- And then we spin the wheel.
- Okay, you're definitely not gonna play...
- 'cause you can't understand a thing
that's happening. - I'll play.
No, you won't play, because you've been
nothing but gross and foul...
and polarizing the entire time.
- You're embarrassing me in front
of the whole nation. Dee... - Mmm.
- You and I are gonna play.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
- Can I do my fart key chain?
Absolutely goddamn not. Now go get something
to eat. You look terrible.
No, no, no. I'm very hungry, but I'm not
gonna blow it now. This is my close-up.
Oh, God, don't be
a dumb, hungry bitch the entire time.
- Guys, we're back.
- Ooh!
All right, you're going first, Dee.
- You're going first.
- Come on, Dee! Go, Dee!
All right, we are back with Fast Money,
here with Dee Reynolds.
But first, there's somebody who
wants to say something to you.
Yeah? Hey, Reynolds family!
Win 20,000 and bring home
the money for Paddy's Pub!
Yeah, all right.
- I'm done dancing like a monkey. Give me my
five bucks, Charlie. -
Ha-ha, wow! That was a rough video right
there. That dude is hard on the eyes.
Yeah. He's all burned up.
- We couldn't get anybody else?
- No.
- Okay, you ready, Dee?
- Oh, you better believe it.
- But, uh...
- Mm-hmm?
First, hold on a... hold on a second.
- Yeah?
- There's, um...
- There's, uh... Ooh!
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- You all right?
Uh, yes. There's a...
Just a quick bit I wanted to, uh...
- Oof.
- Oh!
Oh, whoops-a-daisy.
That's about as lowbrow as it gets.
Yeah, Dennis isn't gonna like that.
- It's pretty funny though.
- Okay, new plan.
All right.
- This is so good.
- Yeah.
So we're back here with,
uh, Fast Money here.
Uh, and now we got Frank doing it, 'cause...
people just be faintin' up in here, so...
Okay, give me 30 seconds on the clock.
- Name something you thought existed
when you were a child. - Santa Claus.
- Name something you might find in a bathtub.
- Soap!
- Name something people add sugar to.
- Coffee.
- A thing you associate with Charlie Chaplin.
- Little mustache.
- Name a foreign country whose films
are popular in America. - France.
Damn!
You did it, man! That was great!
- Yeah, man! That was really good!
- That was so good, Frank!
- Hey, you ready?
- Yeah, I'm ready.
- Frank did great.
- Frank?
- Yeah, uh, Dee passed out.
- She...
- Of course she did. She's so embarrassing.
- Right.
All right, here we go, everybody. We're
gonna bring Dennis out right now.
Here he is, Dennis Reynolds.
- Here we go.
- Yeah, Dennis!
All right.
Okay. Now, Dennis...
Frank got the number one answer
for every single question...
- so you only need five points to win the game.
- Okay, I can do it.
- Now, Grant, listen, I know I gave
some bad answers before. - Yes.
But I understand the game perfectly now,
and, uh, that does not represent me.
- I like that.
- So I'm ready to give good answers.
- That does represent me.
All right, that sounds good.
If you repeat any of Frank's answers...
you're gonna hear this sound.
- Mm-hmm. And then...
- Thought we were done with the buzzer.
- Oh, only if you repeat an answer.
- Even in this round?
Yes, even in this round. Yep. Mm-hmm.
If you don't know an answer,
you can say "pass"...
- and we'll just move on to the next question.
- Okay.
- All right, are you ready?
- Yes, yes.
Thirty seconds on the clock.
- Name something you thought existed
when you were a child. - Santa Claus.
Oh, God. Uh, pass.
- Name something you might find in a bathtub.
- S... Uh, soap.
Ah!
God, I really hate that buzzer.
- Can we not do that?
- Clock's ticking.
- Okay, uh, pass.
- Name something people add sugar to.
God. Coffee.
- Oh, God.
- No, no.
- Nope, we gotta... We need an answer.
- Yeah, no, no.
Okay, no, then pass, then pass, 'cause...
- A thing you associate with Charlie Chaplin.
- Mmm... Pass.
Mm-hmm. Okay, name a foreign
country whose films are popular in America.
France.
- Oh, God, no, no!
- Already said that.
Oh, God, France. France...
- That's still not the answer.
- Little mustache.
Soap, soap, France.
- Say something!
- Go with something else!
You said that already. Don't say "France."
- Give up.
- All right.
I have never seen a more embarrassing
display in my entire career.
Oh, but please don't air this.
Okay?
Please don't... don't air this.
- You won't air this, right?
- We definitely air it. We always air it.
- No matter what. That's how we do it.
- But this went so wrong.
Good night, everybody!
Thanks for joining us here on Family Fight!
- This doesn't represent me.
- Take care.
- Ah, God!
- Why'd they have to air that part?
- That was the end part.
- The best part.
Yeah, they air the whole show.
This doesn't represent me though.
This doesn't represent me.
That's not who I am.
So just... So just don't air it.
- It's the buzzer that was...
- This doesn't represent me.
So just don't air it!
Ripped By mstoll
Happy New Year 2016 - New Year, New Color ;-)