Ripped By mstoll
Happy New Year 2016 - New Year, New Color ;-)
My apartment is not a spa.
Dennis and I are gonna take a soak.
You and Dennis are going to bathe together?
It's that Turkish bath thing.
What are you worried about?
I'm not worried about anything...
but my apartment is not
a Turkish bath, okay?
Well, Dee, this is
Dennis's apartment now too.
No. No, goddamn it, it's not, all right?
Mac and Dennis do not live here.
- What the hell is this?
- One more!
Stop!
- Hey!
- Good set, boys!
What are you doing?
Oh, Dee, this is Jojo...
- Tiny, Charlie you know.
- I don't care.
Together, we are Ass Kickers United.
You guys, come on, please. I don't want you
doing your weird routines in here!
It's not a routine, Dee,
and there is nothing weird about this, okay?
Ass Kickers United is a way of life...
based on the life-improvement
teachings of the Master.
What kind of cult shit is that?
No, no, it's not a cult, Frank.
The Master is the only
human to ever achieve enlightenment...
through the way of the warrior.
Snap, two, three.
One, two, seven, three, nine.
Come on. Goddamn it!
Frank, I can't get this Fight
Milk out of the goddamn couch!
Oh! Shit!
It burned a hole in the cushion!
That's probably the crotein.
Don't get that on your skin!
Hey-oh! Frank! Frank,
sorry I'm late, man, but, uh, good news.
I brought checkers. Oh, what's up, Dee?
I got dominoes, and what the hell is going
on? Your place looks like shit.
- What happened?
- Yeah, it does. I'll tell you what happened.
Mac and his goddamn
Ass Blasters Incorporated...
were in here jerking around all day.
Mac, Charlie and a bunch
of goons started a queer club.
- Hmm.
- They got a newsletter.
Oh, shit. "Ass Kickers United."
- Oh, my God.
- What?
- Dee, Mac didn't start this club. I did.
- What are you talking about?
Yeah. I, uh... I just made this shit up
about Ass Kickers United...
to get Mac to stop eating my Thin Mints.
- Huh?
- You know how Mac is all irritating and shit?
- Of course.
- The worst!
Right. He was doing all this irritating shit
and he was driving me crazy.
Worst of all, he was eating
all my Thin Mint cookies...
and, so, you know, playing
on Mac's physical insecurities...
I decided I would get
in his head a little bit.
So I created this Master character,
all right?
I typed up this newsletter...
which was mostly about fitness
and, like, just kicking ass...
at life in general, just kind
of speaking Mac's language.
But mostly, I was speaking of the dangers of
consuming too many Thin Mint cookies.
And I'll tell you, it worked like a charm...
'cause he stopped eating
Thin Mints almost immediately.
- That... is extremely impressive.
- Oh.
Dennis, I missed most of that last part.
Run it by me again.
Frank, I just spoke for five straight
minutes. I'm not doing it again.
- Dennis started a cult.
- No, I didn't start a cult.
Sure sounds like a cult.
Hey, I got a great idea.
Why don't you type up another newsletter...
and tell Mac and his dum-dum friends...
to go and fix up your apartment, right?
That way, you guys can get out of my place.
Or maybe get some broads involved.
Cults are great for attracting new age tail.
Guys, you can't go straight to fixing
apartments and getting young, new age tail.
You can't do that.
That takes years of brainwashing.
Here's the problem. If you don't do that
and write the newsletter...
and fix up the apartment,
then I'm gonna rat you out.
- Come on.
- I'm gonna have to. You know why?
I'm up to here. I've had a very bad day!
I'm at the end of my rope...
- Okay, Dee, calm down.
- If I'm being honest.
All right, look, I'll test
the waters a little bit, okay?
See if we can get 'em there slowly.
Maybe you can get 'em
to eat a shit sandwich. That would be fun.
Why the hell would I... What?
No, this isn't about fun.
This is about...
It's about Thin Mints, goddamn it! Right?
And the reason I'm so good
at this is because I take it seriously.
Now, just watch and learn.
Listen up!
According to the Master, guys...
we're not getting enough vitamin D.
So these stickers harness
the power of the sun...
and deliver it directly to our bodies, okay?
And, apparently, guys,
there's another exercise.
Yes, sensei!
All right, now, they're
called hammer jerks...
and it's sort of like
a hammer, then you bend.
- Then you snap, then you jerk.
- Ow.
- Then a hammer.
- Hammer!
- Now bend!
- Bend.
- Snap.
- Damn it.
- Jerk.
- Oh, yeah.
Hammer, bend, snap...
jerk.
Hammer...
I can't believe they went
for the sticker thing.
Thank you. Thank you.
Okay, time to dial it up a notch.
Let's put 'em to work
and get 'em to your apartment.
We can't just dive into that shit.
We talked about this.
It's a slow burn.
They're wearing stickers on their heads.
They're there.
Look, look, look, stop.
You guys are going crazy.
You're gonna blow the Thin Mint thing.
Will you just trust me? I got this.
I am the Master.
I'm gonna get you what you want.
You just got to let me do my thing.
- That sounds... That sounds good.
- Mm, yeah, okay.
- You gonna goddamn blow this for me?
- No.
- You gonna blow the Thin Mint thing?
- "The Master saith."
- Yeah.
"Kicking ass in life is all about drywall."
And pussy. Put "pussy."
Goddamn, Frank, don't say "pussy."
- It's disgusting. I'm not putting it.
- Mmm.
"To be a total badass...
- you must learn carpentry.
- Mmm.
Fixing apartments is what you must do."
And buy Wolf Cola.
Let's make some coin.
Okay.
"And buy Wolf Cola, the only
cola for true refreshment."
That's good.
- "Splash into the beast."
- Mm-hmm, that's great.
I know it is. Cool it with the jerky, will
you? You're driving me nuts.
- Now, put-put "bring pussy."
- Goddamn it. All right, fine.
- Just put it.
- Hey, listen! This is what I'll do.
"Ladies are now mandatory.
Each of you dick-bags must
recruit at least one woman."
Should we put anything else?
- Make 'em eat a shit sandwich.
- What is it with you?
Do you really want to see
somebody take a roll...
and stick doody in it
and put it in their mouth?
- God! You are so gross.
- Nah.
Okay, so, how much for the Wolf Colas?
- Five bucks apiece.
- Okay, great. Ma, how many you want?
I'll take three.
Okay. And Mrs. Mac?
- Sh-She'll have one.
- Huh?
One. Any more caffeine
than that, and she will not stop talking.
Really? Oh, kind of want to see that.
Charlie, can I talk to you for a second?
- Yeah. What's up?
- Um, does all this seem kind of strange to you?
Huh? Uh... Oh! You mean the Wolf Cola thing?
Yeah. I was wondering.
Like, how does the Master
know about Wolf Cola?
Oh, he's an aficionado of all beverages.
He's gonna know the finest of colas.
Oh, oh. You mean the carpentry thing. Yeah.
No. Throughout history,
uh, Ass Kickers have always known carpentry.
- Jesus Christ, Harrison Ford.
- Right, okay.
- Then what are you talking about?
- The women. The women, dude.
This is supposed to be a men's club, you
know? Who wants that around?
Oh. Uh...
I don't know. I'm kind of cool with it.
Also, I don't ever remember
anything in the newsletters about no women.
It could not have been more clear...
no women, no gays.
I don't ever remember you
reading anything about that.
It was implied, okay?
Look, in these kind of texts,
you need to be able to in... infer what's be...
Look, I'll explain it to you later.
I think I'm just gonna...
I need some time off.
Whoa. Hey, man, you can't take a day off
from kicking ass, okay?
Look, an Ass Kicker
must be present every day.
An Ass Kicker must do the exercises.
An Ass Kicker must avoid Thin Mints.
I know the rules, okay? I don't need to...
I'm gonna go.
I'm gonna go. I'm just gonna go.
- You're just gonna go?
- I mean...
I mean...
Okay, I'm taking the men with me,
and Frank's got the women.
Oh, cool. Are you an Ass Kicker now?
- I'm an Ass Kicker now.
- Sweet. Who signed you up?
- The dumb one.
- Oh, Tiny?
No, no, no. The one eating
paint chips off the wall.
These taste like paint.
Uh, yeah, those are paint chips there, pal.
- These are?
- Yeah.
- Oh, they're delicious.
- Yeah, that's the good paint.
Let's go.
All right, let's go. Hey, we're gonna, uh,
go swing some hammers.
Oh, you guys, it's so great
that you do construction.
I mean, this is just gonna be easy...
just slap a couple coats of paint around,
maybe a couple of new doors.
- You're gonna be in and out in a few hours.
- Yeah.
Ha... Oh!
Wow! Shit.
- No wall! That's pretty awesome.
- Okay, boys, let's get to work.
- Yeah.
- Look, I do construction for a living.
I mean, I thought Ass Kickers was just some
sort of fun workout club, you know, like...
- CrossFit.
Hey, man, you don't want to take
this seriously?
Hey, that's fine. Why
don't you give me those stickers back then?
Uh, no, I'm coming down
with a cold and I need mine.
Did you do, like, your deer antler spray?
Some. But I'm running lower.
Have some of mine. Here.
All right, you know what?
I overreacted, boys. I overreacted.
I snapped at you,
and the Master wouldn't like that.
And I'm sorry. I think
maybe this is my mission and my calling.
So why don't you guys find some other
mission and I'll handle this one, okay?
- Thanks, Charlie.
- All right, cool.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
- Goddamn it, Charlie.
- It's fine.
You know, the guys have been
working their asses off. I got this. Look.
Dee, the Master says fix it?
I'm gonna fix it.
Frank, is that you?
Missed you in there, pal.
Still pretty steamy though
if you want to hop in and...
- What the hell's this?
- Just watching a little TV.
- Are those Thin Mints?
- Oh, yeah, big-time, dude. I love these things.
I notice, uh, you're
looking a little out of shape there, bud.
I am?
Yeah. Yeah, and it's a shame too...
because you've been looking
so great lately. So sexy.
- I was?
- Yeah, so to see this is just disappointing.
To me, but, you know...
- This disappoints you?
- Yeah.
What are you doing? You taking a day off
or something? Is that okay?
I'm sure the Master allows
for that though, right?
- Well, I'm not really sure about that.
- Oh, you're not sure, yeah.
Did the Master not make that crystal goddamn
clear in all those newsletters?
- Was that not clear?
- I-I didn't read into it like that.
Wow, wow. I mean, I haven't read
the things, but I've just...
You guys have been telling me.
Thin Mints, from what I understand...
that was a whole thing.
- I think that was, like, rule number...
- Oh, shit.
I... Yeah. I-I...
I-I may have... I messed up a little bit.
I hope he doesn't notice the fat that I'm
noticing sort of accumulated all over.
But maybe he won't notice.
I noticed, but maybe he won't.
- Y-You don't think he would, or...
- No, I think he will.
Uh, do you mind if I use the computer?
I'm just gonna grab this and take it over
here for a little bit, okay?
Mmm.
And snap it back!
Bend and snap.
How's that neck, Cindy? Everything good?
How are the muscles? You feeling okay?
- You may want to soak 'em a little bit.
- Actually, I feel great.
- Oh, you feel great.
- Frank, I'm in tremendous pain.
I'm not talking to you.
I'm talking to her.
I can't breathe.
Oh, she needs a cigarette break.
Could we stop, please?
I don't care what she needs.
I'm not talking to you.
Do whatever you want.
I'm trying to hurt her.
What?
Uh, well, it's... it... I'm...
You have to tear the fascial tissues...
in order to tone the muscles properly.
- Oh.
- According to the Master.
- Okay.
- So you bend and you snap.
But snap your head back.
Bend. You see it?
- Frank?
- And snap!
- Frank, Frank, Frank. We need to talk.
- Yo, Cindy, you keep working.
- Go ahead. Snap it.
- Okay, you got it.
Hey, listen. We gotta make
a bit of an adjustment.
Tiny and Jojo, they don't
want to do the construction...
so I was looking into what cults do
to force people into labor...
when the mind tricks don't work, and one of
them was a personality test, right?
You basically just get a bunch of dirt on
people and you hold it over their heads.
So, blackmail.
Yeah.
So this is a basic personality test.
It's really simple.
It just measures the amount
of... guilt stressors that you're feeling.
You know, I took it,
and I just... It's changed my life.
What are guilt stressors?
Yeah, Dee, what... what are guilt stressors?
Oh, great question. Great question.
Apparently,
secrets and lies lead to guilt stressors...
and that's not good, you guys.
You know why?
It impedes muscle development.
- I have read that.
- Oh, really?
- Well, it's science. It's just basic science.
- Oh, shit.
It does sound like good science.
You guys just hang on to that machine and
talk about all your regrets.
And what are regrets again?
Y-You just talk about things you feel
really guilty about.
- Oh.
- Oh, okay. Uh, okay.
- Do you want to...
- I'll go. Dee, where do my feet go?
- Oh, it doesn't matter.
- Okay, uh...
I ate a baby toad once. I'm not proud of it.
Uh, just kind of happened.
- It pains me to think about how scared
and confused it was... - Mm-hmm.
And wondering, "Why am I not home...
and why am I in some sort
of acid pond that's burning my skin?"
What if it was looking for its mother?
It was a baby.
I got an idea. How about we let one of these
guys, uh, give it a shot.
- I'll go.
- I don't feel better, but all right.
- Where do my feet go?
- Dee, his feet?
- It doesn't make a goddamn difference.
- Okay.
- I ate a toad too.
- Oh, God.
- Really?
- I did.
- Do it again, like that?
- Yeah, do it again.
- Go ahead.
- Whoo!
Oh, I feel the burn.
Yeah, how's...
how's the neck feeling? How's the neck?
You know, it's not bad.
- It's actually a little tight.
- It's a little tight.
Well, how about
if we hop in the healing pool.
- Okay.
- I'll give you some touch therapy...
so you don't seem too weak for the Master.
- Yeah.
- I don't suppose that could hurt.
- No, that won't hurt.
Oh, shit.
Oh, hi.
The water's wonderful.
- When did you get in here?
- You don't mind that we came in first, do you?
- There's plenty of room.
- No, how long are you gonna be?
Well...
- Oh, God.
- She thinks she has a tear in her uterine wall...
so it might be a while.
All right. L-Let's go.
Oh, God.
I'm gonna go do a few sets of kettle pops
while I run the block a few times.
- Yeah.
- Don't want to disappoint the Master.
- You want to come?
- Go... You go get yourself good and banged up.
- Okay!
- Oh, yeah.
Guys, guys, guys,
there's been a mistake, a terrible mistake.
I got a new newsletter from the Master.
There's gonna be no more women,
no more Wolf Cola...
and no more carpentry in Ass Kickers United.
This has all been a test...
designed by the Master to figure out who
the true believers are.
I passed, you failed,
and that's why I'm going to level two.
Oh, also, uh, Dennis will
be level two as well...
but he'll be directly under me.
Wh-What? Where'd you get that from?
- It was implied in the newsletter.
- No.
How is Dennis in level two?
Or an Ass Kicker, for that matter?
- Oh, he bought in.
- He... bought in?
Come on, Ass Kickers,
let's get out of here...
- before we're tainted by these
disgusting women. - Mm-hmm.
All right. God, crazy. Failed that test.
Go kick some ass, huh? Go kick some ass!
- Hmm. - Thought you could
outmaster the Master, idiots?
So you swayed 'em back.
Uh, whatever. We can do that too.
Dee, you think this is easy?
You need years of practice
to even sniff my talent for manipulation.
Now, if you'll excuse me, I have a cult that
needs a charismatic leader.
Yeah.
Goddamn it, Frank. Goddamn it!
No. No, we cannot let him
get away with this.
No, this is about something different now,
something much more important.
- Shit sandwich?
- What? Why? What is that? No!
God. No, this is about control now.
This is about control,
and it's about beating Dennis.
Mmm.
I know exactly what we need to do.
Hmm.
Deandra, we're all set.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- He's out?
- He's lit.
I have so much alcohol in here.
I gave him three bottles of Fight Milk.
Whoa. That's a lot.
Okay, you ready? Got your cards?
- Okay.
Here we go.
Charlie.
- Say it louder.
- Charlie, wake up!
Huh? What's... What's...
What's happening?
It is I...
the Master!
- Am I dreaming?
- You're having a vision.
- Am I peeing?
- Uh...
- Is he peeing?
- Just read the card.
You and the other Ass Kickers must con...
con...
What's that word?
- Congregate.
- "Congregate"? What does that mean?
It doesn't matter. Just say it.
Congregate.
- What does that mean?
- Oh, God. You know what? Just...
Hey, Charlie, hey.
Get all the Ass Kickers together and meet at
Mac and Dennis's apartment, okay?
Lord Zolo is gonna get you
on the mother ship.
Lord Zolo?
Charlie, you've graduated to the next level.
Congratulations.
And your reward is to get
to know all the secrets of the universe.
Yeah, there's just
a few things you have to do.
Okay. I'll do them.
I'm peeing.
- Uh-oh.
- Oh.
Okay, you guys...
Holy shit!
Whoa! What the hell happened in here?
You like it?
Yeah, well, before Master Rex said...
that we weren't supposed to do carpentry...
I talked to Tiny and Jojo and they got their
construction crew in here.
- There's a wall.
- Oh, you're goddamn right there's a wall.
I'm good. Dennis is gonna shit his pants.
Why? What are you good at?
Good at my...
I'm a good person, and you know what?
It's time to... to do the plan...
that the Master laid out, right?
I'm gonna take Tiny in the other room
and make the pods ready.
- Come on, Tiny.
- We got pods?
Of course we got pods.
Lord Zolo's gonna take you guys
on that mother ship with him. You need pods.
- Am I right, Master?
- Do... Do I get a pod?
Okay, guys, guys, guys, we got a...
Uh, wow. Holy shit.
- That's a wall.
- Yeah. This place looks great.
You're goddamn right this place looks great.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's pretty
impressive stuff, Dee, but, uh...
it doesn't seal the deal.
I've got an announcement.
I've got some big news here.
The Master texted me while we were
on our way over here.
Oh, interesting.
Uh, I wonder how it's possible that the
Master could've texted you...
when he's been here with us the whole time.
Rex is the Master?
- That makes so much sense.
- Yep.
Yes. Of course I know that Rex...
is the Master, and of course I would never
question the word of someone so... wise.
But I actually got
a text from the Supreme Overlord Master.
And that's Rex's master.
- Oh, shit. - "Oh, shit" is right, you
guys. That's... He's the big guy.
He sits right at the tippy-tippy-top, and he
made it very, very clear to me...
that all of you are going to need to...
commit suicide.
Tits! I knew it! The final circle.
Yeah, okay, sure, but hang on a second.
- Can I please talk to you for
just a quick second? - Sure.
Why don't you guys get yourselves lathered
up in lighter fluid...
and, uh, you're gonna get ready
to light yourselves ablaze.
- Thanks for trusting me.
- Yeah, of course.
I did it. I won.
I am the most charismatic leader.
I got Tiny to eat a shit sandwich.
- Ugh!
- Oh!
Goddamn it!
I got him to eat a poopy.
You idiot!
I got these guys to think
they were going to another dimension.
- I'm the winner.
- Are you kidding me?
They were gonna light
themselves on fire for me. I'm the winner.
- Oh. - Guys, guys, hang on a
second. The winner of what?
The... The Ass Kickers, okay?
The winner of the Ass Kickers.
It's mine. It's not theirs.
- What? - It's mine. The whole
thing's made up. I made it up.
Master Rex, is this true?
Oh, don't ask Rex. What...
The fire is started.
Thank you so much for trusting me with this.
This is good-bye!
- Goddamn it! No, not again!
- Don't do it!
- Whoa!
- Run!
Hey! We'll get you some help, okay?
- We'll call the fire department.
- Oh, God.
- Yeah.
- And then we'll go to Dee's.
- No, no, no. Can't we go anywhere else?
- No, Dee.
What if the Supreme Overlord
tries to contact us?
- He has to know where we are.
- Yeah, exactly.
All right, well, at least
he's on the mother ship now.
- Yeah.
- Oh, my God! Unbelievable!
Come on, let's go. Get help. Let's go.
Good luck, Jojo!
Thank you! Aah!
Ripped By mstoll
Happy New Year 2016 - New Year, New Color ;-)