Uh... I feel like
you guys should have,
like, dressed up
a little bit for this.
No, no, it sends
the wrong image, you know?
Uh, we're not selling
a game for squares,
we're selling a game for, like,
everyday people like us, man.
Yeah, that's a good point.
Oh, Frank, Frank, Frank.
You will never guess
what happened. Okay.
So this guy comes in, right?
We think he's just
a regular customer.
We start chatting him up.
Turns out, he's an
executive at Mattel.
Yeah, so of course
we start talking
to him about Chardee MacDennis,
and he seemed totally into it.
Yeah, he's coming by today, man.
We're gonna pitch it to him.
Maybe we could, uh, work in
some of the ideas
I've been suggesting.
Those aren't "ideas"
as much as they are...
random acts of violence.
Well, you see, when I was a kid,
games were much more violent.
I mean, we used to play
"Purple Nurple,"
"Sock Full of Quarters,"
"Kick the Jew"...
No, why don't you
try winning one time?
And then you can start
throwing in new rules.
How about we just change
the name of the game then?
"Franken MacChardeeden."
What?
That's terrible.
First of all,
your name isn't "Franken."
Secondly, Chardee MacDennis
is just a working title.
Technically, we're still
in arbitration.
Last we left it,
Dee had filibustered,
and Charlie had
a motion pending.
And I will not yield
to the gentleman.
'Cause you have no honor,
you goddamn bitch.
You have no honor!
You see what I'm talking about--
it's a whole thing, Frank.
Then let's call it "Chardee
MacDennis 2: Electric Boogaloo."
What?
What are you talking about?
What does that have
to do with anything?
What made you just
think of that?
It's not a break-dancing
competition.
There's no electricity involved.
Uh-uh-uh-uh.
Hey, there, how's it
going, uh... Andy was it?
Yes, exactly.
Ah, Andy, I want you to meet Frank.
Frank, uh, meet Andy
from Mattel.
Hello, hello.
I got to tell ya--
I'm pretty excited.
Adult game play is
a fast-rising market,
and we are always on the lookout
for something a little
out of the box.
Oh, we-we can help
you there, bud.
That's great. Now, what was
the name of the game again?
Chardee MacDennis 2:
Electric Boogaloo.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Okay, Andy, you're gonna like
this video we made for you.
Chardee MacDennis.
Chardee MacDennis is all your
favorite games rolled into one:
Mouse Trap,
Chutes and Ladders, Sorry...
But it's not exactly
like those things.
It's also like Boggle,
Wheel of Fortune, Risk.
Chardee MacDennis!
What other games do you like?
It's like those other games too!
But more better.
And different enough legally.
I'm a lawyer.
Shh!
I'm a lawyer in this part.
We're like Moby...
remix!
Ch-Ch-Chardee MacDennis!
Regular board games
should be called...
"I'm bored... games"
I don't get that one.
I... No, I told you not to...
Stay out of my peripheral...
Do you want a game that lulls
you into a sense of security,
but surprises you
with constant rule changes?
Then you want
the game of games...
Back... back up.
Sorry.
Chardee MacDennis!
We always win.
And they always lose.
What are you guys doing over there?
Oh, shit.
W-Why'd you put that in?
Yeah, what was that?
Factually accurate.
So, Andy, what did you think?
I... got to say,
it's a little confusing.
Uh, can't we just play the game?
Ooh. Ooh, ooh, ooh.
Yeah.
That wouldn't be good.
Yeah, see, we tend to get a
little competitive when we play.
You know, we're not exactly
a mellow bunch.
Right. That'll be fun.
Plus, that's the best way
for me to understand the game.
But that's what... why you would understand...
Yeah, that's why we did that.
Okay, let me confer
with my associates for a minute.
Why don't you grab a drink?
It's o-on the house, of course.
Um, guys, can we talk?
Uh, cool, man.
I think we can probably, um...
We can't...
No, no, no... no, no,
I-I think we can.
Uh, we can do this, guys.
We just got to be...
just got to make it fun.
You know what we have to do?
Is we have to not care
about who wins. Just for this time.
Yes.
That'll help. That will help.
We just have to sell the game.
Just sell it. Okay. We can do it.
All right,
so, Frank, you'll
be on Andy's team.
Wait, don't
stick me with him. He-he
doesn't know the goddamn rules.
I'm gonna get crushed again.
Shut up, Frank, just...
Shut up. Shut up. It's not
about winning or losing.
Exactly. It doesn't matter. It's fun.
We're not gonna care...
It's fun.
So we'll just...
we'll keep our emotions
in check.
Yeah.
Sure.
Just be like:
Exactly.
Gentlemen, good luck to you.
And to yous. And to yous all.
This is nice--
a little role playing.
Very big in gaming right now.
This also celebrates
sportsmanship.
Yes, indeed. Yeah, well,
you're totally getting it.
You're catching on.
Oh, by the way, there used to be
a couple rules about not cursing
and not asking questions
in certain rounds, but I think
we should do away with that,
for now, because it's your
first time playing and, guys,
we don't want
anybody blacking out.
Yeah, no problem. Right, that's fine.
I think that'll be fine.
We're flexible.
It's a good idea.
Okay, are we ready?
Three, two, one.
Gentlemen...
suck my dick.
Hut,
hut, hut.
What the hell's going on?
Oh, uh, this is our
flag-raising ceremony.
Yeah, we used to do
the Maori war dance,
but that-that got us
a little too riled up.
Either way, this is
all about intimidation
and showing off your prowess.
Uh, think of it like
the Indian-Pakistani
border ceremony
that they do over there.
Now, this is Mac
and Charlie's flag,
which, as you can see,
is fairly badly burned.
Not only does the winner get to
stomp the loser's game pieces,
but they also get to
burn their flag up.
Now, you'll notice
that the Golden Geese flag
is unsullied.
You'll also notice that
Mac and Charlie's flag is
just a little weird,
and that's because
their original name
was the Thundercats,
uh... but they were
confused by that.
Well, 'cause we're not cats.
Yeah.
We're not cats.
So, then, how could we...
Mm-hmm. Even though
it's the name they chose.
So they went with
the Thundermen.
This brings us to Frank's flag,
which is, uh... yeah,
it's just unfortunate.
It's four Fs.
I didn't know it was
gonna come off like that.
Pretty sure you did.
Okay, Andy, Level 1 is Trivia,
Puzzles and Artistry.
The first team
to get three points
moves their game piece
to the next level.
All right. Here we go.
All right.
What Philly celebrity would you most
want to have a drink with? Oh, shit,
okay, yeah, you know what--
a lot of the questions
are opinion-based. Heads up.
Ah. Okay... I-I see.
Uh, all right, this is,
uh, let me guess. Um...
Oh: Dr. J.
That's not it! All
right, all right.
Play it cool, play it cool.
Okay, okay, sorry.
Yeah, all right. That is wrong,
though. You wouldn't
want to have a drink with him.
Dee, chance to steal.
Bill Cosby. Yes! All right.
Point for us.
Shit.
A lot of the questions
are outdated.
Yeah, yeah, they are
a little outdated.
Okay, our turn, our turn.
Um, artistry. And it's
an all-play, guys.
Oh! Oh!
All right, now,
a member of each team
must make this clue out of clay
while the other member
tries to guess what it is.
Okay, uh, penis.
What?
Uh, lip-penis.
What? No, look, look.
Oh, hard penis.
A hard clay penis.
Oh...
Gargoyle inside.
No?
It's a-a, okay,
a chopped-off head,
a decapitat...
uh, head in a box!
Dee, I'm gonna put
your head in a box
if you don't start
getting the answer right.
Goddamn it!
A heart, it's a heart!
Uh, it's, uh...
it's, uh, love!
Love!
Oh! He got it! Was that it?
Get another card. How
do you make a heart?
If the... Love?
Yeah, because I was making,
uh, Cupid's arrow, dude.
Well, why does it have
a big vein running through it?
Because that's the streak
as it flies through the air.
Come... At least I didn't
put a woman's head in a box.
This is not a woman's head
in a box, you sick freak.
This is a woman's
head in a freezer.
And it's supposed to represent
the preservation
of love forever and ever.
Whatever, dude. It's our turn,
it's our turn. We go.
No puzzles, no puzzles,
no puzzles, no puzzles
no puzzles, no puzzles...
Puzzles.
Oh!
Put this bottle back together.
Oh, shit.
Oh. Yeah.
Oh, that's interesting.
What bottle?
This one.
Now just be very, very careful.
Okay.
Final touches, final touches.
Watch that blue string--
don't pull it apart.
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, okay. All right.
Ready, ready?
Okay, okay,
okay... okay.
Okay, very... Very careful.
Very, very careful.
It held.
It held!
It held! Just swallowed a
little glass, but it held, man!
You see, that's what I'm talking
about-- you sacrifice,
you put the work in...
That's right!
you earn that card.
We're catching up to 'em.
Hey... Okay,
it's our turn, then.
Dennis and Dee
skip right to Level 2.
Yes, yes! Aw... Aw...
Face, face!
Due to some alcohol-related
cheating, we decided
to incorporate I.V.'s
to keep everything
on the up-and-up.
You guys were the ones that were cheating.
Yeah, yeah.
Now, I feel like Andy
has to have one of these.
Well, Andy's our guest.
We don't want to be
poking him with needles.
Unfair, unfair!
Yeah, unfair, unfair, unfair.
Hey, hey, as you can see,
Mac and Charlie
are a little worked up about
never having won the game. Ever.
I'm a little concerned
about the safety of this.
The... Why... Oh, oh,
If it were beer?
No, no, no, no--
we're mainlining wine.
It's not beer. We switched
Level 2 to wine because
you can't mainline beer because
it's got bubbles in it and shit.
We tried-- it was bad.
I'm not sure it's safe
for people to put those
beverages directly in... Time!
Oh!
Okay, Andy, welcome to Round 2:
Physical Challenge,
Pain and Endurance.
Okay, now, we've added
a new challenge
to Level 2-- this is,
this is really exciting.
So what you do-- you spin the
globe, you point your finger.
Wherever your finger lands,
you have to speak in the accent
of that region for
the rest of the round,
otherwise, you gotta drink.
That sounds fun.
That's a great idea.
Isn't that good?
Let's go.
Uh... ha!
Russia!
Oh, okay, so I got it.
I guess I...
I guess I got to do that?
Huh?
You do Russia.
Hey, look at Andy, look at Andy.
Okay, let's see...
What do you got?
"Brasial."
No, Brazil.
Mm-hmm.
Wh-What's the accent
of Brazil?
It's a-it's a country in South
America-- why don't we say
any Latin American accent'll do?
Any Latin American? Okay.
Okay, homie.
Uh... Hola, le homes.
Yeah, I can do that. Yeah.
Okay, man. Nachos.
Oh, real racist with it, huh? Yeah, that
is extremely racist-- and by the way,
that's more of a Los Angeles
sort of Mexican cholo vibe.
Let's go... let's go see the Dodgers
play the Lakers. Low rider.
Okay. Uh, Dee, you
want to spin for us?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Jesus Christ.
Oh! Ah, would you
look at that--
Philadelphia.
That shouldn't be on there.
You barely spinned it, homes.
That's bullshit, man.
Hallelujah.
Looks like the tide's turned.
Yeah, looks like
we got an advantage
over yous guys, huh, Den?
What is going on?
What the hell is that?
My Philly accent.
Wow, that's not even close.
Drink, homes.
Ow! Okay, slower.
All right.
Physical challenge.
And this one's an all-play.
Oh! Hey! Okay,
everybody.
This is good. We like...
Hands on a bird body!
A member from each team
must try and keep their hand
on Dee's bony body for
as long as they can.
Dis is shit.
Dis is not good.
I don't understand.
Hang in there, homes. I can't
do it, "mang." I can't do it.
You barely even put your
hand on there already.
Hang in there, man.
I know, but...
Ah! I can't do it, I can't do it!
Oh! Ha!
Mac, that's crazy!
Ay, ay, ay!
Mac and Charlie are out!
Hey, why'd you do that?
I couldn't do it!
Ay, ay, ay!
Oh, violation!
That's not L.A. Mexican.
That's, like, Cartoon Mexican.
We barely even switched it, homie.
No, I don't know.
I'll have a drink, all right?
You got to drink, too.
Oh...
What is so hard
about keeping one
hand on this woman?
She's a very pleasant woman.
She's a very, very pretty woman.
Ugh. Don't sexualize her, dude.
This is bad enough as it is.
Vhat is the matter, Dennis?
Vhy are you zo uncomfortable?
Because the closeness
of your hand to her breast...
Stop. Yeah, stop.
...which is
making you want to have sex
with her?
Don't, don't... oh, goddamn it!
Ugh! Oh... Oh!
Wait, what's...
what's going on?
You stupid idiot.
Oh, my God, you glued
your hand to her!
Cheater! Cheater!
Cheater!
Oh, is that the accent drop?
Yeah, yeah,
all accents are dropped
the minute someone
gets caught cheating. Yeah,
yeah, we have to be able
to break them in
our native tongue
to allow for maximum shame.
Shame, shame, shame...
Shame, shame...
So... so no more I.V.'s?
No, no, no, no. No, no, no, no.
That's a Level 2 game.
You don't want to mainline liquor, buddy.
You don't want to do it.
Still a pretty stiff drink.
Oh, yeah. Things
get ratcheted up
in Level 3.
Then even get worse in Level 4.
There is no Level 4.
Yes, there is:
Mind, body, spirit, horror.
Stop, Frank. Come on.
There's no horror level.
Look, Andy, his ideas
don't represent the game.
They don't represent us.
Okay, pick a card now...
Whoa!
Shits and Ladders.
Oh!
Sort of a play
on Chutes and Ladders.
Oh, yeah. Each member must take
a laxative and get on a ladder.
- The one who can hold it in the
longest wins. - Love this one.
Also known
as Shoots and Splatters.
Poops and Bladders!
Andy!
I'll go get the laxatives.
All right, All right.
Here you go.
Strongest stuff on the market.
All right.
Mm. Oh, that's strong.
Ugh!
I don't like it.
Okay, to the ladders!
I'm already feeling a twinge.
Yeah, I-I feel something.
I don't feel like I
have to poop, though.
I feel weird.
I kind of feel crazy. Like, what is that?
That isn't a laxative,
is it, Frank?
Nope.
Welcome to Level 4,
horror.
Oh. What is this?
Wake up, guys. Wake up.
What's going on?
Hello, gang.
The keys to your cuffs
have been sewn
into your forearm.
Beside you are some tweezers
attached to a car battery.
Last team out of the room loses.
Frank, this is insane.
Let us out of here!
What are you doing?
Everything has to be based
on an existing board game!
That's the whole thing!
Oh, but it is, Dennis.
Ever hear of a game called...
Operation?
Oh, shit.
He's got a point.
Damn it.
Let's go.
- This game is totally insane!
- Don't give up on the game!
The game is fine!
No, no, no, no.
No, this isn't representative
of us...
Oh, God!
Oh!
Oh, I'm gonna stop!
I'm gonna stop!
No, I quit, too. I quit.
I can't do it.
- I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it!
- Oh, God!
- It's just the bone.
- Charlie!
Oh, Jesus Christ, dude! Oh!
Oh! I think
you shit your pants, too.
Well, it was probably just the
laxative kicking in. It wasn't
a goddamn laxative, Charlie!
You just pooped your pants!
You guys quit! You quit
and we won the game!
Finally.
Finally, I won the game.
This is not what I signed up
for, you donkey-brained maniac!
Uncuff me!
Cool it, cool it.
Take it easy. I mean,
it's just a... it's just
a simple mind game.
No one had a key on 'em.
You know, I knew
they'd cave like bitches.
Hold on a second.
Wait a second.
Andy, did you just call him
"donkey-brained"?
Yeah. What? It's an expression.
What did you mean by
"not what I signed up for"?
Do you two know each other?
No!
No...
No. No.
No.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait-- look at this, guys.
"Mattel" is spelled wrong on his
business card. That says "Matel."
I'm calling this number.
Welcome
to the home of Wolf Cola...
Oh, okay, Frank, so you clearly
just hired this guy
so that you could win
and put your stamp on the game!
No, there's no truth
in that at all. No.
Tell 'em, Andy.
What?!
It was all bullshit?
It was just a hoax?
- Yeah.
- Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait...
Unreal.
So, then, if this isn't about
selling the game anymore...
Well, then it's about winning.
Okay, here we go.
Public humiliation.
Are you ready, Charles?
Yes... Okay,
I'm-I'm in a sort of...
Dude, are you-you
sure you're okay?
You might've lost a lot of blood from
digging around in there with the tweezers.
You know. He's around it. Yep.
Here we go. Okay, then here we go.
You have to withstand
one full minute
of intense berating.
Okay, that's, uh, lights on.
He's ready. "Lights on," he said.
"Lights on." Okay.
But it's not gonna be from us.
Nope. Not from us.
It's from her!
Ow! Ow! You're holding my hair!
Okay, hold on a second.
Ow, let go! Oh, my God, that hurt so much!
Goddamn it.
Okay, well, you know what, it
was supposed to be a big reveal.
I had a whole thing planned.
What's wrong with you?
You know what, of course you
ruined it-- you are the worst.
Oh, my God, what is that smell?
Is that poop? Did you poop
in your pants, Charlie?
Yeah.
Oh, gross.
That's so disgusting.
This is gonna be so easy.
No, dude, don't
listen to them, okay?
You can do this, Charlie.
If you can not cry
for just one minute,
just one minute,
we win the goddamn game.
Yeah, man.
You can do this.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Okay, yeah.
All right. Okay. Okay.
Here we go.
I can do...
Ready, get set, go.
Charlie Kelly, I have been
waiting for this
for a long time,
you poop-smelling
trash person.
Your face,
it looks like a troll!
You look
like you have troll features!
You stalked me! There's
something wrong with you!
Your brain is broken!
I hate you!
I hope you die! And I hope you go to hell!
Three! Two!
And I hope it burns!
One!
You did it! You did it!
Holy shit!
We won!
Charlie?
Come on, buddy, you can do it.
Come on, wake up,
Charlie, wake up.
I don't know
if he's gonna wake up.
I don't either.
Charlie, come on, buddy.
Charlie, are you okay? Charlie...
Charlie, open your eyes.
Charlie? Oh. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. There he is.
Oh, thank God. Oh, thank God.
We thought we lost you, buddy.
We thought we lost you.
Hey.
Oh, my God. Oh, man. What happened?
God... like, all I remember is,
like, winning the game
and then passing out.
Is that how you remember it?
Yeah. Yeah.
No. No, no, you
cried like a baby.
Yeah, pretty much right when
the waitress started talking,
you cried like a little bitch.
Quite a bit.
Yeah. Yeah. You-you
must have been
hallucinating
from all the blood poisoning.
So... did you guys win?
Yeah. Big-time.
We always do.
So did you crush
our game pieces?
No. Oh, my God, Charlie, no.
Charlie, we weren't even thinking
about the game anymore.
No one was.
We were terrified for you.
With you in that condition?
Really? Oh, thank you.
Oh, thank you so much, guys.
Oh, God.
Are you kidding me?
That's, like, really, the
nicest thing you've ever done.
Uh, Dee, can you...
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Charlie, no,
we wouldn't have done that
with you... with
you in that condition.
Yeah. It-it...
No.
But now that you're
conscious, you know...
Dee, are you, uh,
all set back there?
Yep.
Okay.
Loser. Yeah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah!
Yeah! Yeah!
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com