Holy shit! Holy
shit, that is steep.
Trust me, this is
the best way to learn.
See, this is why I don't like
leaving Philly, man.
This is nuts.
You're gonna be fine, man.
The mountain is a
majestical place
where you push your limits and
you maximize your potential.
No, the mountain is a place
where you party, man,
have fun. That's what it's all about.
Yeah, like those '80s movies.
Yeah, but we're not in a movie. I mean, we're
gonna get hurt. We're not gonna get hurt.
For some reason, the rules are
just different on the mountain.
The rules for what? Everything, dude.
You've seen those '80s movies.
What do I do with my hands? How do I ski?
Well, you're supposed
to have poles. Uh... You know what,
hold on to these guys for balance.
These are glass. Yeah.
And don't break 'em, bitch.
What is this,
a double black diamond?
I wish it was a triple black.
Dudes, let's shred.
♪ I remember ♪
♪ One girl ♪
♪ Saw her again ♪
♪ In a magazine ♪
♪ Front cover ♪
♪ Big star ♪
♪ Showing things ♪
♪ That I'd never seen ♪
♪ Well, maybe... ♪
Whoo, yeah!
Still got it, baby!
Rip city!
Wonder how Charlie's doing.
Oh, here he comes.
Whoa! Whoa!
Uh...
Yeah...!
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Another
beautiful day at Alpine Ridge.
End of the season
is right around the corner,
so get those turns in
while you can,
and don't forget to sign up
for the big race this Sunday,
which will determine
the best skier on the mountain.
That was totally insane.
I mean, I can't believe
you guys can ski like that.
Hmm?
It's just nuts.
I'm not doing it again, man.
What are you talking about?
It's so dangerous.
No. You did a great job, man.
Hey, look, is your body hurt?
No.
You okay?
Yeah. That's 'cause it's
mountain rules, man.
I don't get that, though.
I just feel like I got lucky.
Nah. You just need to learn to use
your edges a little bit more.
Learn to turn...
Right down the mountain!
Après-ski!
Let's get our drink on!
No, I don't think I'm
gonna be doing that.
I'm gonna get a sensible meal,
head back to my room,
log in my times,
chart my progress,
'cause I'm gonna win.
Win what?
- At skiing.
- Oh, hey.
What's shakin', brother?
Oh, what's shakin'?
Well, I'll tell you
what's shakin'--
these skis, quite literally.
Now, I need these things waxed
and sharpened by 8:00 a.m.
I want to make first tracks.
No problemo.
Anything else?
You guys need helmets?
Uh, I'll take a helmet.
While you're back there,
could you slap a sticker on the
side of mine that says "pussy"?
Yeah, I feel you, babe,
but those are the rules.
Whatever, dude. Probably
what makes skiing so fun
is that your brains could
get bashed in, in any moment.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah,
it didn't used
to always be this way.
This used to be Party Mountain.
Hot babes, cold brews.
And now I hear some
corporate stooge wants to turn
this place into a private resort
for rich CEOs. They can't
do that to Party Mountain.
It's not called Party Mountain.
It's called Alpine Ridge.
There's one of those
yuppie vultures now.
Don't worry.
We got this covered.
Show this fat-cat asshole
what's what!
Eat this, bitch!
Oh, shit.
- What'd you do that for?
- Oh, sorry, Frank.
We thought you were
some jerk-off
who bought the mountain.
I am the jerk-off
What?!
I'm turning it
into a members-only resort
for millionaires to plow
their trophy whores in private.
Whoa! That sounds
amazing, Frank.
I'm in. I'm in.
What are you talking about?
And ruin Party Mountain?
You know, who cares
about your stupid plans?
Let's go rage, Dee.
Hang on a second.
I-I'm, like, so lost.
So, uh, who do I go with
in this situation?
Well, that depends, Charlie.
You could go drink cheap beer
amongst swine and savages,
like you would on any other day,
or... you could get the most
out of this mountain.
And you could get
the most out of yourself
by joining an elite class
of athletes and gentlemen alike.
Right, Frank?
Yes.
Huh. That sounds kind of cool.
Yeah. All right, you guys go--
why should I go with you?
Go with them.
Who cares?
We're here for two days.
You guys it is!
All right.
Hey-yo!
Hey, man.
Remember us from the ski shop?
Ah, the party guys!
Hey!
Yeah!
Come on in.
Awesome. Awesome.
Well...
looks like you guys had
a real shit-kicker
last night, huh?
Rager!
Oh, oh, the cans.
No, no, we're just recycling
to help pay the rent.
Oh.
Mm.
That's my roommate, Turkey.
We call him Turkey, 'cause his
favorite drink is Wild Turkey.
Awesome! Yes!
Oh, badass!
Like your suit, too.
What are you, coming
from a Gatsby party?
No, I was in court all day.
I was trying to win back
custody of my daughter.
Oh.
Mm.
That's a bit of a downer.
Yeah.
Yeah, pretty much.
Hey. Hey, Roach. Roach,
come meet some people.
Who stole my goddamn burrito?
No, it's there, Roach.
I just moved it to make room
for my coleslaw. Look.
Did you mess with it?
Did you come in it?
Did you come in my burrito?!
I didn't come in your burrito!
I wouldn't do that to you!
He's a little squirrelly
from the concussions.
Like I said,
no helmets back in the day.
Guys, I got to admit,
this is, uh...
it's not as much of a party vibe
as it is a, uh...
A pathetic vibe.
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean,
come on, this used to be
Party Mountain,
you know, and...
and Babe Manor,
that's the capital
of Party Mountain.
Yeah. When was the last time
you even had a babe in here?
Oh, uh... my daughter stopped by
about six weeks ago.
Served me a court summons.
I say count it.
No, don't. Don't count it.
Oh, guys, guys,
guys, guys, don't you
miss the old days,
when you were
the kings of this mountain?
You used to rip sweet powder,
then come home and crush brews.
I do.
Let's take back this mountain!
Why don't you guys dig deep
and show me those
inner party animals.
Let's crush some brews!
Let's empty some cans!
Yeah! Whoo!
Yeah!
Hey, hey, hey!
Rent money!
No, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
Whoa, no, no.
Drink 'em.
Oh, yeah,
it's been so long, I forgot.
Let's drink 'em,
Whoo!
then recycle!
Yeah!
Sure. Yeah.
Okay.
2,000 acres of private powder,
high-speed lifts,
five-star lodging,
and a state-of-the-art spa.
Snow Palace.
Well, Frank,
it's... marvelous.
Thank you. There's only
one thing missing.
What's that?
- The Dennis Reynolds Ski Academy.
- Could be a...
a good idea
to get a model of that.
What are you doing?
Hmm?
What are you doing,
eating a tree?
Yeah, I thought
this was made out of candy.
It's a plastic tree, Charlie.
It's not made out of candy.
You said
that this was a candy model.
I never said it was a candy model.
I believe I heard
you mention it was a
model made out of candy.
Well, let's just
focus on the banquet
that I'm having tomorrow night
to entice local investors.
It'd be a good idea
to get a model of the banquet.
We could make that candy.
I'd like to get a
visual on that banquet.
And we may as well make it candy.
It should be candy.
All right, look, forget about the model,
all right? Let's not talk about the model.
The only model
that you should know is Tatiana.
Tatiana, come in here.
Meet Tatiana.
She came all the way
from Bulgaria
to hand-deliver her finest
caviar.
Nicely done, Frank.
She'll be a fitting reward
for me after I win the big race.
Until then,
Tatiana,
I want you to clean yourself,
for I will enter you hard
and deep,
and it will last for as long
or as short as I please.
But you will be clean.
Only when you are clean
will you know my power.
What the hell is that?
It sounds like a party.
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug!
Yeah! Yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
This is so great. I can't thank
you enough. I feel alive again.
And look at all the cans. We're
gonna be rich! You got to drop it
with the cans, all right? Nobody
cares about the cans. Really. Yep.
Oh, okay, well, what about...
these cans?
Oh! Oh, my God!
You can't do that!
You can't do that.
Though they don't seem to mind. They
look like they're really enjoying it.
Yeah, mountain rules, baby!
Everybody get your tits out!
Hell yes!
He just said, "Take
your tits out," Yeah.
and they all just took their tits out.
Yeah, I'm gonna keep mine in,
just for now.
Party's over, burnout.
Whoops.
Frank Reynolds.
Wow.
It's been...
30 years to the day.
How they hanging, Drisko?
Uh, I lost one of 'em.
Prostate thing. You know.
Yeah, yeah, me, too. It's
still bouncing around in there,
but it don't do nothing.
I'm gonna stop this.
You guys know each other?
We skied together.
This mountain wasn't big enough
for both of us.
Loser of the big race
was banned for 30 years.
Looks like old Frank here
let his mouth write a check
his ass couldn't cash.
Huh.
Well, I just wrote
another check.
To buy the mountain.
How 'bout we race
for the mountain?
Or are you scared you'll lose?
I don't race no more.
I let my son race for me.
Oh...!
Really?
Your son, huh?
Don't think you can beat me?
Oh, I'll beat you.
You better go enjoy your party
while it lasts.
It's gonna be your last one.
Burnout.
Last day
to squeeze in some turns
before tomorrow's big race.
On a side note,
it's good to see Frank Reynolds
back on the hill.
We'll see if he can patch things
up with old rival, Dave Drisko.
But I wouldn't count on it.
Yo, hey, Dennis, did you just hear that?
What?
The-the P.A. announcement.
What-what was that?
Well, there's a lot of people
on this mountain, Charlie.
Everybody's gotta stay informed.
Yeah, but that guy was, like, saying
a bunch of, like, really
personal information about us.
Like, how does he know that?
Right. That's how it works.
Why's he talking about us? There's,
like, hundreds of people out here.
Well, we're the most important
thing that's happening right now.
What? Look, I-I think
I got something
that's gonna clear this all up
for you. Meet my race team.
Where'd these guys come from?
Switzerland?
Yeah, but they came here and
they're racing with us?
I don't... I-I don't
understand that at all.
Well, I needed somebody
to be behind me.
I mean, this guy's my...
kind of my captain,
and these guys are my goons,
you know? If I need 'em
to do something for me,
back me up, you know,
if I'm getting into some...
And... they just
showed up and they're
racing with you?
Yeah.
All right. No
more questions.
- Okay, good. All right. Uh, yeah, I-I...
- Okay.
All right, now, listen up, guys.
Tomorrow's the big race.
And anything less than first
place will not be tolerated.
In fact, it'll be punished.
But, remember,
I want you to have fun.
But not if it means you're not
gonna get first place.
'Cause
I'll-I'll punish you.
All right, now go limber up, and
I'll-I'll meet you at the chair.
Let's go, guys.
March, march, march.
Wow. Uh,
I got to hand it to you,
looks like you got
a pretty good team.
I think so, too. Yeah, yeah. Uh,
look, I don't... I don't get
anything that's happening.
So, uh, I'm out,
you know what I mean? And maybe
we should drink some beer,
eat some snow, and just...
What the hell, man?
I'm disappointed in you.
I thought you were a champion.
Why? You showed me some
real stuff out there, guy.
I was falling. You were
falling, but you were fast.
But I crashed into some tables.
Crashing and exploding is all
part of the learning curve.
I could turn you
into a champion,
but that's clearly
not what you want.
You want to just be a burnout and
a loser like those other guys.
Dude, I don't even
understand you, man.
Just, like, take it easy...
Where are those coming from?
I'm out, dude.
Like, it's crazy to me.
I'm gonna hang out
with Mac and Dee
and see if I can
figure them out, man...
Oh, yeah, yeah. Go hang with
those other two burnout losers.
Yeah, go ahead. You know
what your problem is, buddy?
You got no allegiance.
We're here for two days!
Look like Charlie
Kelly's walking off the mountain
and out of the big race,
ladies and gentlemen.
He knows my name!
Oh, yeah. Here we go.
Take a look.
Oh, wow!
Can you see through the wall? Yeah.
Yeah, you can see right through.
Okay, I think I'm getting it.
Yeah. Yeah? Okay.
- Hey! I heard your guys' voices. What are
you guys doing in here? - Hey!
We are in the middle of a prank
war with Frank and Dennis. Yeah.
All right, nice. What's
the prank? What's the prank?
We're drilling a hole
in the women's shower
so we can look at 'em naked.
Yeah.
Why? What-what does that
have to do with Frank and Dennis?
I don't know. I don't know.
Well, nothing, really.
It's just a warm-up prank to
get the juices flowing. Yeah!
Warm-up. We're warming up.
I don't want to be a bummer,
but I kind of
don't get how spying
on naked, unaware women
- is a prank at all.
- Me, either.
Me, either. Me, either.
Well, the real prank
Mm-hmm. is when I jam
my dick through that hole
and yell, "Special
delivery!"
- Oh, dude, I don't think so.
- Oh, no.
You can't do that, man. You'd get in a
lot of trouble for something like that.
That's, like... Yeah.
Maybe we can just
do something that doesn't
involve naked women.
Just... You know, 'cause
that's not fun for me.
How 'bout if I show you my dick?
Why would I want that?
Oh, okay, okay, it's a prank
if you don't want to see it
but he shows you anyway.
This guy gets it. It's gonna be hilarious.
I think I get it.
I'm gonna get myself hard,
and I will show you what I mean.
Hold on a sec. Oh. Oh.
Oh, you bastard! You know what,
if you guys are already hard,
just go ahead of me and
I'll-I'll just circle back.
Oh, God.
♪ Jessie is a friend ♪
♪ Yeah, I know he's been
a good friend of mine ♪
♪ But lately
something's changed ♪
♪ It ain't hard to define ♪
♪ Jessie's got himself a girl ♪
Shit.
♪ And I want to make her mine ♪
♪ And she's watching him
with those eyes ♪
♪ And she's loving him
with that body ♪
♪ I just know it ♪
♪ Yeah, and he's
holding her... ♪
Hello, Charlie.
Oh, my God. Uh, I'm so sorry,
I didn't mean to spy.
I was just walking by;
I'm not a Peeping Tom.
Oh, Charlie, I do not mind.
We are on the mountain.
Yeah.
What does that mean?
Everyone keeps saying,
"We're on the mountain,"
but I-I don't get it,
you know what I mean?
Look, where I come
from, you know,
jamming your dick through
a hole in the wall,
that-that's assault,
that's a felony,
and, uh, it's just plain wrong.
Something bothering you,
Charlie?
You do not like my breasts?
Uh, no, no, your breasts...
your breasts are great.
Do you want to jump in with me
in the hot tub now?
Yeah. You know,
um... Yeah. Yeah.
I'm gonna stop complaining
about the mountain.
I'm just gonna, I'm gonna let
the mountain work for me.
Now we're talking.
My! Here we go.
♪ You know, I wish that I had
Jessie's girl ♪
♪ I wish that
I had Jessie's girl ♪
♪ Where can I find
a woman like that? ♪
♪ Like Jessie's girl ♪
♪ I wish that
I had Jessie's girl ♪
♪ Where can I find a woman ♪
♪ Where can I find ♪
♪ A woman like that? ♪
Welcome to the annual big race.
Who will take home
the top prize?
Local free spirit Dave Drisko...
...or fierce new competitor
Dennis Reynolds?
The stakes are high
because the loser today
is walking off the mountain
for 30 years.
Do you realize how important
this race is, Dennis?
Well, yeah, 'cause he just said
how important it is.
I hope you got your bags packed.
I'm gonna get rid of you
once and for all,
Frank Reynolds.
I'm gonna save Party Mountain
and bring back the
glorious good old days.
Freeze! Police!
David Drisko,
you're under arrest.
Oh, shit!
They framed Drisko
so he couldn't do
the big race!
Oh, come on!
This man has committed
a litany of sexual assaults.
His semen was recovered
from crime scenes
all over the mountain.
Let's go, pal.
Lose the hat.
This guy might not be as
cool as we thought he was.
Even his awesome hair
is bullshit.
You forgot one charge.
What's that?
Assaulting an officer!
Never stop partying!
Oh!
That'll do. You know? Let
them keep thumping ass.
He probably deserves it.
Yeah.
Never stop partying.
Never stop partying!
So...
which one of you losers wants
to win a silver medal?
Ugh. Not me--
I got blasted last night.
I'm so sick. I don't
feel good, either.
I'd also like to remove myself
from the sexual predator team.
Well, I guess that does it.
The winner by default
of the annual big race is...
Not so fast!
This is good.
So you gonna race for them?
No, Dennis, I'm gonna
race for everyone.
I want to race for the people.
You see,
last night Tatiana taught me
all about Communism.
Cold, hard winters, gross soups.
She also taught me
a lot about sex.
Sweet sex, amazing sex,
a lot of sex,
Jacuzzi sex, Dennis!
♪ Jessie's girl... ♪
It was amazing.
So I get it now--
I like the mountain.
I understand the rules.
And I'm gonna shred.
Well...
this ought to be rich.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
He's-he's getting destroyed.
Oh!
My ankles are broken!
My ankles are broken for sure!
His ankles are broken!
He has broken his ankles!
Oh, they're surely broken!
Charlie can still win!
Go, Charlie!
Come on, Charlie!
Little faster! Come on!
A little faster, bud.
Straighten out!
No! No!
Yeah!
Ah, shit!
Okay.
- I won!
- All right.
The mountain is ours, Frank!
Uh... not exactly.
Uh...
actually, uh...
the whole Snow Palace thing
was, uh, all for show.
Huh?
I needed to distract the local
environmentalist groups
while I fracked the mountain.
Wh-Wh... What?!
You fracked the mountain?
Yeah. Yeah,
the banquet, the race--
it was all set up.
It was just a diversion,
it was...
a distraction, because
I wanted to get into this hill
and suck out
its natural resources.
So all this here was
just one big setup?
Yeah.
I hired the hookers,
so you could rip their tops off.
That makes sense.
Oh... That makes a lot of sense.
So what do we do now?
I'm good. You want to...
you want to stick
around, it's okay. No.
It'd be good to go back to
Philly, right? I mean...
I'm pretty tired.
It was quite a weekend.
Honestly, I don't even
like skiing that much.
I-I need to go see a doctor.
Yeah, I should probably see a
doctor, too, actually, I guess,
if Tatiana was a hooker.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, God, gross. Yeah.
That's not good.
Well, folks, you heard it.
Frank fracked the mountain,
and it looks like
- we'll all be out of jobs.
- Oh... God!
So, did you even hire that guy?
You know, Charlie, I have
no idea who that guy is.
Huh. I guess some things really
are different on the mountain.
Yeah.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
♪ Uh-huh ♪
♪ Whoo! ♪