Hey, Dee! Dee! Dee! Dee!
Do you want to take your feet
off my bed, please?
It's not your bed, okay?
It's my goddamn floor!
And how many times do
I have to ask you guys
to please just pick up your shit
when you wake up in the morning!
You're turning this place
into the Superdome.
Superdome? That's, like,
six years too late.
That's a super lame reference.
And it's kind of offensive.
You'll be happy to know,
by the way,
we are looking
for a place right now.
All right? What about
this place, man?
Ah, it looks a little bit junky.
It kind of reminds me of here.
Yeah, this place
is a piece of shit.
It's not junky, okay?
You guys have destroyed
everything, and that's
why it looks junkier,
like a couple of locusts.
Oh, I take that as a compliment.
It's not a compliment.
Well, it's biblical,
so it's a compliment.
Yeah.
Why is everything
so goddamn expensive?
I mean,
I wish we hadn't burned down
our rent-controlled apartment.
Yeah, you think?
Dee, I will slap you
in the teeth.
You think this is easy?
We-we have a list
of demands here.
We need two bedrooms.
We-we need two bathrooms,
minimum.
You know what? Whatever.
What's your plan?
Where are you guys gonna
find a place that fits
all of your needs for
under 1,500 bucks a month?
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Well, guys,
this is it.
Welcome to our
beautiful new home.
This is crazy.
You guys should've just
moved into that empty apartment
in our building.
The one where the family
was murdered?
Brutally murdered.
Pass.
This place is awesome.
You guys are gonna thrive out
here, and I am not gonna have
to worry about you
hogging my shower anymore.
And we don't have to worry
about getting ringworm.
You brought the ringworm.
Yeah, and now your apartment
is infested with it.
Yeah.
Don't worry, you'll
be back to giving
each other worms soon enough.
These are city scum.
They can't hack it out here.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
You want to bet?
Absolutely.
Okay, Frank.
So if Mac and I
can live here for a month,
then you have to pay
our rent for an entire year.
Deal. And if you don't,
you have to sleep in bed
with an old man for a year.
Gross!
What?
Yeah.
What are you laughing
about, Charlie?
You already sleep
with an old man,
and for no reason other than
you seem to enjoy it.
Yeah.
Okay, you know what, Frank?
You got a bet.
Won't last a month--
Frank is insane!
This place is paradise, man.
We can really
stretch out, you know?
It-it's quiet,
it's calm.
It's not like the city
where everything is so
stressful, you know?
I'm-I'm just...
I feel at ease.
When was the last time
that we had a home-cooked meal?
Oh, dude...
it's been forever.
Well, my friend, dig in.
Mmm.
Oh, my God.
Mac...
this is incredible.
You like it?
Oh, my God.
Oh, that is such a relief
because I worked so hard on it.
Yeah.
I call it Mac's
famous mac and cheese.
Okay, well, I don't know how...
I don't really know
how famous it is.
I mean, I'm your roommate,
and I've never heard of it.
So, what do you want
to do after dinner?
Uh... well, see, the
TV's not hooked up,
so can't watch TV.
Um, there's not really any
bars around here, so...
Right.
You know what we should do?
Hmm?
Let's just get a
good night's sleep.
That's a good idea.
Yeah.
What was that?
What was what?
You hear that,
that chirping sound?
I did not, no.
Probably a smoke detector
or something like that, huh?
Right, yeah.
No big deal.
Hey, to a great night's sleep.
Good morning.
Mm.
Hey, man, did you hear that...?
The pool filter?
Oh, my God.
It was like a jet engine.
I didn't get any sleep
at all last night, you know?
One noise is so much louder
than all the city noises
combined, you know?
You just, you fixate.
Totally.
I get that, but I-I
was actually talking
about that chirping sound--
did you hear that?
It was, like,
happening all night.
No, I didn't hear that.
Oh, man, it was driving me nuts.
Yeah.
Anyway, want to roll?
I, uh, got us some music.
I made this Creed mix.
Oh, uh, Creed, huh?
Yeah, it's a long commute, so...
Yeah, I was thinking more,
like, Bryan Adams.
Okay.
But it-it is Tuesday.
Yeah...
Which is technically my music day.
Right, it's...
Yeah, and that was cool and all
when it only took us,
like, ten minutes to get to
work, but now we're looking
at, like, an hour or so commute.
I'm thinking
maybe more my thing.
But hey, you know what?
Here's an idea.
Why don't you take
a personal day?
You know, I mean, we got
a lot of property here.
It might be nice to have
someone here to look after it.
Yeah.
You know, maybe get that TV working.
Maybe take a run at that,
uh, pool filter?
- Oh. Huh?
- Hey!
You must be the new neighbors.
Name's Wally Schmidt.
No relation to Mike.
But don't tell my wife.
Boy, it sure is a
hot one today, huh?
Okay.
Nice to meet you boys.
What the hell was
that all about?
He just comes up
and starts talking to us?
Right, some guy comes up to me,
I don't know what he's...
I don't know what he's up to.
No. It's like the whole time,
I'm staring at him, I'm
thinking, does he have a knife?
Are we gonna have to take
this bitch out right now?
No. I don't know.
I don't know.
But it's-it's the city, though.
It-it's forced me to develop
these sharp edges.
For protection, you know?
I got to smooth them out.
We're in the suburbs.
Let's work on it a little bit.
Okay, all right.
Shall we? You know, 'cause now I'm all tense.
I don't want to bring
this energy into work, you know?
Luckily, I got
the commute to relax.
♪ Bought it at the five and dime... ♪
Aw, merge, merge!
You had your...
Come on, you got, you have to
seize the goddamn gap!
People are
so goddamn inefficient!
Oh, goddamn it!
I don't care if you're old!
Seize the gap!
You old fat bitch!
You fat bitch!
- So, how was your day?
- Good.
How was work?
Any-any good stories?
Charlie and Frank are doing
something with Russian hats now.
Really? What?
I don't know.
I couldn't follow any of it.
What did you do today?
Did you, uh, fix
that pool filter?
Uh... I tried.
But it turns out it's
actually really complicated,
and I didn't go to school
for that, you know?
Mostly I just tried to get
the living room set up.
It took a little while
to find a stud.
Yeah, I can, I can see that.
Maybe, uh, take another
personal day tomorrow, huh?
You know, maybe I will take
another run at that pool filter.
Maybe try and do
all the other things
that you tried to
do today, but, uh,
you know... do them.
Shut up, shut up, shut up,
shut up!
Aw, damn it!
What is that?
♪ Played it till
my fingers bled ♪
♪ Was the summer of '69... ♪
What's your plan, huh?
Two miles an hour. There you go.
Oh, gun it.
Use your signal, you cow!
♪ Jimmy quit ♪
Goddamn it.
♪ Jody got married,
I should've known... ♪
Unbelievable.
I don't see what the problem is.
Hey. Hey, hey!
Slow down!
Children play here, you fat cow!
Hey, Wally.
Oh, hey.
Hot one today, huh?
Yeah?!
Oh, that Wally loves to say
"It's a hot one"
when I already know
it's a hot one.
'Cause I'm standing outside
in the hot one.
Thanks a lot, Wally.
You know what?
Tell me about future weather.
Don't tell me
about present weather...
Oh, I didn't realize
we had company.
Hey, Dennis.
This is Jimmy--
he's the pool guy.
I invited him over for dinner.
Mac, can I speak to you
in the foyer for a second?
Oh, uh...
Sure.
Excuse us for a second.
Just be a...
just be a...
just be a quick minute here.
Hey. What?
Come on, man.
You gonna invite some guy
over to my house
that I don't even know.
I just wanted to have, uh,
somebody over for dinner.
So I got to have dinner
with some guy, "Hey, pool guy."
His name is Jimmy!
Jimmy? I don't give
a fuck what you do.
You could ask him about
all sorts of things. I mean...
What do you want me
to ask pool guy?
If he knew shit
that I was interested in,
he wouldn't be
a fucking pool guy.
I said I'm sorry.
Yeah, yeah. No, I'm
just, uh...
I'm just confused,
you know, I...
Here I am thinking that we
got a pool that's outside.
Eh... I didn't realize
that we had an indoor pool.
Can we just forget about it
and eat our dinner?
It's just so funny.
We got enough money
for two pools.
And yet we don't have enough
money for a recipe book,
'cause here we are eating
mac and cheese again.
You don't know how hard it is
to be cooped up in here
all by myself, okay?
At least you get to go to work.
I "get to go to work"?
Yes.
Oh, everybody, hey,
I get to go to work.
I "get" to have a job.
I "get" to have to
make money for us.
Oh, my... You know
what, screw this.
Wh... Oh, oh, yes.
Fine, just walk away
right in the middle...
Dennis.
Goddamn it.
What is that?
Aah.
Son of a bitch.
What...?
The hell you doing?
Oh, do you hear it, too?
I heard you bashing.
Yeah, yeah, that chirping?
I'm pretty sure it's a cricket.
Okay, you know what, I'm
gonna say something here,
and it might not
be popular, but...
I hate this place.
And I got to get
back to the city.
I'm going nuts.
I miss the city, too.
I miss the action.
You know, I thought this
place would soften my edges,
but they're sharper than ever.
Dude, I cannot
be cooped up here.
You know, cooking
and cleaning and fixing.
All right, all right,
calm down, calm down.
I... I think I
have an idea.
L-Let's... let's
invite the gang over.
You know, we'll
clean up the place,
we'll serve 'em a nice dinner,
we'll show 'em how-how
well we're doing,
and I'll feel Frank out
about this bet, you know,
which in retrospect is
completely ridiculous.
How are they gonna
find an old man
that's gonna go along with this?
Right. Exactly.
Mac and Dennis, old man.
Old man, Mac and Dennis.
Ah...
So, uh, what's with the hats?
I... You wouldn't
get it. Uh-uh.
Yeah, you kind of had
to be there, man.
Hey, how about that food, huh?
Mac calls it "Mac's
famous mac and cheese."
And it is famous.
In my stomach.
We're your friends,
and I've never heard of it.
Hey, guys.
We are having so much fun
at this house.
I'll tell you, I can't believe
we ever lived anywhere else.
But I was just curious,
if we were to lose this bet,
what would the logistics be,
like, with the old man thing?
Oh.
Well, I'll tell
you what I'll do.
If you guys are cracking,
you can forfeit now,
I'll buy the three of youse
a California king-size bed
- to sleep in.
- What?!
No, they're not gonna forfeit--
this place is rad.
You want a little side action?
No, no, no, don't muddy
this with side action.
Dee, don't do it.
I'll take some side action.
No...
Tell you what.
How about if they win,
I'll take that California
king bed for myself.
Fine, and if they lose,
the three of you got to
sleep with the old man.
Fine.
Deal.
Goddamn it.
Excuse me.
I have to piss.
Out of my penis.
Right.
Okay, well, clearly Mac wants
to speak to me in secret.
Uh, so excuse me.
Wha...?
Oh, good, you got my signal.
Yeah, got your signal.
Dude, we're not gonna make it,
we're not gonna make it.
Yeah, dude, it's cool, man.
W-We'll figure
it out. It's...
No, no, it's not cool.
There's no way
we're gonna make it.
And also, dude,
what's with the hats?
What is with those hats?!
Dennis, I got to know.
They told me the story,
and it didn't make sense,
and now we can't
get it out of them.
Look, dude, I don't
want to sound racist,
but can we just discuss the fact
that it's an old black man?
Yeah, mmm.
It was supposed to be an old man.
Just an old man.
Now it's a black man.
Dude, that's, like, a whole
other thing. That's two things.
That's two things,
it's two things.
All right,
you know what, let's...
Maybe we just...
we-we just...
we take the California king.
I mean, that's a big bed.
You want to share the bed
with an old black man?
No, of course not, I...
All right, that sounded racist.
I don't want to share
a bed with an old man.
I'm just saying it's a big bed,
and we could probably
work it out.
Okay, so picture
big bed, big bed.
Me on the side,
you know, you right here.
Old man, right here.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Why am I in the middle? Black
man should be in the middle.
Don't call him "black man."
His name's not "black man."
His name's "old man."
Let's stick with "old man."
Okay.
Just sounds better.
All right, so how about this?
You and I on the big bed,
side-by-side, black man, he's...
Now you got me doing it.
Mmm.
Old man is down at the bottom,
sideways, like a dog.
Are you calling
black people dogs?
No, that's not what I...
That's very racist.
What the hell is going...?
Oh, my God.
You guys are cracking, aren't you?
Nah, it's-it's, like... fine. Nah, it's fine.
What?!
- It's soul-crushing, Dee. - Oh, my God,
I can't make this house into a home.
I didn't go to school for that.
He didn't go to school for it.
No.
Well, why did you let me
take the side action?!
I told you not to take the side action!
You bitch. You bitch.
Why didn't you yell it so I could hear it?
I'm tired of yelling.
Damn it. Now we got to figure
out where Dee goes in the bed.
Oh, right, Dee's got to be in the bed.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I'll tell you exactly
where Dee goes, okay?
Dee goes right
in the goddamn middle
of her brand-new
California king-size bed
all by herself.
How are we even having
this conversation?!
All you boys have to do...
Guys, all you got to do
to win is just exist.
Hey, morning, buddy.
You're up early.
Yeah, I'm up early,
and I'm feeling great.
You know, I was thinking
about it, and Dee was right.
All we have to do is exist here
for the next couple weeks,
and we win this bet.
So... check
this out.
I made you that.
"Mac's Honey Do List"?
Yep.
That is a list of chores to
give you a sense of purpose,
so you don't feel so
cooped up and lonely.
How's a list of chores going
to make me feel less lonely?
Well, check out
chore number one.
"Name the dog."
Well, that's so stupid.
I don't have a dog.
You sure about that?
Yeah, positive.
I don't have a dog.
I mean, I had Poppins,
but he's gone.
Are you sure?
I don't have a dog.
What do you mean, am I sure?
Of course I'm sure.
I wouldn't be so sure.
What are you doing?
Why...
What... are you okay?
Look behind you, asshole.
Oh.
You got me a dog?
Yeah.
Oh, my God, he's so cute.
I mean, he's no Poppins, but...
Yeah, he's a lot better
than Poppins, trust me.
Oh, Dennis, Dennis.
I'm gonna name him Dennis.
Huh?
You're Dennis.
He's Dennis Jr.
Weird.
Um, but sure, yeah, that's fine.
Hey, so why don't you go ahead
and cross number one
off the list there?
See how it feels.
Okay, yeah.
Hey, what's a-a couple weeks
between two best friends, right?
It's whatever we make of it.
So why don't we agree right now
to make these next few weeks
the best of our lives?
You with me, buddy?
I'm with you.
I'm gonna raise this guy
like he was our own son.
Okay.
Yeah. Weird.
♪ I remember when ♪
♪ I remember, I remember
when I lost my mind... ♪
No, don't merge, don't merge.
We're all... we'll all wait!
We'll all wait
for you to send your text!
You fat pig!
How you doing, neighbor?
♪ Does that make me crazy? ♪
Shut up!
- ♪ Does that make me crazy?
- I'm not letting you in, pig!
Gonna show up to work,
have everybody be like,
"Why is there blood
all over you?"
'Cause I had to slit
the guy's throat
who causes all the traffic!
Boy, it sure is a hot one, huh?
♪ Who do you,
who do you think you are? ♪
♪ Ha ha ha, bless your soul ♪
♪ You really think ♪
Shut up.
♪ You're in control? ♪
I can't believe it.
♪ Well, I think you're crazy ♪
Goddamn it! Damn it...
I hate the fucking suburbs!
♪ I think you're crazy ♪
♪ I think you're crazy... ♪
Hey, buddy.
Haven't seen you for a bit.
You've probably
been staying inside
to avoid this, uh,
heat wave, huh?
Boy, it's been hot.
It's hot, huh?
Yeah.
It is super hot.
It's getting real hot
around here.
So hot, Wally.
But you don't really know
what hot is, do you?
Hot's a storm.
You ever been in a storm, Wally?
I mean, a real storm?
Not a thunderstorm,
but a storm of fists
raining down on your head.
Blasting you in the face.
Pummeling you in the stomach.
Hitting you in the chest so hard
you think
your heart's gonna stop.
You ever been in a storm
like that, Wally?
Dennis.
You okay, dude?
Yeah.
Who you talking to?
No one.
What's that?
Dog grave.
Oh.
Anything exciting
happen at work today?
Uh-uh.
Well, I called up there.
They... they said
you weren't even there.
Can we not talk about my day?
Sure.
Perhaps we can talk
about my day.
And how was your day?
Not great.
You know, with the dog dying
and all, but...
somehow, old Mac
pulled it together.
He cooked for you,
and he cleaned for you.
In fact, Dennis,
everything I do,
I do for you.
What are you talking about, man?
I'm talking about
everything I do, I do for you!
And everything you do,
you do for yourself!
Sleeping in your car.
Eating at Applebee's.
Were you spying on me?
Oh, don't you turn this
around on me.
All you do is think
about yourself!
You didn't even notice
that I switched up
the mac and cheese.
Is that what this is about?
The goddamn mac and cheese?
Well, yeah, I noticed!
You put meat hunks in it!
Wow! Hunks of meat!
Mmm!
Well, of course Dennis
would like Dennis.
What?
It's Dennis!
What are you talking about?
You're eating the dog!
Oh! Oh!
Oh, God! What is
wrong with you?
I don't know! I guess it was
just a cry for attention.
You didn't even blink twice
when I told you
that the dog was dead.
I can't live with you anymore
in this goddamn place.
I'm out of here.
I'm gonna go stay in a hotel.
Where's my suitcase, Mac?
Wait. Wait, wait.
Wait, wait.
Dennis, Dennis,
Dennis, Dennis, Dennis...
Tell me about Mac's
famous mac and cheese.
Okay, I can explain.
I called it my famous
mac and cheese as-as a joke.
But then it seemed
like you like it.
You like that it was
Mac's famous mac and cheese.
And so I just kept saying it.
You're pathetic.
You're the one
that's sitting at Applebee's
eating pot stickers
all by yourself.
You're the one that's pathetic.
Oh.
Well, that must be nosy Wally.
Coming to see what all
the fighting's about.
Well... why don't we show him
what all the fighting's about?
Why don't we show him right now?
Wait, wait, wait!
Dennis, Dennis, calm down.
Don't you tell me to calm down.
There's that chirping again.
How are you not hearing that?
News flash, asshole!
I've been hearing it
the entire goddamn time!
Then why wouldn't
you say something?!
Because I hate you!
Oh, my God.
You did it!
Look at this!
Huh? We did what?
You got this, man.
Hey, in less than a minute,
Almost there.
you guys will have
been here a month.
Yep.
We almost...
we almost won the bet?
Yeah.
We almost did it!
W-W-We almost won the bet?
We're gonna do it!
We're gonna win the bet!
Yeah!
Here it is, paid in full:
one year's rent.
Free rent for a year!
We did it! We did it!
Free rent for...
Wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Free rent for where?
For right here.
Here we go.
In five, four,
three, two, one.
Hey, guys.
Is he dead?
Yeah, I think so.
Quiet your ass down.
Sorry, black man.
Old man.
Sorry, old black man.
God damn it.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com