Oh, where am I? Oh.
Oh.
Where am I?
Oy, I made it home.
Oh, God.
Oh. Oh.
Ah.
I don't know.
Where am I supposed to be?
Oh, shit, look.
Fuck. Okay.
Get up.
Oh, I drank too much.
Ooh, got to piss.
Got to piss. Got to pee.
Where's the toilet?
Ah, there it is.
Oh!
Ah, Frank.
Pull yourself together,
get to the bar.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Eh, eh. Eh.
Mm, mm. Mm.
Still got it.
All righty, here we go. See what
we're getting into today.
It's only a backup.
You're gonna be fine.
If everybody sticks to the tasks
that I've carefully tailored
for each of you,
then you're gonna be great.
- Everything's gonna work out.
-  Oh, shit!
Frank, do you know
what's happening?
Mm, play it cool, play it cool.
Ah, Dennis, I know
what's happening.
- Ah!
- My God. -So what?
Well, if we were just asking if
everybody knows what's going on,
I just want to say that I do.
I wasn't asking.
We're not. He didn't.
That's not what's going on.
He didn't ask that.
That's not the thing.
I wasn't. All
right, you know what?
Let's just... let's go
over the blueprint, okay?
Yeah, the blueprint. I want everybody to
map out their positions. Specifically...
All right, here's
your chance to catch up.
Look at the blueprint.
Listen to the vain one.
He knows the deal.
What's his name again?
Is it Damon? No. Delroy.
No. DeMarcus. Why can't I think
of his name today?
Shoot! I think he just
explained the plan!
So I think we're good.
Yeah. Frank, you ready to run us
all through it again?
Shit. Deflect! Deflect!
Shut up, bird!
Don't ask him
to run us back through it.
He knows the plan.
All right, good.
So we're good.
Let's-let's do it.
Yeah. Frank.
Let's do it.
Nice save, Frankie.
Like, your timing is...
You're so funny every time.
Frank, what? Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Where you going, man?
You got to stay back here on the
walkie in case of an emergency.
Right, yeah, emergency.
Right, okay, and you
have your walkie, right?
No.
Yes. Great.
All right.
All right, let's do it.
We'll be in touch.
Ah, shit!
Got to get home.
Got to get that walkie.
Starving.
Oh, what's that?
Pondy. Aha!
"Let's party."
Ha! Sorry, Pondy. Can't.
Old tits. He's saying I'm old.
Goddamn it, Pondy's the coolest.
L... O... M?
Yeah, "M." Stupid phone!
L... O... L.
Ah, shit! Probably Asians.
Oh, walkie, walkie, walkie,
walkie. Where?
Where the hell
did I put that thing?
Where the hell is it? Ah, shit.
I'll get... There it is.
Okay, got it. I'm here.
Keep the line clear, you idiot. Over.
Roger that.
Stop talking! Over.
Well, well, well.
Goddamn it!
I hate this slimy bastard.
Where's the rent, Frank?
In my pocket where it's gonna
stay until you fix the plumbing.
You're playing games
with me, Frank.
I don't like games.
You know what I like?
This sandwich.
It's snake meat.
Snake meat?
Huh. Is that what
you people eat?
Yeah, snake meat.
I hope you choke on that,
and you die, you piece of shit.
You slime ball bastard!
Oh. Oh, shit!
He is choking.
You son of a bitch!
Frank?
You're dying, you bastard.
Look at me.
You're dying.
Give me that goddamn thing!
Snake meat, huh? Hmm.
Mmm, mmm. Mmm!
Oh, went down the wrong pipe.
Now I'm choking.
Light's going out.
I don't want to die looking
at you, you sack of shit!
Yet! Ooh, shit.
I'm checking out.
Somebody
throw me in the trash.
Where am I?
Where am I?! Oh!
Am I dead? Huh?
Am I in hell?!
No.
I died and went to heaven.
Oh, come to Papa.
Let me have 'em.
Rest up now.
You're in the hospital.
Everything's okay.
Mr. Reynolds,
you're a very lucky man.
If it weren't
for that choking fit,
we would have never been able
to run tests, and...
We found something.
You have a very serious disease,
but fortunately,
we caught it just in time...
There's a malignant tumor
on your front lobe...
Oh, look at those Winnebagos.
Shaboya roll call!
I would like to take a ride
down the Grand Canyon
in those honeys.
Which sadly means,
we might have to remove it.
- Huh?
- Frank!
Frank, come in. Over.
Shit, I got to go.
Sir, sir. You shouldn't be
running anywhere.
Your condition may be terminal.
Out of my way!
Wait, please, sir,
whatever you do, don't...
Frank, Frank, come in. Over.
I'm on my way.
Aw, shit. I need a ride.
I'll bet Pondy will pick me up.
Party mobile's here!
Thanks for the ride, Pondy!
Hop in, Frank.
Aw, goddamn it,
Pondy's the coolest.
It's official, Frank.
I divorced that cheatin' bitch.
Yeah.
I mean, I cheated on her, too.
But who's keeping score, right?
Anywho, I got a nest egg to blow
so that whore can't touch it.
Let's rage!
Hey. Here. Take an aspirin.
That ain't aspirin.
It ain't aspirin.
Does Frankenstein want
to come out and play?
I'm sorry, Pondy.
No drugs for me today.
I need to keep my wits about me.
Lame!
- More for me.
- Yo, Frank!
We're outside the bakery on 6th
Street. Where the hell are you?
Pondy, I need the car. Solo.
Roger dodger.
I'll just drop myself off
at the roller rink, you know?
Get some strange. Hop in, baby.
Pondy is the coolest.
♪ Rock you like a hurricane... ♪
Oh, look.
Dumb bird got a boot on her car.
You're right! You're right, I'm
wrong, okay?!
Get in the car.
God. Where the hell have you been?
Don't blame him.
He's not the one
who got a goddamn boot
on his car.
Whose car is this, anyway?
Ponderosa's.
Pondero... Aw, we're all over the place, man!
What?
What are we doing in this car? No, no, no,
no, no. We're good, we're good, okay?
Except why aren't
we moving yet, Frank?
All right.
Okay. All right. We're good.
Let's huddle up, you guys.
Let's review the plan.
Okay, listen.
Pay attention.
So, Frank,
you're on guard dog duty.
Dee, Charlie, and I are
gonna distract the guard.
Mac is tossing the rug over
the barbed wire and sneaking in.
Yeah?
I'm still lost.
Uh, one problem.
We're gonna need
- a new rug because I threw it clean over.
- What?
- Oh. Goddamn it!
- Oh, Jesus, dude!
How'd this happen? All you had
to do was drape it on the barbed wire
and-and climb over the fence.
I'm too strong.
I'm sorry, Dennis.
"Too strong." Okay, well, you know what,
don't apologize to me.
Apologize to everybody else
that you let down. All right, we
don't have time for apologies.
What's Plan B here?
Does anyone know?
There is no goddamn
Plan B. I don't know.
All right, Mac, you got to find
some other way over that fence.
We'll go... we'll go distract the guard.
I-I... Yeah, yeah. Let's get
a look at the schedule, maybe? Just
got to figure out Let's go. Come on.
what's going on. Yeah, yeah,
yeah, that's a good idea.
Hey, Frank?
Do you think
that Dennis hates me?
What? I just want him to think
that I'm cool, you know?
And I just feel like...
Is this a little bit lame?
I just feel like I can talk
to you about this kind of stuff.
Yeah? Oh, yeah, you
can tell me anything.
Really? Oh, well,
honestly, I just feel like...
Oh, God, this one creeps me out.
I hate being alone with him.
If he touches me, I swear
to God I'm gonna freak out.
...you know what I mean?
Yeah, yeah. Totally, totally.
Yeah, okay. Well, look,
if you could just casually,
off the cuff, mention
that I can bench-press...
What is that, fudge? ...I
think that he'll respect me.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Dude,
what are you doing? Mmm.
Those are dog treats laced
with sleeping pills.
Those are for the guard dog.
Tasty.
I'm gonna keep eating it.
Maybe I could just hop
the fence, you know? I mean...
Oh, shit. Oh, shit. I know
where there's another rug.
I know where I can get a
rug real quick. What?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
No, wait, we'll go...
Are you sure you can drive,
dude?
Out of my way, creep.
Aah!
Franklin, thank you for coming.
Yeah, I got no time for
swapping loads. I'm in a jam.
Whoa, Jews!
What is this?
We're sitting shiva,
for my Aunt Joyce.
Come, meet my family.
That dog stuff is kicking in.
Lisa.
Ooh, hoo. Shabooya roll call.
Aw, shit. There's the rug.
Under the buffet table.
Mom, Dad,
this is my part-time
lover, Frank Reynolds.
I am starting to feel woozy.
Say something smart.
Uh, uh, excuse me,
I'm full of dog poison.
That's not good.
That's not good, Frankie.
What's happening?
Come on. Come on. Frankie.
Hello, Frank.
Artie.
Better go get that rug out
from under that table, Frank.
Got to get the-the rug.
I'm getting a rug.
What? There are drugs
in the medicine cabinet.
There's drugs
in the medicine cabinet!
Uppers, uppers, uppers, uppers.
Jackpot!
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Ooh. Crush it.
Crush it, Frankie.
What are you gonna do?
Oh, slowin' down.
Need uppers.
It's Frankenstein! Ha!
Frank? Are you okay?
Rug, rug, rug, rug.
Get out of the way, Jew. Out of my way.
What's happening?
Back off. Frank!
What's going on?
Rug!
Frank!
Car. Come on. Come on.
Don't get killed,
don't get killed.
Watch the car, watch the car.
Get in the car.
Get out of here!
Heya, kid. Balloon.
Food! Got to get a hot dog.
Hot dog, hot dog, hot dog.
Ow, hot! Hot!
Need booze.
Now flush it out.
Booze, booze, booze!
Got to flush them out.
I'm coming.
Oh, sick. Oh, sick.
Get out of here!
Ah, that's better.
Got to modulate, Frankie.
I'm coming, Pondy.
I'm coming. I'm coming.
Don't worry about it, Pondy!
I'm coming! Where is he?
Pondy? Where is he?!
Where is he?!
Oh. Keep that engine running,
Frankie!
Screwed up, Frank.
What did you do?
I got handsy
with some pretty young thing.
She looked 18 to me.
I don't know.
I'm out of control!
Oh, shit.
Pop the glove compartment,
Frank.
Someone's dying today, baby.
No, Pondy!
Give me that gun! You
got too much to live for!
You're right, Frank.
You're right.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Everything's going to be okay.
Come here!
I'm coming, Pondy!
- Eat shit! Daddy!
- Ah.
Oh, he's getting his ass kicked!
Get out of my face, old man,
before I kick your ass
and throw you in that trunk.
Now think of
something tough to say.
Nice nips, cupcake.
What's happening?
Oh, shit,
that bald bitch knocked me out.
I'm in the trunk, aren't I?
How long have I been in here?
Ah! Still got the gun!
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Oh, shit. Where am I?
Oh, shit.
I'm at an impound.
Pondy's car must have
got towed here.
Oh, my head, is...
Oh. Oh.
Oh, is that the gang?
Why are they dressed like cops?
Hey! What the hell
are you guys doing?
Frank?
Frank!
He's in there.
Frank! What?!
Awesome! He did it!
You did it, man!
Okay, okay, now go get Dennis' car!
Yeah, come on.
That... Get Dennis' car?
Hey, your name is Dennis!
What the hell are
you talking about?
Dude, get my car before
the guard comes back!
Go!
Okay, I'm on it. I'm on it.
On it.
- Goddamn!
- Oh!
Big spill.
Oh, are you okay, man?
Are you all right?
You all right, Frank?!
You all right?
Charlie, you there? Oh, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know. Your glasses are right in
front of you. Just-just... Where?
Hurry! Yeah,
go, go, go, go!
Faster, Frank! Faster!
Where?
They're right there!
Right there!
Aw, shit!
Run, run, run, run,
run, run, run, run!
Run, run, run, run, Frank!
Run, Frank!
Eat glass, you mangy mutt.
Come on, think of
something cool to say.
Anybody need a ride?
Come on!
That's right.
Frankie, number one.
Nice, Frankie!
You came through!
Aw, crap. This one's gonna sit
in the front.
I hope he doesn't try
to touch me.
Don't touch me!
Oh, shit, dude, I'm sorry.
Think of something.
Think of something good.
Dee's a bird!
She is a bird! She is a bird!
That's nice!
It's only a bird.
You getting in
there deep, Frank?
Oh, yeah.
What a day, man.
Oh, what a day.
Yeah, it sure was, Charlie.
I'll tell you, though.
Great work, bud.
You killed it, really.
Ah, thanks, Charlie.
When you got a good plan,
you stick to it.
- Piece of cake.
- Yeah.
All right, well...
I guess we should go to sleep.
We've got a big day tomorrow.
We do?
Yeah! With...
You're just messing with me,
aren't you?
Oh, you know exactly what
we're doing tomorrow, don't you?
Of course I do.
We got the thing
with the thing. Uh, the thing.
We... yeah, we probably
should go to sleep.
Yeah. All right, well.
Hmm.
Could go to sleep, or, uh...
we could play one quick game
of night crawlers.
Oh. Aah!
You down for that?
I knew you would be.
All right, let me get the
blanket, let me get the blanket.
Okay.
Darkness falls.
And magic stirs.
As we become... the creatures
of the night...
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com