Okay, so there we were.
We're in the brig
and the whole ship just,
you know, bumps; we get
thrown against the the wall.
Yeah. You know, the-the
lights are going off.
The sirens are blaring.
Whoa, whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa.
How did we get in the
brig in the first place?
What do you mean, Frank?
You were there.
I'm very cloudy
about the beginning.
I think I need a recap.
Recap?
A recap would be good, you know?
Just to kind of brush up
on everything that happened.
A recap...
Now, see, I forgot that.
...honestly might be good
because, you know,
we want him
to be completely clear
before the final judgment.
All right, you know,
Right, yeah.
the amount of energy
we're using talking
about whether
or not we should recap,
we may as well just recap,
so fine, fine.
So there we were.
We're on a Christian cruise.
Yeah, we're all thrown
in the brig
for various sins
that we committed.
Me, admittedly,
for a little bit of lust.
Um, and in summation,
we're all good people,
asking for forgiveness.
My thing, not a rape.
Move on; you're
losing him.
Move on; you're losing him.
I just want to be clear.
Okay, yeah, yeah.
I just wanted to be clear.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
What the hell is that?
What're those sirens for?
Oh, God.
Oh, my God, see, I knew
I shouldn't have
come on this cruise.
I knew it! I mean, it used to be
I would never even leave Philly!
And then, you know,
you guys drag me to this,
you drag me to that,
and next thing I know,
I-I'm stuck in a box
on a sinking ship!
Hold on, the boat's not sinking.
How do you know that?
How do you know it's not...?
Well... Oh.
There you go. It stopped.
All right, uh,
I guess that's good.
I mean, like...
like, if something went wrong,
they-they'd come down here,
they'd get us, right?
You know what, guys,
what difference does it make?
You know?
Life is just a series of events
with no meaning or plan,
you know?
It's like, we live, we die,
we're gay, we're straight,
we're tops, we're bottoms.
Wait, wait, wait.
Calm down, everybody.
We're gonna be
in the Bahamas in an hour.
Well, you sure? Like, I...
I don't think we're moving.
We're moving. I can hear
the engine buzzing like crazy.
No, I think Charlie's right.
I-I don't think that we're
moving, and-and besides,
the buzzing would be,
like, an electrical system.
You know?
The engine sounds more like...
Yeah, maybe on a speedboat.
This is a big cruise ship.
It's got like a big,
deep sound; it's like a...
Yeah, if you're starting
the engine, but, like,
we would be hearing a steady...
Gah, gah, gah, gah,
gah, gah, gah, gah...
No, no, you
guys are all wrong.
No, boats are mostly
computerized these days,
so the engine barely
makes any noise at all.
I mean, they-they make
a fake noise
to-to make people feel better,
but it's like...
But it's fake, it's not...
it's not real, you know?
It's kind of like how I carry
a little piece of onion
around with me to elicit tears,
you know,
in case someone needs me
to feel something
about what they said or
are doing, you know what I mean?
Do you have an onion in
your pocket right now? No.
No, I'm taking
a vacation from myself.
W-Was it a vacation
from hearing, okay?
'Cause if the engine was going,
we would hear a gah, gah, gah,
gah, gah, gah, gah...
Are you deaf, Charlie?
I was like...
I mean, that's ridiculous! All right, okay,
all right. All right, all right, all right!
Goddamn! Okay, look.
Let's just, let's all agree
that it doesn't sound
like a speedboat,
or something
that's off-roading, all right?
It does make a little
bit of a buzz.
Yeah?
But most modern ships
these days, their engines,
they don't make a lot of noise,
that they do make
a little bit of noise.
Can we all just agree on this?
Yeah.
Fine, I can live with that.
I can live with it.
Fine.
Okay, all right.
How long have we been
talking about this?
Four hours, six minutes.
Well, there's some pros
and some cons, guys.
Pro: We've cut our conflict
resolution time in half.
Four hours, that's good for us.
That's-that's huge,
that's huge.
Con: Charlie's right,
the ship is probably not moving
because we definitely would've
been in the Bahamas by now.
What?
Yep.
Oh.
Well, that's not good, right?
I mean...
No. It's not good.
I mean, f-four hours?
Well...
The-the boat not moving!
No one comes down
to say anything like,
"Hey, guys, there's something
wrong with the ship!"
No, they've forgotten about us!
And we're gonna die in here!
Oh, my God, I'm freaking out.
We got to get out of here.
Help! Help!
Calm down, Charlie.
Help us!
Charlie!
You got to help!
Hey! Hey!
Oi, oi, oi, oi,
oi, oi, oi, oi, oi, oi!
Mm, yep, yep, yep. Mm.
Whoa.
Yeah?
Yep.
Oi, oi, oi.
What-what was that, dude?
You sound like
a soccer hooligan.
Uh, yeah, that's just something
I've been doing
with Charlie lately
when he gets a little wound up.
You know, it seems to work.
- Say yup, yup, yup.
- Oh, that's good.
The most important thing
for us to do now
is to keep our wits together.
We got to occupy ourselves.
Mm-hmm.
Why don't we play a few games?
No, no! I just wanted to
get away from you guys,
just for a few days.
Now we're stuck in a box,
and you're gonna play
some games now?
You know what? I'm out.
What?
What the hell
do you mean you're out?
- I'm out. Nobody talk to me.
- No, Dee.
That's not a very good idea.
You know when my dad was
in solitary confinement,
I used to write to him
every day to see how it was.
He never wrote back, but if
he did, he would've said,
"Son, you've got to keep
your mind active.
Also, I love you."
Uh, are you
sure he wouldn't say,
"Remind me who you are again"?
Ho!
That was great!
That was Luther!
My-my-my dad knows who I am.
Yeah-yeah.
Hey-hey do the voice again,
but this time say,
"I love you, son."
Nah.
Oh.
But, no, that's
a good distraction,
like, um, you know,
like any kind of impressions
you got, like any kind of...
You want to hear me do
a couple of impressions?
That'd be fun. Yeah,
okay, so let's see.
All right, so let me know
which ones you want to hear.
I'm sorry, Dee, I thought
you were sitting out.
Well, I was out, but then
these guys wanted to hear
some impressions, and since I'm
always wanting to be of service,
here I am, uh... They don't
want to hear your impressions.
They want to hear my impressions.
No.
Your impressions are terrible.
Are you out of your mind?
No.
My impressions are fantastic.
Give me somebody.
Anybody.
Do Obama.
Obama?
Well, I can't do that.
- Why not? Yeah.
- Why can't you do Obama?
'Cause he's a black man
and I'm a white woman.
Can you give me a white woman?
You think I can't
do a black woman?
I mean...
No.
I... okay, give me, name one.
C.C.H. Pounder.
Who's that?
C.C.H. Poun...
Yeah. The actress
from The Shield.
Love that show.
Okay, yeah.
No, I can do that.
Yeah.
Let's see.
Goddamn it, Dutch!
What other errands do you
have us running for the D.A.?
- Wow!
- Holy shit!
That was great!
That was spot on!
Thanks, man.
"Spot on"?
You don't even know
who she is, Frank.
I just assumed
she's a no-nonsense
black broad from the precinct.
That's exactly who she is.
Fine, fine, fine.
I'll do Obama, okay?
Okay.
Okay, what do you got?
Hey, yo, what up, son?
What's up wit'
Congress bein' all
up in my ass and shit, brother?
Oh!
- Oh, my God, Dee.
- That is bad!
What are you doing?
That was so racist.
- Are you kidding me?!
- Very racist!
Deandra, he is the President
of the United States.
- That's our president.
- Well, hold on a second.
Why was that racist,
but what he did was fine?
Because that's not what Obama
sounds like, Dee. That's why.
Uh... okay, well, you know,
I-I'm just warming up.
Let me, let me try again.
Um...
Hey, yo,
where my senators at, dawg?
Oh!
Oi, oi, oi, oi!
Oi, oi, oi, oi, oi, oi, oi!
Welcome to my first ever
dinner party.
I'm gonna have lots
of these types of functions
in the future, you know, with
my new lifestyle.
Wow, you're really just diving
right into that, huh?
Just, stereotypes and all.
Guys, we are gonna have
an imaginary meal. Mmm.
I read about this. Yes.
If you truly believe it, then it
will make you full. That's true.
Okay. Can I have a broad
with me with big tits?
No, because that's
gonna force us
to imagine things
that we don't want to imagine.
Ah, good point.
So get rid of my dog?
Yeah, no dogs.
Go! Go!
Hey, get out of here!
So kick it.
Get, get, get!
Kick it in the skull.
We do not allow dogs
in our house, right, Dennis?
Wh...? Our house?
Wh-Why's it our house?
Okay, let's get started.
Let me... let me set
the scene: the food.
The menu. Okay, all right. Ooh,
yeah, start with the food.
Yeah, yeah, let's get to it.
Okay, all right, here we go.
Paint a nice picture for us,
all right? I'm starving.
All right, now
you're gonna start
with, like, a big
hunk of chicken.
You know, like, boiled and
skinless, or-or whatever.
- Huh. Ugh.
- Okay.
And then, um, you're gonna want
brown with the white, right?
So, like, maybe, like, um,
some, like, brown rice.
No... no butter
or-or seasoning or...
Really?
I want mashed potatoes.
No, no mashed potatoes;
that's just empty carbs.
Why can't we just imagine
whatever we want?
Because this is my dinner party.
Well, then take us there!
Yeah!
All right! All right, okay.
Everybody's got
something to drink.
Is it a milkshake?
No!
No, not milkshakes.
Gatorade.
And it's gonna be
my favorite flavor: blue.
"Blue" is not a flavor.
How am I gonna taste blue?
Well, just imagine
what blue tastes like.
It does... It just
tastes like blue.
Let's just dig in.
Yeah, can we eat?
All right.
Yes.
Mine's kind of tough.
D-Did you overcook this?
No, I didn't cook it at all.
Y-You...
Spit it out! It's raw!
You're gonna get sick!
Spit it out, man, spit it out!
No, no, don't spit it out!
What are you guys doing?
You don't need to spit it out.
For the love of God.
Look, just imagine
that it tastes good, okay?
Look at Dennis, see?
Oh, I'm not...
I'm not imagining your meal.
No, I'm imagining
a lovely coq au vin.
Braised with lardons
and mushrooms.
I want that!
Yeah.
Well, then have it--
it's right in front of you.
As is your buxom date, Frank.
Ah, come here, baby.
Oh, hey!
She got her foot
in my raw chicken!
Get your hooker's foot out of my
chicken, man! No, no, no, no.
No dates, no coq au vin,
no hookers.
Stop ruining this!
We're not ruining this.
What the hell is that?!
Oh, this? It's the sound
of my blender
cranking milkshakes.
Anybody want one?
- Shit, I'll take a milkshake. Yeah.
- I'll have a milkshake.
I'll take one. That is not
what blenders sound like, Dee.
No! Don't leave my table! Crash!
Hey!
What are you doing?
I'm flipping the table!
Smash! Crash! Oh!
Now I'm breaking a plate!
Boom! Smash! Oh, man.
What the hell, dude?!
Oh, that was really uncalled for.
That's nice.
Nothing is working, all right?
You know what,
I want you guys to just...
Everybody just be quiet.
Why don't we just try
not talking for a while?
I'm fine with that.
Yeah.
Well, that'll be
the first time ever.
Shh!
Of course.
Yeah.
Okay.
Ha!
Well, that was lame.
So stupid.
So stu...
I hated that show, Stomp.
Ugh, I hate rhythm.
H-H-Hang on. Hang on.
D-Dee, what was that?
Well, I-I thought
we were all doing,
like, a Stomp thing.
That-that bench,
you opened that bench.
What's inside there?
Oh. That opens? Yes.
Maybe there's food in there.
Is there food in there?
Uh, no, just...
Just this water gun.
That's not a water gun,
man, that's a flare gun,
which I'll hold onto
for safekeeping.
Uh...
Why?
Well, because I'm the most
responsible person.
Uh, guys, guys, I-I don't think
any of us should have a gun.
Yeah.
Well, one of us does, so...
the end.
Charlie, Charlie,
let me have the gun.
Back up, Frank.
Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh.
Don't come close to me.
Whoa. Charlie, calm down.
"Calm down, Charlie"?
We're trapped
on a sinking ship, okay?
We're gonna die in here.
I don't know what you guys
are capable of.
I will hold the gun,
thank you very much.
Wait a second, Charlie, the...
the boat's not sinking, okay?
It's-it's just stopped.
Right. Right, it's okay.
Everything's gonna be all right
as long as everybody
remains calm.
What the hell is that?
Oh, my God!
What's going on?
Wh-What was that?
Oh, this is bad.
This is really bad.
Let's think.
If the room's on its side,
does that mean the boat's
on its side? Or...
Yeah, that's what it means!
I don't know how boats
this big work. All right.
Help us!
This is bad!
This is very bad!
All right, we got to get up
there and try that door again.
Maybe that lodged
something loose.
Get up there? How are
we supposed to reach?
Oh! What about
a human pyramid?
Yes. Yes, Mac, a
human pyramid.
All right, you and I
will be the bottoms.
Why? 'Cause I'm gay?
Not because
you're gay, dumb-ass!
Because we're the strongest.
Damn it. All right,
and, Frank, Charlie,
you'll be on us.
And, Dee, you'll be
on the very top.
Okay.
Okay, I'll be a bottom now,
but in real life, just to
be clear, I'm gonna be a top.
Okay, fine, when you're having
gay sex, you can be on the top.
But for now we're on the bottom.
Damn it, the door is locked!
- We're done for! We're gonna die in here!
- Hey, Frank.
Frank, get yourself together!
We're gonna die in here!
Stop losing your shit!
All right, relax!
- Nobody's dying!
- That's right.
Just listen to Charlie;
he seems to have
his head straight.
Calm down.
'Cause we're already dead.
Come again?
I figured it out.
We're dead. We died.
And I don't know
when it happened.
It might have... might have
happened on the cruise ship.
It might have happened on
the drive to the cruise ship.
You were going
awful fast, Dennis.
I don't know.
Maybe it happened
weeks ago in the bar,
in some sort of colossal and
awesome event, I would imagine,
but we're dead,
and we're in hell.
We're just being
toyed with here.
Or-or m-maybe we're not
in hell yet.
You know,
maybe this is purgatory,
and we're on our way
to be judged.
And soon, oh, boy.
Yeah, soon,
we'll really be in hell.
Won't that be something.
Charlie, calm down.
It's-it's gonna be fine, okay?
We can't be freaking out
every five minutes.
Now, look, if we work together,
everything's gonna be fine.
We're gonna get out of here.
Nah, we're already dead.
I'll prove it.
No!
Oh, I think he's coming to.
Oh, shit, that hurt.
Oh, easy.
Well, I guess that means
we're alive, huh?
Yeah, guess we are.
Guess we are, Charlie.
Good, well, then maybe
everything's gonna be okay.
Uh, no, pal, we're
in deep shit here.
Oh, shit! Take it easy.
Okay, take it easy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's not good. It's not good.
- Oh.
- As long as, um,
we're not gonna
get out of here--
and it looks like that's
sort of where this is headed--
is it okay if I just
confess something,
get it off my chest
before we die?
That's a good idea.
We shouldn't die holding
things in about ourselves.
Go ahead, Dee.
Mac owns a Cowboys jersey.
I saw him wearing it
in the back office.
What? Uh... What?!
That's a secret, Dee!
What are you...
Don't say it's Romo.
Of course it's Romo!
Who else would it be?
Oh, my God!
I'm sorry.
You don't think
he deserves to be MVP?!
You son of a bitch.
He's constantly overlooked!
You are a traitor!
How many Super Bowls
have the Birds won?
Oh, shut up!
Go Birds!
Oi, oi, oi!
Okay, you know what?
I've got something
I want to confess.
Charlie changes Frank's
prescription on his glasses
to keep Frank dependent on him.
Whoa! Why the hell
you blowin' up my spot, man?!
Wow.
Uh, I'm sorry, Frank.
All right, fine.
Well, as long as
we're "tattling,"
uh, Dennis ripped
up all the letters
that your dad wrote from prison,
so... you know.
What?
My dad has been writing?
Dennis, is that true?
Yeah, man, but you were
just gonna be, like,
talking about it all the time,
and then your dad was probably
gonna come to our house
and, like, try to kill
us or eat our butts.
You know? I'm trying to
protect you, dude! And me.
Does he still write?
Well, no, pal, 'cause
you never wrote him back.
But, hey, if it makes
you feel any better,
I-I read all
those letters,
and he never once said
that he loved you.
He just mostly wanted
you to send him,
like, pornographic magazines
and put drugs in your butt hole.
I can't believe you're saying...
I could've had
a relationship with my dad.
But you ruined it.
Normally, I would
attack you, but...
I-I don't have any fight left.
Wow.
Well, shit, man. I...
I... I hurt ya.
I can see that.
And, uh...
you know, it was... it was wrong
of me.
Oh, God, I'll tell you...
I see how much pain
you're in right now.
It's just...
...it's tearing me up inside.
Jesus, Dennis, you're crying.
Well, yeah.
I mean, you've turned me
into a blubbering fool here,
because I've hurt...
not just my friend...
...but my brother.
I've hurt my brother.
Onion! I just saw it! Onion!
He's got an onion there!
Aw, I knew it!
He's got an onion!
You are such an asshole.
I...
Now I gotta tell you!
I got a confession.
What is it, Frank?
I was at Chappaquiddick.
The girl, Teddy Kennedy,
the bridge, the car...
I played a major role.
Jesus, Frank,
we're not doing confessions.
We're doing tattling.
Keep up.
You know what?
It's all right, it's okay.
Guys, let's just...
let's stop fighting, okay?
No more confessions,
no more tattling
on each other, all right?
Look, guys,
let's just try to enjoy
these last moments
we've got together.
Okay? Or these last hours.
Or, hell...
it could even be days.
God, we're gonna drown.
I'm too young to drown!
We should die
thinking good thoughts.
Yeah.
For me,
that's Romo connecting
with Dez Bryant.
Oh, stop it!
You traitor!
You son of a bitch!
Shut your mouth!
Guys, guys, guys, don't fight.
Don't fight, come on.
Oh, we're not good people;
we can't even die peacefully.
Yeah.
♪ Amazing grace ♪
♪ How sweet the sauce... ♪
Sauce?
♪ That made... ♪
It's not "sauce."
Look, you gotta
get the words right,
otherwise Jesus is gonna know
we're trying to trick him.
Jesus isn't gonna listen to us.
He's just not,
'cause we're bad people.
But if he's gonna listen to
anybody, he might listen to Mac.
Mac, you've been talking
to him your whole life.
Mac...
He knows you!
He doesn't even know who I am.
Save us! Mac, save us.
Guys, guys...
there is no God.
Oi!
Oi, oi, oi, oi, oi, oi, oi, oi!
Oi, oi, oi, oi, oi, oi!
Okay, okay, okay.
One last shot.
Uh, dear Heavenly Father...
Yeah.
...if you do exist,
and you are listening,
if you could find it
in your heart
to send us a miracle...
Just send us
one miracle, please.
One miracle.
Our goose is cooked!
I'm going down.
Highway to hell, baby!
Sis... I love you.
Whatever.
What?
Whatever?!
Whatever?
Unbelievable!
Ah, whatever.
I can't believe
nobody came to save us.
Should we do this?
Let's go be with the gang.
All right.
♪ ♪
A-And then, uh, you know,
and then we all got pulled up.
I mean, it was a miracle.
It was an actual miracle.
Yeah. Hey, I'm sorry,
can I stop...
Can you just move
that light a little bit?
It's really blasting me right in my face.
Yeah, it's been
blasting us this whole time.
It's kind of blasting all of us.
- Can you move the light, please?
- Just a little bit?
Sorry about that.
Oh, wow!
So much better.
Should've said something
earlier.
Well, harrowing stuff,
but I think I got
everything I need.
Could you mark down
in your report,
uh, that I'm not gay? Because I'm not.
What?
What do you mean, you're not gay?
Since when?
He's gay.
Oh, well, because
God answered my prayers
and saved us.
That means that there is,
of course, a God,
and if there is a God,
then in his infinite wisdom,
there's no way
he would have made me queer.
- Oh.
So I'm-I'm straight.
All righty. Okay. Look, look...
are we gonna get in trouble
because of this accident?
Uh, nope, you're good to go.
I just needed your report
for my insurance claim.
Insurance claim?
Y-You're not a cop?
Cop?
No, I'm an insurance adjustor.
I'm just collecting reports
of people's experiences
for insurance purposes.
Oh.
Whew.
I'm so relieved.
So, so... are we
gonna get a payout?
Well, you might have,
had you not just
admitted to breaking...
several laws.
What? Right, well...
hang on though.
I mean, we got
trapped in a room...
...by a drunk captain
who sunk the ship.
We almost died, man.
Yeah, man. Yeah.
No, no, it wasn't the
captain's fault. He was sober.
Well, what happened?
Whose fault was it?
Nobody's fault. The ship just hit
a massive wave during the storm.
In the insurance biz,
that is what we call
"an act of God."
Well, God is great.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com