Ooh. Man, that was, like,
one Mississippi that time.
Yeah, that storm's, like,
right on top of us, huh?
Yeah. It's kind of cool, though.
I mean, I can't think of a better
way to have a movie night
than in the middle of
an electrical storm.
- It's kind of cozy, right?
- Mm-hmm. Cool, right?
Why do we have to watch The Wiz?
This movie sucks.
Well, it's Old Black Man's
night to pick the movie.
Yeah, but he's asleep.
Yeah, but, like...
why do a remake of The Wizard
of Oz? I mean, the original
was a classic. Uh, don't you
think it's fair, though,
that they get their version? You know,
I mean, it's very difficult
being a black person
in America, you know?
So what? Doesn't mean I
want to watch Orlando Bloom
in Boyz n the Hood.
Yeah, I don't want to see that.
Oh, yeah, if you flip it it's weird,
man, yeah. I would see that.
I would see that. I would see that.
I mean, look, this may be
a little bit touchy for me to say,
but, uh, you know, black people...
They have a lot more
opportunities these days.
Well, we did have a black president
before the orange one.
Yeah, but that doesn't mean
there's not problems.
I mean, what about the whole,
like, Black Lives Matter thing?
Uh, well, sure, no, good point.
But, I mean, I don't know why
it took 'em so long to realize
that their lives matter.
I mean, they-they've always mattered,
you know? But I would also say
that all lives matter, you know?
And while black people
may not feel like it,
it's kind of tough out there
right now for everybody.
I mean, really, our lives
aren't all that different.
Whoa. Oh...
What the hell happened?
Did we get struck by lightning?
Uh, I think it came through
the electric blankets.
Yeah, we got electrocuted. Holy shit.
Look at this... the VCR's toast.
Uh, wait a sec...
Where's Old Black Man?
Oh, my God. He's gone.
What the hell? What?
Uh...
guys?
You're gonna want to see this.
What?
Well, that's interesting.
...Synced and corrected by DaddyBear...
...www.addic7ed.com...
What the hell is happening?
Why are we black people?
But only in our reflections.
This is insane.
Are we in a dream? Do
we got, we got to, like,
pinch ourselves or something?
Why is it daylight outside?
How is this happening?
Forget how. We're past that.
It is happening. It just is.
♪ Give me one good reason ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
- What are you doing?
- ♪ Give me one good reason ♪
♪ Why we're this way ♪
- Why are you doing this?
- ♪ I don't have a reason ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ I don't have a reason for a thing ♪
♪ That's happened today ♪
♪ I wonder why we're singing ♪
♪ Every word that we say ♪
♪ I wonder if we're living out
The Wiz in some way ♪
Uh, oh, well, no, it's not
The Wiz, because nobody
switches bodies in The Wiz.
Got to be something else.
I mean, I think we're
experiencing something
a little more like...
♪ The Hot Chick, The Change-Up ♪
Here I go.
♪ Vice Versa, All of Me ♪
♪ Like Father, Like Son ♪
♪ Dating the Enemy ♪
♪ A Boy Thing, A Girl Thing ♪
♪ 13 on 30 ♪
♪ Detention ♪ - ♪ Face/Off ♪
Uh... Right. Oh, actually,
no, Face/Off wouldn't work,
- because that's a face-switching movie.
- Yeah, no,
guys, I think we found ourselves
in a Quantum Leap.
Hmm? What the hell's a Quantum Leap?
Oh, a great show from
the coke-fueled era
of '80s television where Scott Bakula
would leap into other people's bodies,
but he didn't know it unless
he saw his reflection.
♪ These are not good reasons ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Now I'm just confused
and I don't know ♪
♪ What the hell to say. ♪
- Wow.
- Shit.
- Yeah, I don't know what that was.
- That was super weird.
Okay, guys, I think I know
what's happening here.
I think we're in the
respite of a musical,
where people can get out
the necessary information
that doesn't fit into rhyme form.
Clearly, yeah, that's
what's happening.
That's what's happening,
right? So let's talk fast be-before
- another song starts.
- Okay, so... Okay, that's a good idea.
You know what the problem
is? We don't know the rules.
And there's no way we're
gonna figure this out
until we figure out what the rules are.
♪ What are the rules? ♪
Oh, Christ, I'm singing again.
♪ When you've just turned black ♪
♪ And you can't switch back ♪
♪ Well, you got to go ♪
♪ And find out the rules. ♪
Wh... Oh.
- Oh. Oh, my.
- Yeah, yeah. Wow.
Holy shit, what have I
done? Um, okay, look,
this is gonna keep
happening, I think. Oh, God.
All right, so let's-let's
figure this out, soon.
Let's split up, okay? Y-You two,
- uh, go and try and find Old Black Man.
- Mm...
- I'm sorry... Old Man. Just Old Man.
- Yeah. Yeah.
And, um, help him out, you know?
Do-do the Quantum Leap thing.
See that thing through, in case
it's that. And the three of us,
we'll go out and, um, we'll try
to do the Freaky Friday thing...
Try to figure out whose
bodies we switched with.
But are they gonna look like us, though?
I don't know.
♪ What are the rules? ♪
♪ When you just turned black ♪
♪ And you can't switch back ♪
♪ Well, you got to go
and find out the rules ♪
♪ I think we're in The Wiz ♪
Don't force the Wiz thing.
Wait, where are my keys?
- Where are my keys?
- You got 'em?
I can't...
Wait, what is this?
- It's a wallet.
- I know it's a wallet, asshole.
I'm saying it's not my wallet.
Oh.
I appear to be a guy
named Reggie Williams.
Oh, shit. Oh.
Yeah, this is an interesting new rule.
It seems that even though
we have our own clothes,
we have access to the
pockets of our reflections.
- What movie is that from?
- I don't know that one.
My pockets are empty.
Oh! Maybe the lesson
we're supposed to learn is
that black people are broke.
You're broke.
- That's a good point. Yeah, yeah...
- Oh, shit, hang on a second.
This kid's got 25 bucks.
Oh! Black people are rich.
- That's the lesson.
- You know what, no, I think we're not
supposed to make wild
assumptions about black people
based upon whether or not
we have stuff in our pockets.
Yeah, that's... that's just...
Don't make that assumption.
But I'll tell you what, you know what
the first thing I need to do is?
Find Reggie Williams.
Uh, no, actually, that's
the second thing.
I got to cancel my credit card, 'cause
this Reggie guy might have it, you know?
Oh, right, that's the
lesson we have to learn:
that black people
will ruin your credit.
No... What?
Dude, you... you have to stop.
And you have to stop. I mean...
What are you talk... I'm just trying
to figure out what the lesson is.
We're never gonna zap
back making these kind of...
Well, hold on a second... the
thing I was saying was that I
would cancel my credit card no
matter what race the guy was.
- But you went right to it...
- All right, you know what,
okay, fine, let's just find the guy.
Look, how are we gonna get in
your car without your keys?
Oh, I can get in, man. I've
lost my keys before. You just
got to kind of rock the car a
little bit. Wiggle it down?
And check the back door,
actually, 'cause sometimes...
- sometimes that's unlocked.
- Back door.
- Like a wire hanger or...
- Usually if I push it
- a little bit, though...
- A coat hangar somewhere.
Just kind of slide the window down...
Car 559, responding
to robbery in progress.
Shit. Okay, look, it's all right,
all right, calm down, calm down.
It's all good, it's all good.
You know, we can talk
our way out of this.
We get out of this stuff all the time.
♪ Well, I think we just
found out a new rule. ♪
This is the exact same place
where I found Old Black Man...
- What. God, God, Frank.
- Oh, sorry, sorry. Old Man...
- Okay.
- In the first place.
You know what? This has
got to be our mission.
I just feel it. We're
just gonna find Old Man.
- We're gonna find him a place to live.
- Yeah, yeah.
Like, we'll stick him in a
nursing home or something.
You can afford that, right?
- Right, right. And then...
- Yeah.
When we turn white again,
I'll stop paying the checks.
Oh, stop! Don't-don't say that out loud.
Just... I feel like whoever zapped
us here is probably listening.
Who's that? Who zapped us?
I don't know, Ziggy? They don't...
They never really clarified
on Quantum Leap.
They just, they just accepted it.
What? You mean nobody ever
went after the guy for revenge?
Can you just move past it like they did?
Okay. Let's go find your guy.
All right, all right, but
let me do the talking,
because, you know, guys like
Z, they don't like strangers.
Yeah, but you're not you.
Oh, right.
Um, okay. Well, I got an idea
of how we can ingratiate
ourselves to them.
♪ Let's make one thing perfectly clear ♪
♪ I'm gonna say some words down here ♪
♪ I haven't had the chance
to say before ♪
Where are you going with this, Frank?
♪ I'm gonna say "homie" ♪
Oh, come on.
♪ I'm gonna say "bro" ♪
Are you serious?
♪ I'm gonna say "my man" ♪
Well, not you're just stereotyping.
♪ I'm gonna say "fo' sho'" ♪
Okay.
♪ I'm gonna say the "N" word. ♪
No, no, no, no, no.
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
- Why? Why?
- Thank you. No.
No, we're not saying that.
- Absolutely not.
- Why? I'm black now.
It's probably the only
chance I got to say it.
Why are you looking
for a chance to say it?
Well, a lot of black guys say it.
Why-why-why should they get a pass?
It's just not the same, okay?
♪ You're not one of them ♪
♪ Don't say them ♪
♪ No, that's not what I mean ♪
♪ What do you mean? ♪
♪ You're not one of us ♪
♪ That's just confusing ♪
♪ Now I'm getting lost ♪
♪ We'll say "N" together ♪
♪ Not saying the "N" word ♪
♪ We'll leave off the "E-R" ♪
♪ Not saying it that way ♪
♪ And that is the end ♪
♪ On saying the "N" word. ♪
What's up, my niggas?
Oh, well.
What are the rules?
There you go. Hey, see?
- You know what it is?
- Yeah.
I, uh, I'm black.
Uh... too. Uh...
I'm, uh, I'm black and I,
I'm a friend of Frank's.
- Right, right, right.
- And, uh...
And I was looking for... Okay.
A man, uh, you know, that Frank came
and brought to Dee's apartment to, uh,
sleep with a bunch of
other people, and I...
I don't, I don't know
how to describe him.
He's, uh, old, and, uh, um...
- And he's...
- And, uh...
He's, uh, about... this tall; he has...
Nigga, you talking about Old Black Man.
He right over there laying.
How much does this
guy sleep? Is he a cat?
All aboard. Chug-a-chug-a-toot-toot.
You really like that train, huh?
Can you put it down for
a sec, so we can talk?
Well, I'm, I'm still
playing with it, though.
Okay.
Listen, I'm a social worker,
and I have some questions.
Now, are those older guys your friends?
Oh, yeah. That's my gang.
Wait.
Y-You're in a gang?
Oh, not like a gang-gang, like a...
Oh, right... this must sound weird.
All right, how can I explain this? Um...
♪ Well, we hang in a bar ♪
♪ Where I like to clean the toilets ♪
♪ And I also kill the rats
and get tanked ♪
♪ And I live in a walk-up ♪
♪ In some section eight housing ♪
♪ Where I sleep with a man named Frank ♪
You sleep with him?
♪ Unless he brings home a hooker ♪
♪ Then I sleep in the closet ♪
♪ Excuse me, can I
make this train fly? ♪
Um, sure.
Is Frank your father?
♪ No, he's just some guy ♪
♪ That banged my mother ♪
♪ Like this guy and the other ♪
♪ She's a hooker and it's sad ♪
♪ But I don't feel all that bad ♪
♪ Guess I'm just another black kid ♪
♪ Who doesn't know his dad. ♪
Guess we got that in common, huh, kid?
Oh, unless he knows his dad.
Oh, shoot. That was racist.
This is bullshit, man.
Th-This is total discrimination.
Well, we were breaking into
a car that wasn't ours.
But, dude, I think we've got
bigger problems on our hands.
- What if we have priors?
- I do have priors.
Oh, I have priors, too.
I-I didn't mean us, I meant them.
Dude. That could be...
He probably does have
priors. You prob...
- Yeah.
- Oh, no, see. No. Let's not do that.
Let's not go there, man.
♪ Let's not draw conclusions ♪
♪ They're only just illusions ♪
♪ Never, ever, ever just assume ♪
Right.
♪ The road is always two ways ♪
♪ And assumptions make bad
through-ways ♪
♪ Let's open our hearts
for much more room ♪
Yes.
♪ Like maybe I'm a doctor ♪
♪ Maybe it's just that ♪
♪ Or maybe I'm a French chef ♪
♪ And that's why you're so fat ♪
♪ Maybe you're a fireman ♪
♪ Saving people's lives ♪
♪ Maybe we're just good men ♪
♪ With houses, kids and wives ♪
♪ Let's draw good conclusions ♪
♪ Let's make a better guess ♪
♪ Let's hope we learned our lesson ♪
♪ And just pray for the best. ♪
Well, Reverend, I see that you
and the deacon are praying.
I apologize about any inconvenience
and just want to thank you again
for all the work your parish has done
with the police athletic league.
We're church blacks!
Church people.
Yeah. Church... we're
just church people.
The fact that we're black is irrelevant.
Has nothing to...
Will you look at this place, Old Man?
You will not have to be living
with that Dee person anymore.
So it's kind of a win-win for
everybody in this situation.
- Carl.
- Ruth.
Where have you been?
Looking for you.
Children, did you find him?
Yes. Yes... children?
We're their kids!
- Holy shit!
- Oh, shit.
- We reunited them.
- We did.
- That was our mission.
- We did it!
- Oh!
- Oh, God, yes.
Hey. What's all the hubbub
about over there?
Oh, shit.
Oh, what?
That's Scott Bakula from Quantum Leap.
I thought you said
Blacula, like a black vampire.
Hey. So we were right?
Wait a minute, are you
here helping somebody?
- Are you leaping?
- Oh, my God.
The show... I can't get away from it.
Look, that was just a TV
character. I'm an actor.
- Why do you got a mop?
- Researching a role.
So...
You didn't get a piece of the show?
Your residuals ran out. I'm sorry.
I've been working constantly
for 30 years, okay?
All right. Okay, yeah.
So... Well, anyway, we just
reunited a family, and
we're gonna, Yeah.
We're gonna leap. We're gonna leap now.
Yeah, right now.
Ziggy, now!
It's not working. How do you do it?
- How'd you do it on the show?
- Tell us how to do it.
Okay, just get out, okay? Hmm?
- Get out. Everybody, everybody get out.
- Wait.
Fine. Fine, Scott.
But listen to me.
Don't steal our leap.
Yeah. Don't steal our leap.
♪ How did they know ♪
♪ That my wife took it all? ♪
♪ And I'm not researching roles ♪
♪ How did they know? ♪
♪ Ziggy, if you hear me ♪
♪ Take me far, far from here ♪
♪ Let me leap to '89 ♪
♪ That was a better year ♪
♪ I miss my old Camaro ♪
♪ And my mansion in Van Nuys ♪
♪ Wish I still hung with Nash Bridges ♪
♪ Played poker with The Fall Guy ♪
♪ Oh, Ziggy, can you see ♪
♪ My tears? ♪
♪ Ziggy! ♪
♪ Leave me far... ♪
♪ Far from here. ♪
Hey, Hollywood.
Why don't you leap on
up to the third floor.
Somebody shit all over the dining hall.
Okay, boss.
Dude, can I admit something to you?
I feel like that's the nicest the
police have ever treated me.
Well, maybe that's the lesson
that we have to learn.
That if you're an upstanding
member of society,
then the police will treat
you with respect.
Hmm. Although I still do suspect
that we were arrested
- due to racial profiling.
- Aw, I don't think so, dude.
No?
I think it's still, I
think it's still unclear.
♪ What are the rules? ♪
Ugh. Here we go with this.
♪ When your race has changed ♪
♪ Life can be real strange ♪
♪ When you're trying
to figure out all the rules ♪
- Hey, guys.
- Oh, hey. Hey.
- Well, we're not in a Quantum Leap.
- What?
We reunited Old Black...
Old Man with his wife.
- Nothing happened.
- Yeah, we ran into Blacula.
- Bakula.
- Scott Bakula, the actor?
- Yeah, I think
- he's trying to steal our leap.
- Yeah, he might be.
- Mm-hmm.
- This doesn't make any sense.
See, we're not in a classic
body-switching movie, either,
because we've been learning
lessons left and right,
- and we're still not changing back.
- Really? Huh.
♪ Oh! What are the rules? ♪
♪ What are the rules? ♪
♪ When you've kept your brain ♪
♪ But the world's insane ♪
♪ How the hell you gonna
find out the rules? ♪
Well, guys, maybe we didn't
keep our brains after all,
like the Scarecrow in The Wiz.
I grabbed Dee's VCR, 'cause I'm thinking
maybe if we get this thing fixed,
we can get shocked again
while watching The Wiz,
and that'll send us back.
Oh, my God! Charlie! I can't
believe I didn't think of this.
Do you guys remember
that electronics store
on Market Street? The Wiz?
It's called The Wiz! Yes!
Maybe we got to bring the VCR there.
Guys, I think we really are in The Wiz.
- You called it, man, yeah.
- I don't know, I don't know.
We can't be sure, but, uh...
at this point it does feel like
the path of least resistance.
It's the only thing we haven't tried.
Yeah, right?
♪ What are the rules? ♪
♪ Of being black in America ♪
♪ Of leaping from your body ♪
♪ What are the rules? ♪
♪ Who can say the "N" word? ♪
♪ I really wanna say the "N" word ♪
♪ What are the rules? ♪
Oh, shit, there it is! The Wiz!
We can't do that dance anymore.
- That was exhausting.
- It's closed!
Hey, open up! We need
your help! Open the door!
- Back up. Here he comes.
- Ah.
What do you want? We're closed.
- We're to see the Wiz.
- Yeah, we really got to talk to him.
There's no Wiz. It's just
the name of the damn store.
- Oh, yeah?
- Oh. Well, all right, man,
well, can you just fix this
VCR for us, please? Yeah.
Go away. Come back when we're open.
- Wait-wait-wait.
- Just-just hear us out.
♪ Excuse me ♪
♪ Ooh... ♪
♪ My kind brother ♪
♪ Ah... ♪
♪ But can you lend a hand? ♪
♪ Ooh... ♪
♪ Ah... ♪
♪ We really are in trouble ♪
♪ Ooh... ♪
♪ Ah... ♪
♪ We
really need a friend ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Ah... ♪
♪ We're trapped inside these bodies ♪
♪ Trapped inside, we're trapped inside ♪
♪ Ooh... ♪
♪ It's so hard to understand! ♪
♪ But if you look inside ♪
♪ Our souls, sir ♪
♪ Ah... ♪
♪ You'll see that we're white men. ♪
Oh. Oh. Oh, I see.
Yes! I see it now.
Let me fix your VCR.
Yeah! Oh, great!
Thank you! Thank you,
thank you, thank you.
That's a nice white man.
And the song helped.
- Yeah, it worked.
- 911?
I'd like to report a disturbance.
He's definitely
calling the cops.
- That racist bastard!
- Hey, you know what happened,
is we intimidated him
'cause we're black.
Oh, my God.
No. You know why he's calling the cops?
He's calling the cops 'cause
he thinks we're insane people.
We were singing and talking
about switching bodies and shit.
What are the rules?
- Whoa-whoa-whoa.
- Ugh, I'm sick of that one.
I don't want to have
to sing that song again.
All right? That being said,
it is difficult to decipher
when exactly we're being
discriminated against. Yeah.
Well, look, look, look.
♪ Maybe that's the lesson here ♪
♪ Things are not always that clear ♪
- That's definitely true.
- They're not.
♪ We have a lot in common ♪
♪ But too much of it ♪
♪ Is fear ♪
You're right.
- Right.
- That's right.
♪ So here come those police again ♪
Shit.
♪ But let me talk,
'cause they're my friends ♪
♪ They like me ♪
♪ They gave me this train. ♪
He's got a gun!
- Oh, God!
- They shot Charlie!
Freeze! Get on the ground!
♪ We just learned our lesson ♪
♪ Aah-aah, yeah! ♪
♪ A horrible lesson ♪
♪ Aah, yeah! ♪
♪ We just learned our lesson ♪
♪ And we wanna go home ♪
♪ Our home ♪
♪ White home ♪
♪ Just say home, we really ♪
♪ Really wanna go home ♪
♪ Let's click our heels together ♪
♪ Whoa, yeah ♪
♪ And pray we leave forever ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ We just learned our lesson
and we wanna go home ♪
♪ Our home ♪
♪ White home ♪
♪ Just say home! ♪
♪ We really, really ♪
♪ Wanna go home ♪
♪ O... ver the rainbow! ♪
♪ I wanna, wanna, wanna,
wanna, wanna, wanna go home ♪
♪ I wanna, wanna, wanna, wanna,
wanna, wanna go home ♪
♪ I wanna go home. I wanna,
♪ I wanna go home I wanna,
wanna, wanna go home. ♪
Go home! Go home! Go home!
Wake up! Hey, go home! Go home.
Go home! Wake up!
Go home. It's morning.
You know the routine.
Go home. Or wherever the hell
it is you go during the day.
I had the craziest dream.
You were there. You were
there. You all were singing.
All right, well, that's great.
We don't give a shit,
'cause we don't like hearing
about people's dreams.
Yeah, let's go, chop-chop. Come on.
Does this mean you
didn't learn your lesson?
What in the hell is he talking about?
Learn a lesson from your dream?
How would that work?
Yeah, the only thing we learned is
that you have terrible taste in movies.
Yeah. Let's go. Come on.
We'll see you later tonight.
Yeah. We'll see you, pal.
- Hit the road.
- Do your day thing. Do your day thing.
He wants me to learn a
lesson from his dream.
♪ We got to have peace ♪
♪ To keep the world alive ♪
♪ And war to cease... ♪
Oh, boy.
What are the rules?
♪ We got to have joy ♪