Oh, Christ, does every single
one of these kids have the flu?
Seems like it.
All right, now I bet you guys
are wondering what's going on
- with this racing suit, huh?
- No, not even a little bit.
You're like,
"What's that rascal Charlie up to?"
"What's he up to this time?"
Right, right?
- I'm not thinking that at all.
- Yeah, yeah, well,
it's an issue of aerodynamics, really.
You see, every second counts
in the water park.
- Right.
- And we plan to ride
- every single ride in there today.
- Yup.
Yeah, the brochure says three days.
We're saying bullshit to that.
- We're gonna get it done in one.
- One day.
All right, well, good luck
with that 'cause you got, like,
ten minutes of clean water and
then every slide's basically
a urine delivery system.
- Yeah.
- We're not gonna get
- drenched in piss.
- No.
We're gonna go in there,
find our favorite ride,
- bomb down it once,
- Yeah.
then sit by the pool the
rest of the day disease-free.
Don't kid yourself about the water,
buddy.
You're not gonna be disease-free;
this water's already infested
with every parasite on the planet.
And I, for one, have no intention
of stepping foot in any of it.
So what do you come to a water park for?
Hot food, cold beer,
bikini'd women seeking relief
from the insufferable
prison of motherhood.
Yeah, lot of pleasures to
be had at the park, Frank.
- None of which involve piss.
- Hmm.
And it's all free, too,
if you know how to get it.
Well, it's not free,
you got to pay to get in.
Not me, I had my bracelet
laminated in the '90s.
I haven't paid to get
in here since I was 14.
- Nice!
- Nice, nice.
- Oh, smart.
- Oh, shush! Shush, shush, shush, shush,
- they're about to open!
- Why do we have to shush?
Oh, guys! I almost forgot.
Do not go near the pool drains,
no matter how good you might
think they feel on your butt.
- What? - Huh?
- What?
You do not sit on those!
You know, because of the suction
on your butthole?
No one's thinking about that, man.
No one's thinking about that at all.
Oh, good, 'cause it is bad news.
Those things will suck the
intestines right out of you.
Like it did to that one kid back in '96.
Now, she had to chew
through her intestines
- just to get free.
- When I see the drain,
I'm not gonna go try and sit on it.
- Oh, here we go.
- Okay, here we go! Here we go!
We got to go! Get in there!
- Go! Go! Go!
- Christ!
♪ Kiddie Twister ♪
Here we go, here we go, here we go!
- Yeah, Kiddie Twister!
- I'm so excited.
- It's been, like, 20 years.
- What's that?
Uh, it's a urine tester.
Just want to be 100% sure.
It turns light red at the
slightest hint of piss.
- And I think we're good.
- Let's roll.
Hey, guys, guys, guys.
Slide's for kids only.
Size requirement.
Shut up, nerd!
Kiddie Twister!
Screw you, nerd!
You're gonna get hurt
Uh, come on, nerd.
Whoo-hoo! Kiddie Twister!
I don't give a shit.
Kiddie Twister!
Kiddie Twis... Oh, shit!
- Kiddie Twister!
- Wait, Dee, no!
No, I'm stuck, wait!
Ow!
Shit!
Ow! Ow, Dee, I'm stuck!
Yeah, no shit!
- Dee, you got to move.
- Me move? You move.
You're blocking me.
Your stupid wrist band
got us all jammed up.
It's not just that.
The slide's too small,
the nerd was right.
Shit, what are we gonna do?
Uh... okay. Just remain calm, all right?
Do not panic,
that's the worst thing you can do.
Okay, but we got to get unstuck
before they send another kid
because... oh, God,
some big, fat kid's just gonna
come blasting down on us.
You're gonna be fine. Trust me.
- Shit!
- Goddamn it!
Jesus Christ!
This is slow, Charlie.
I'm never gonna get through this crap.
We should've gone down
the first slide we saw.
I know, I know, but we needed
to start at the northmost point
of the park, right?
- Then we work our way south,
- Yeah.
and that cuts back on the excess
- running back and forth.
- Oh, yeah.
You know, that said,
I'm sorry I got us so lost.
I can't ever tell which
way is north on a map.
It's at the top.
- I thought north was, like, up.
- "Up"?
Yeah, like if I turn the map this way,
now where is north?
- Still at the top of the... no.
- Down?
- Now, come on, Charlie, this is ridiculous.
- It's confusing, right?
We got to get going here.
- I know, goddamn it.
- Where's he going?
- Coming through. Excuse us.
- What, what?
How come he can cut to the front?
Oh, Ethan is here with a special program
for children with leukemia,
so he skips to the front of the line.
Thank you! Coming through.
AIDS!
AIDS, I got AIDS.
I got AIDS, we're coming through.
- Yeah, yeah, sorry.
- Cutting through.
I'm his doctor, my patient's got to get
- to the front of the line
- Yeah.
- Because he has AIDS.
- I got the AIDS.
He got it from a gay guy in the '80s.
- I'm not gay, I didn't... but...
- Well...
There's two kind of AIDS...
there's the vagina AIDS and
then the needle-based AIDS.
I-I'm a vagina guy.
- Well, no, actually my test results show
- I got... sorry, I'm... AIDS.
that it was the gay AIDS.
- All AIDS are bad.
- Well...
That's... no good AIDS.
But I'm telling you, like I said,
this is not the gay AIDS.
Lie back down.
One of these little stinkers yours?
My son.
This one here?
Mm-hmm.
- Oh, yeah, he's adorable.
You?
Oh, daughter, yeah.
I try to take her to
fun places like this.
Let a little sunshine back into her life
ever since her mom...
Oh, my God. Did she...
Die horrifically?
Yeah.
Drowning. Kind of ironic,
us being at a water park,
but, you know, you got to...
you got to roll with the punches,
you know?
Got to get back out
there and live life...
Daddy, Daddy, can I borrow $20?
What?
Oh, hi there, what's your name?
Abby.
I'm hungry, Daddy.
Can I please have $20?
Well, I think you can get
something to eat
for a lot less than that, hon.
Dad!
I'm hungry, I'm starving,
and you haven't given me any money.
Yeah.
What the hell?
Anything for my little...
Abby.
Interesting.
What's interesting?
Nothing.
I'm done with you.
Keep up.
- Aah! Jesus.
- You'd think all the pressure
would blast us through.
No, it's just squeezing
me further into the stuck!
Okay, well, get-get the bracelet off.
- Just rip it off.
- Dee, I'm trying.
I can't get any actual leverage on it.
Besides, it's triple-laminated.
- It's not just gonna rip.
- Oh, no.
- I think someone peed.
- What?!
Sherman, did you pee?
- No.
- Sherman, my vial
- is turning light pink.
- Ugh...
goddamn it, Sherman,
I ordered you not to pee!
- Sorry!
- Oh, disgusting!
Sorry's not gonna cut it, Sherman,
- it's not gonna cut it.
- Nobody else pee!
Ah, the sun's just blasting me
right in the face.
Why does it have to be right there?
Dee, if God put the sun there,
there's probably a reason, okay?
Don't question him; we need God!
God didn't put the sun anywhere.
The sun stays still;
the Earth moves around it.
- Oh, Jesus Christ.
- Okay. All right.
We gotta get these kids out of here.
All right. I'm going for it.
I'm just pulling on one of 'em.
Come on. Ah, this friggin'
dome's like a magnifying glass.
Get him through, I can get him.
- Get help.
- Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Kid, kid, kid, listen. Come here.
Before you go,
no matter how alluring it is,
do not put your genitals
or your butthole
near the pool drain. You got it?
- In fact, cover your butthole.
- Okay, go.
- Okay, kid. Go, kid, go!
- Come on. Go.
Cover that butthole, kid!
Mac. Stop talking to children
about their buttholes, okay?
- It's not appropriate.
- Okay.
Okay.
Uh, I think we gotta get
another kid out.
You know what?
What about this one?
That kid looks passed out, Dee.
Yeah, he's out cold, but I think
I can maneuver his body pretty easily.
Yeah, but if we send him down there,
he might drown.
Guys, I gotta take a poop.
- I see you stealing.
- I wasn't stealing them!
I just forgot I was wearing them!
Let go of me!
My dad's a cop!
Abigail! What is going on in here?
Where have you been?
I've been worried sick about you.
- This your daughter?
- Yes.
Officer Dennis Reynolds.
Hi. Off-duty, of course.
This is your jurisdiction.
- Look, I caught her stealing sunglasses.
- Yeah?
- No, I didn't! I was just...
- Abigail,
I gave you $20 to buy
whatever you wanted.
What happened to that?
Do you still have it?
Yes.
Well, then you need to
pay for these sunglasses.
Actually, no. You know what?
On second thought, no.
You don't get the sunglasses.
- You need to be taught a lesson.
- I think that she gets...
I really appreciate
everything that you do.
Real police officer to security guard,
honestly,
I want to thank you for everything.
- Thanks.
- This little girl,
she's gonna be grounded for a month.
Come on, Abigail, let's go.
Try to touch me, and I'll scream "rape."
Please.
I see the road you're headed down:
the lying, the stealing, all of it.
And as somebody who's
been down that road,
let me tell you something:
you've got real talent.
Okay...
Mmm.
That ought to work.
What are you doing?
Oh, it's a simple lunch play.
I tell the burger stand
some hyperactive brat knocked
my food on the ground,
they replace it, no questions asked.
I usually just swipe a burger
off some dumb-ass family
while they're not looking.
Well, that begs the question, Abigail:
you want to be a thief or
do you want to be an artist?
You see, an artist takes whatever
he wants when somebody's
looking right at him.
- These are too small for me.
- Yeah.
- You get the point.
- I got AIDS, AIDS.
- AIDS! Guy with AIDS, coming through.
AIDS, coming through. AIDS, AIDS...
- AIDS!
- Hey, man, go through.
Hey, go for it, go, go, go!
No, you need a raft! You need a raft!
- Ah! Ah!
- Ow!
Go.
- My camera!
- Oh, great, your camera.
I was really worried about that.
This is my watch.
Go.
- My sunglasses.
- Oh, all of our chains!
You know how hard it is
to get all of our chains.
- AIDS...
- AIDS, AIDS!
Ow!
Stop sending kids, nerd!
- You goddamn nerd!
- Go.
- We're making good time.
- We're doin' it, Charlie.
We're pretty much...
we're pretty much caught up.
Whoa, hey, hey, guys!
What are you guys doing?
You guys doing a AIDS thing?
- Oh, yeah!
- Yeah.
I gave Frank a couple hickeys
- to sell the lesions.
- Sucked on 'em.
Yeah, yeah.
You doing a fake daughter thing?
- Yeah.
- Cool. All right, man, see ya.
See ya.
Three, two, one, go!
I got AIDS!
Yeah!
- Frank, we did it, man!
- Charlie!
- With time to spare!
- Charlie! We...
- Every single ride in here!
- We won!
Hey! Hey, hey, hey!
Hey! Suck on that, river rat!
Every ride!
- We did it.
- Oh, shit.
Frank. Look at this!
- Oh.
- Oh...
What... what is that?
I don't know.
I mean, that-that's not on the map...
what ride is that?
Excuse me?
- Excuse me, ma'am?
- Yeah?
What is this ride over here?
Oh, that's our new slide.
It's, uh, Thunder Gun Express.
We just finished construction.
It'll be open in a few weeks.
- A Thunder Gun ride?
- Yeah.
Like the movie?
Yeah, but there's no water
or anything yet,
- so we still have to test it.
- Oh, yeah.
It's totally dry.
- Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- It's not, it's not...
no, but it's not, it's,
it's not open yet.
It's Thunder Gun, man. No hesitation.
- No, no, no.
- No surrender. No man left behind.
We got to get to the top of that slide.
And raw-dog the shit out of it!
- Mac?
- Yeah?
My vial is blood red.
That's because the water's not
even running through anymore.
It's just pooling up.
- Well, I got to tell you something, though, I...
- Huh?
I don't know if I'm gonna be
able to hold it much longer.
- What?!
- I-I've been in here for so long, I-I...
Don't you do it, Dee! Don't you do it!
The problem is it's already happening.
I'm peeing on your shoulder right now.
But I don't mean to, I'm sorry.
- It's warm.
- You bitch!
When we get out of here,
I'm gonna kill you!
What am I supposed to do?
How are you even holding your pee?
We've been stuck in here forever!
Oh, I peed as soon
as we got in the slide.
- Me, too.
- What?!
- Ew!
These animals are, they're laughing!
Of course they are!
I think they're actually
enjoying this shit!
Oh, they love every second of it!
- They're just pissing all over us!
- Goddamn it.
We're gonna die in here with them!
Wait, wait, wait. Wait a second, Dee.
- I've got an idea!
- What?
If we can get Sherman's mouth
to this bracelet,
we can get out of here.
You said you couldn't rip through it.
No, I can't.
But Sherman can chew through it!
Like the girl in the pool drain
when she got her anus stuck,
she chewed through
her prolapsed anus and
chewed herself to freedom.
- What are you talking about?!
- Sherman!
Get your mouth to this
bracelet and chew!
Aw, screw it. Try it.
Chew like you've never chewed before.
Go, Sherman, chew!
Whoa!
Whoa! Hey, hey, hey, hey!
What are you doing?
I got some boy to give me this.
I said I'd kiss him if he
met me in the parking lot.
Then I swiped his wristband,
so he can't get back in.
Nice.
Thanks. Well, I got to roll.
What do you mean? Where you going?
We're just getting started.
Yeah, but my mom said
it's time to leave.
Wow.
That's a disappointing
glimpse into your future.
Now, why don't you tell your mom
you want to stick around
for a little while?
That won't work.
She never listens to me.
Oh, now, see, no. That bothers me.
A genius whose fate is
controlled by an idiot?
You think I'm a genius?
Yes! Yes, I think you're a genius.
Are you kidding me?
When I was your age,
I couldn't have accomplished
half the things you did today.
See, this is why the
Chinese are destroying us.
If you were born in China,
you'd be the head of
some factory by now.
Or they would've thrown you in a river,
'cause you weren't a boy.
All right, it's not a great analogy,
but you get my point.
A-Abby...
you deserve better.
Here, I... I want you to have it.
No, what do you mean? You earned that.
No, please, take it.
So you never forget me.
Thanks, Dennis.
For being the first adult to
actually give a shit about me.
You!
Yes?
We need to have a conversation.
Your daughter is a special kid.
A gifted child who should be treasured.
If she were born in China, she...
Wait, I already did that.
Didn't work.
If she were born in...
What country treasures their women?
- What are you talking about?
- What am I talking about?
Mom, can I have a slushy?
Yes, in just a minute.
Is that Abby's brother?
I don't have a daughter.
Yes, you do. The girl that was just...
Please take it.
So you never forget me.
See, an artist
takes whatever he wants...
...when somebody's looking right at him.
What is wrong with you? Why are you...?
Huh.
How would you even describe
something like that?
It's so beautiful.
They should've sent a poet.
- All right, let's go, let's go.
- Okay.
- All right, all right.
Here we go.
Oh, oh.
All right.
This should be good, right?
Oh, that's great.
- That'll do it.
- Oh!
Who's going first?
Well, it should be you, right?
I mean, you pulled off the AIDS thing.
Oh, Charlie! Charlie!
All right!
Let's go before we get caught.
Let's go before we get busted, okay?
- All right, here we go.
- All right.
- Ready, Frankie!
- I won't let you down!
- All right!
- I like the spirit here.
- Oh!
Oh, it burns! It burns!
It burns! It burns!
Aah!
My back!
That guy has AIDS!
Aah! Aah, my back!
AIDS! Everybody out.
Aah! Aah!
We're free!
Oh, my God!
Ah, we're free!
My God!
Is that blood?
There's AIDS blood in the pool!
That's goddamn AIDS blood?!
Has anyone seen my son?
Goddamn it!
I hate this goddamn water park!
- synced and corrected by sot26 -
www.addic7ed.com