What's going on with you, man?
Are you limping?
Uh, no, I've just been working out
on this new exercise bike I got,
- and my glutes are, like, so sore.
- Yeah.
Know what it is?
- Oh.
- Yeah, big-time, big-time.
- Howdy.
- Hi.
- It's... it's very windy today, isn't it?
Yeah.
Oh, man, look at this.
Dog shit.
Did you just step in that on purpose?
Oh, no, I just...
you know, I didn't really see it.
You pointed it out to me!
And then you stepped directly in it.
- Since when do you read?
- What? Nothing. No.
Books are stupid.
I don't. I was just...
It wasn't... like, I didn't time it out.
- I mean, why would I do that?
- I have no idea.
- Why are you still standing in it?
- It was just an accident, man.
People step in dog shit
accidentally all the time.
Is that a lottery scratcher?
Sometimes it's in,
- sometimes it's out.
- Are those mirrors?
- No.
- You creep.
Look out, faggot!
Holy shit.
God!
Are you okay?
Hey, Frank, what the hell was that?
What? I saved your life.
But you called me the "F" word.
So what? I'm a hero.
You used a slur, dude.
That's like a hate crime.
Yeah, that's hateful speech, man.
- You really can't...
- Yeah, but he saved his life.
Yeah, but you can't say
that word anymore.
So, which is it?
You are entitled to nothing!
Listen, motion to present
articles of confederation.
- Motion denied.
- Oh...
Shut up, bitch.
You don't deserve anything.
Excuse me. Hey. Can I help you?
Okay, look, well, usually,
we're a pretty reasonable crew.
- Yeah, right? I mean...
- Yeah.
...we have our differences,
but we settle them in house.
- Sure.
- We have a good process.
There's filibusters, the whole thing.
- No.
- This one's a doozy.
- Yeah, this one we can't do in-house.
- We can't... we can't...
That's why I wanted to
bring in a third party.
Someone to hear us out and
deliver a final verdict.
- That's you, guy.
- Yeah, that's... you.
That's you.
Because a great injustice
has occurred, okay?
Frank committed a hate crime.
I saved your life.
- But you used a slur!
- It was a slur.
- That's...
- You'd be dead if I didn't!
Okay, okay, I think I'm getting it.
You want me to figure out whether or not
a hate crime's been committed?
What?
- No.
- No, no, no, no.
- Way off. Way off.
- No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, but, no,
it's not about that at all.
Yeah, it's about this.
A two-dollar scratcher lottery ticket.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
Y-You've hired an arbitration attorney
to figure out which of you is entitled
to a two-dollar scratcher?
- Now you're getting it.
- Me.
- He's getting it.
- Now he gets it.
The thing is, each one of us
feels that we're entitled
to that ticket, and we need you
- to tell us who it belongs to.
- Yeah.
Why don't you scratch it
and see if it's worthless,
and then you wouldn't have
to go through all of this?
- Okay, so he's not getting it.
- What?!
- Is he serious?
- Do you not want a job?
Hold on. Is it Phil? Is your name Phil?
- Yeah, Phil, yeah.
- It is Phil?
It's Phil.
This ticket represents hope, okay?
Potential... yeah?
Promise.
The very foundation upon
which this group rests, eh?
- Yes.
- And that hope
belongs to me.
It belongs to me, you son of a bitch!
Please, stop.
Each of you will have an
opportunity to plead your case.
The only rule I have is that
you each treat each other
with respect and common courtesy.
Do we all agree to those terms?
Well, we would like to thank you so much
for taking our case so last-minute.
The other guy was not our style.
Well, I'm very happy to do so.
I do have a few questions.
- Fire away. - Yup.
- Of course, yeah.
Now, the ticket in question,
uh, who purchased it?
- Me! Thank you.
- Well...
That was me, and that's why
- this whole thing is so cut and dry.
- It's...
Hold on. I purchased the ticket,
and therefore the ticket belongs to me.
I actually bought the ticket
a couple of weeks ago.
But I didn't realize it was
gonna be so goddamn blustery
that afternoon.
And as I was putting
my book into my purse,
the ticket flew out and
landed on the ground.
So, you purchased the ticket
two weeks ago.
I did.
And why hadn't you
scratched the ticket yet?
Oh... well, that's because
nobody ever wins those tickets, right?
But as long as you don't scratch it,
then you're not a loser.
You know, in fact, you're a winner.
Potentially.
- God, Dee...
- That is so sad!
- It's so pathetic.
- What are...
- It is pathetic.
- So sad.
What are you talking... You just said
this exact same thing,
like, ten minutes ago,
talking about how the ticket
represented hope and all that bullshit.
Somehow coming from you,
it just came off so sad.
Well, hold on a second.
Motion for sub-arbitration
to determine whether or not that's sad.
Motion accepted. All in favor?
Aye.
Motion passed. It's sad, Dee.
I'd also like to point out
that while Dee's version is the truth,
it's not the whole truth.
Why don't we talk about the
contents of Dee's purse?
The scratcher ticket,
the candy sour worms,
the pack of cigarettes.
Now, what I want to know is...
how can a woman who makes
less than minimum wage
afford such impulse buys?
So, you're smoking now, Dee?
Is this about your weight?
Because if it is,
you're already too bony.
No, I don't think so.
I mean, I think you're
getting pretty tubby
in the midsection area.
- What?
- Like a bird.
No, no, that's fine.
Her hands are becoming a
major problem for me though.
I have Parkinson's disease.
What?
Well, at least I have a 46% chance
of getting Parkinson's disease,
according to a DNA test I took.
The medical journal was
because I'm trying to learn
as much as I can about this, you know?
And, you guys, according to that,
smoking can reduce your risk of...
Oh, my God, who gives a shit?!
- What?
- Dee, this isn't about whether or not
you have some horrific
neurological disease
or whether or not your
hands are the right size.
They are, by the way,
but your elbows are a mess.
They're too sharp.
I don't like it. They're stabbing me.
- That's what it is.
- You got it.
That's not the point,
that's not the point.
The point is:
how can you actually afford to smoke?
You see, Dee and I had a deal.
I give her money for coffee
every morning on the way to work.
And she's instructed to give
a very generous tip
to the cashier, Cassie.
"This is from my boss, Dennis."
Now, this establishes both
generosity and authority.
Possibly a little dominance.
It's all a very choreographed dance
between two soon-to-be lovers.
Ah...
Cassie's underage.
No, no, no, what-what?
What are you talking about?
Cassie is not underage.
Cassie is 21 years old.
So, the champagne I was purchasing
was to celebrate her
legal drinking status.
And to honor her full maturity.
You see, I was waiting
for Cassie to mature.
You know, much like an IRA.
Y-You put the money in, then you wait.
And then you make a hefty withdrawal.
Okay, yeah, sure.
Before full maturity, yeah, ew.
Yeah, but weren't you just saying
that you were doing
deposits before maturity?
Uh, no, no, no, no.
See, that's where you're wrong.
No, I was, uh,
between the ages of 18 and 21,
simply making investments.
But not for early deposits?
Well, deposits
are part of the withdrawal.
Sometimes I can't make a deposit at all.
Ugh, come on, man.
Just...
Okay, just to be clear:
a deposit's a load, right?
- Yeah.
- Well, yeah, yeah.
That's not what I'm talking about.
No, it's a totally different...
- Are you sure?
- No, with my... no.
Look, not in this particular case,
it's not a lo...
It's-it's...
Yeah, it's a load.
- Yeah. I mean, yeah.
- But that's not the point!
That's not the point! The point is:
Dee has no rightful
claim to that ticket,
and I'll prove it.
You see, yesterday,
after noticing the
contents of her purse,
I decided to follow her this morning.
Cassie never gets her tip,
does she, Dee?
No. Because I refuse to tip for coffee.
- I think it's dumb.
- Uh-huh.
So if you were buying circus peanuts
and candy sour worms and cigarettes,
I think we all know what that means
about the ticket in question, don't we?
I don't. Do you know?
- No.
- Totally lost.
That means she bought it with my money!
So, technically, that ticket is mine!
Okay, okay, okay.
Now, let me sum up the facts thus far.
Miss Reynolds bought the ticket
with Mr. Reynolds' money.
But Mr. MacDonald
currently possesses it.
Correct.
But I deserve it, and here's why.
There we were, right?
We were just walking down the street,
minding our own business.
I'd just spotted the
perfect pile of dog shit,
and naturally I stepped in it.
- What?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Okay, I'm a little confused.
Why would you voluntarily
step into the dog feces?
- Well, I didn't, really...
- You just said you did.
- You said naturally you did...
- And we all watched you do it.
All right, fine.
I voluntarily stepped in the dog shit
so that I would smell of dog shit.
Happy?
- Less happy.
- Why would it make me happy?
I was trying to cover up the smell
of the skunk that I let spray me
so that there would be no questions.
- Well, now I have more questions.
- Of course you do.
Like: why did you let a skunk spray you?
- To cover the smell of cologne, man.
- Oh, man. You know what?
Go to the beginning.
Go to the first smell!
The first smell that begat
all the other smells!
The first smell was cigarettes!
I've been smoking with Dee!
All right? Fine, I said it.
Oh. Oh, okay. So, right.
So you thought we would care
about the smell of cigarettes,
- but not the smell of skunk or dog shit.
- Mm. Mm-hmm.
Well, it doesn't matter anyway,
all right,
because I deserve the ticket.
Because if the shit shoe's a matcher,
Charlie gets the scratcher!
- Oh... shit. - What the shit?
- Come on.
That shirt reeks!
- Is that what that smell was?
- Yeah.
I thought it was just him.
It does smell; it smells very bad.
But give me a cigarette;
I'll cover it up.
But, look, if it smells like shit,
you must acquit.
You know what? If everyone's
gonna be smoking on my dime...
Look, nobody is debating whether or not
the shoe print is yours.
We all know that it is,
because everybody saw you kick me.
We're debating whether or not
you actually saved my life.
Which you did not,
because I was just about to do
- a sweet backflip to safety when you...
- Oh, bullshit.
He's never once flipped!
- Here we go.
- I do flips all the time.
- You have never once flipped.
- In the pool?
Which you would not have done
had I not warned you,
thereby saving your life!
That is my ticket.
Oh...
Ridiculous. "Backflip."
There I was, minding my own business,
bird watching.
Beautiful day, isn't it?
It's really gorgeous and...
Are those mirrors?
- No.
- You creep.
He wasn't really bird watching,
he was looking up women's skirts.
- He peeps on women.
- That's his move.
He's disgusting.
Like I said, bird watching.
Not you.
Now, the point is that I said,
"Look out, faggot,"
which were the words
that saved Mac's life.
Thereby, I am entitled to
at least half that ticket.
Well, why did you use the slur
instead of just yelling
your friend's name?
Well, there was a lot going on.
I needed something
that would cut through.
Well, as soon as I said the slur,
everybody knew to look at Mac.
Look out, faggot!
Mac knew to look.
Dennis and Dee knew to look.
Charlie, who kicked him in the chest,
knew to look.
Hell, even the little kid
with the balloon
knew where to look.
Okay, it may have been effective,
but it was an offensive slur.
And a bigot should not be
entitled to a hero's payout.
You're allowed to use
any language you want
to save somebody's life.
- Really? Any language?
- Yes.
- You gonna let a man die over a word?
- Yeah, yeah.
I mean, come on. It's just a word.
"Just a word." Oh. Okay.
Well, Frank, tell me something:
If you were going to save
somebody else's life,
you know, from a falling piano,
and you needed a word to just...
- to just cut right through...
- Mm-hmm.
...what word would you use
to call out to the arbiter?
Uh...
I suppose...
Yeah, you know what?
We're, uh, we're treading
- on some dangerous territory here, buddy.
- Yeah.
"Nigger"?
Oh! Whoa, whoa!
- What, what?
- Charlie, you can't use that word.
I'm trying to guess
the word that he was saying
- that he thought Frank was gonna say.
- No, you don't say that ever.
- I was not using the word.
- Don't ever... that's not...
You can't use that word, buddy.
And yet, we've just sort of been
casually throwing the F-word around
willy-nilly for the past few days,
and that hasn't been a problem?
Well, yeah, Mac, because the...
there's a very dark history
- associated with... the N-word.
- Yeah.
Did you know that a faggot
is a burning bundle of sticks
on top of which they
used to burn homosexuals?
So, basically,
when you call someone a "faggot,"
you are saying that they
should be burned at the stake.
Is that right? That's, uh...
- Yes.
- That's pretty dark, yeah, that's dark.
- That's pretty dark.
- Yeah, yeah.
Well, maybe there are a few words
- that we shouldn't be throwing around.
- Yep.
- Yeah.
- What about "cunt"?
- Oh!
We can't lose that!
- Yeah, it's a good word.
- What?
That's tough. It's a great word.
And it's just not offensive.
Especially, uh, directed towards
a woman when you're trying
to insult her.
When you're trying to
make a woman feel small.
That's extremely offensive!
Come on, you could yell "penis" at me,
and I'd be fine with it.
Well, all right, fine.
Well, then, we're gonna
take away your favorite word.
- Yeah.
- What, "cocksucker"? - Yeah.
What's wrong with that?
You can't say "cocksucker"
if we can't say "cunt."
I find it offensive that the idea
of sucking cocks is offensive.
Exactly. There's nothing
offensive about sucking cock.
Half the population loves to suck cock.
The other half of the population,
they love getting their cock sucked.
It's kind of a win-win.
We're getting off the point, okay?
In terms of the ticket,
I'm calling bullshit on Frank,
because, for some reason,
he thinks that I'm gay,
and that is why he called me the F-word,
which makes him a bigot.
Oh, wait.
Uh, catch me up here.
Now, you're not gay?
Obviously not.
Okay. Interesting.
So, Mr. Reynolds, um, simply,
was just trying to disrespect you.
He wasn't trying to make a comment
about your sexual orientation?
No, well, see, here's where things
get just a little bit
tricky, because Frank
thinks Mac is gay because...
- Mac is gay.
- Yeah.
What?! What-what are you talking about?
Enough with this.
- This is boring.
- I mean, he's into the closet,
- he's out of the closet.
- Yeah, yeah.
We don't like you either way.
Oh, look, now, I care about my body.
So now they become, like,
obsessed with me being gay.
Obsessed? We don't care!
We're the ones who don't care.
Okay. All right, hold on.
Dee, let me just...
let me put this to bed.
Okay, Mac, we're in support of it.
So, just come on out of the closet
- and be done with it.
- You'll feel better.
- Come on.
I honestly have no idea
what you're talking about.
Mac, Mac...
We found the bike.
Yeah, so?
The bike in the basement?
What about it?
Oh, Mac.
Mac,
- don't make me go get the bike.
- Oh.
I've got nothing to hide.
Just, uh, go get the bike.
I'm-a go get the bike.
I would like to present
into evidence, uh...
Mac's bike.
What? It's an awesome workout bike.
What's the big deal?
Okay.
Mac, why don't you go
ahead and operate the bike.
Yeah.
Sure.
No problem.
Just-just like any other workout bike.
Well...
You pedal...
Uh, there you go.
Outrageous.
Yeah, there it is.
I mean, it's just the craziest...
All right, all right, all right.
Okay, I...
I know what you're thinking, okay?
But it is not what it looks like.
Yeah, what it looks like
is that you are fucking
yourself with a dildo bike.
I mean, you got the bike shorts
with the slits in them, in the...
Oh, the-the ones in the back?
That's for air flow.
This is grotesque.
No, you're not understanding.
I modded out a regular workout bike,
to create the optimal workout.
- And added a penis.
- Yeah.
Oh... I see.
I see where you guys are
getting off the rails.
That's not a penis.
Oh.
It's a fist.
Uh...
I call it the Ass Pounder 4000.
- And it works like this.
- Uh, no...
Imagine you're riding up a steep hill,
and you've already been
working super hard,
and you're sweating and you're tired.
What do you do when you're tired?
You want to rest.
You go to sit down,
it pushes you right
back up in your workout.
The Ass Pounder 4000
will never let you rest.
- Yeah, see?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, we got it.
- That's the way it works.
- We got it.
Now, I even have an amazing tagline.
"The Ass Pounder: Never stop pumping."
Well, um...
think we've seen enough.
I've certainly learned something.
This... this has nothing to do
with being gay.
This is just the work of a man who's
an extreme sexual deviant.
Gay or not.
- Can I have one of those?
- Yeah, whatever,
- Yeah, whatever, dude.
- Oh, whatever.
You know, you guys are just
jealous because I've got
a million-dollar idea
and I've got the ticket.
You don't have the ticket yet, bitch!
I bought the ticket.
What are you talking about?!
Are you crazy?!
Quiet! Quiet!
Quiet!
Now, I've heard from everybody involved,
and I will make my decision.
But let me make one thing clear.
In order for this to be entirely just,
I will make my decision based
on fairness and compromise.
You understand?
Okay, I think I'm all caught up.
- All right, so what's the verdict?
- Yeah, what do you got?
I think it's actually
pretty straightforward.
Mr. MacDonald is in
possession of the ticket,
so he has ownership.
However, he would not be
in possession if his life were
not saved by Mr. Reynolds,
who set off the chain
of events saving him.
So I see it as a 50/50 split.
- Are you kidding me?
- I'm a hero!
- Oh! You bitch!
- 50/50 split?
- ...out of the way!
- Nothing for the man
- who paid for the ticket?
- I bought it!
And this bigot here is
gonna get a hero's payout?
He may be a bigot and he
did use disgusting speech,
but it's not technically
hate speech since Mr. MacDonald
does not claim to be gay.
Oh.
Oh, does that mean if I claim to be gay,
I get all of it?
Well, um, y-yes.
You would be entitled to keep all of it.
I claim to be gay!
- No!
- No, no, no, no.
Now you're gay?
There's a history behind it.
I've been gay forever.
Everybody knows it.
Even the balloon kid knew it.
Soon as he gets that ticket,
he's going back in the closet.
- Yeah. This isn't fair.
- Mark my words.
If he's gonna do it,
he's got to stay out,
which he won't, I guarantee you.
Fine. Whatever. Yeah. I'm out!
Totally out. I'm gonna...
Hey, uh, excuse me,
would you please do the honors
on my ticket, please?
- It's probably worthless.
- Okay. Sure.
Let's, uh...
let's see what we have here.
Okay.
Wow.
What?
- What is it?
- Well, you're a winner.
What? How much?
$10,000.
What?!
- No! No!
- Oh, my God!
Gay Mac rules!
- Bullshit!
- Gay-gay, rich Mac!
All right, if you will just sign this,
releasing the ticket
- and agreeing to my ruling.
- Don't mind if I do.
I wonder what I'm gonna do
with all this money.
Maybe start an LLC.
Ass Pounder 4000?
It's all going right into the product.
Yeah, yeah, sign the paper so
you can go back in the closet.
- Yeah.
- Go ahead.
- You go back in. Go ahead.
- Huh?
Well, you signed the thing.
You got your money.
Just go back in the closet.
Just get it over with.
We know you're gonna do it,
so you might as well just do it.
Yeah. Yeah.
I don't know.
Maybe I'll... maybe I'll stay out.
- Really?
- Yeah.
It doesn't matter.
You can just go back in.
You signed the paper.
Y-Yeah. I mean, you got your money.
No, I think I'm out now.
Yeah. I'm... I'm gay.
Actually feels pretty good.
See ya, guys.
- Wow.
- Finally.
- Eh, good for him, right?
- Yeah, good for him. I'm...
- Absolutely.
- Guess I'm happy for him.
Yeah, it's a relief, honestly.
All right, if, uh,
you'll just take care of this,
then, uh, we'll be all done.
- What's this?
- That would be a bill.
- Ooh.
- Oh, money stuff.
- Uh...
- That goes to Frank.
I know it's steep,
but you did go through
three arbiters,
and you've been here 17 hours.
- Yeah. I'm exhausted.
- Yikes, yikes.
What's-what's it add up to there, Frank?
$9,986.
- Yikes.
- Holy cow, you guys aren't cheap.
You guys aren't cheap.
The arbitration was Mac's idea.
- Let's let him pay for it.
- That's a great idea.
- That's fair. In fairness' sake.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, he's got the money for it.
- He's got the money now. Yeah.
But maybe let's make him
pay it tomorrow, you know?
- L-Let's let him have this.
- Yeah. Yeah.
Poor guy did just come
out over a $14 scratcher.
- That's all that's left?
- Yeah.
- Oh, no.
- That sucks.
Oh, no.
Tell you what, man, I am happy for him,
- but I do still hate him.
- Oh, yeah.
- It's not a gay or straight thing, is it?
- No, no, no, no, no.
It's a Mac thing.
- synced and corrected by sot26 -
www.addic7ed.com