[ doorbell ringing ]
[ locks clicking ]
What?
Hi, mrs. Reynolds.
What do you want?
Frank sent me over
to pick up his toupee.
His toupee?
Yep.
What does he need
his toupee for?
I think he has a date.
Frank has a date?
Yeah, I guess.
Well, he can't have it.
It's mine.
You own his hair?
All right, fine.
It's in a box in the hallway.
I was gonna
throw it away anyway.
So I'm really sorry about this.
I know it's probably
a tough time for you.
Divorce is a tricky thing.
Oh! I found it.
I got the hair now.
Found the hair.
So I guess I'll just,
uh, see myself out.
Right. Thank you for the hair.
Oh, shit.
[ frank ]
wait till you see the hair.
This is really
authentic-looking hair.
It looks good.
So how do you know
this chick, anyway?
Angie spinola--
High school. Firecracker.
Hung out all the time.
Oh, yeah?
Oh, yeah. We did
everything together.
Wild sex. Whoa!
I mean--
you name it, we did it.
- well, she sounds awesome.
- yeah. They don't make women
like angie anymore.
Tell you that right now.
Charlie, you gonna be okay,
I leave you alone
at the bar here?
I think things have been going
pretty well since you put me
in charge, frank.
Right.
Keep your fingers crossed.
[ imitates pistol ]
What are you?
Why? Why would a person
wipe their own shit
onto a wall?
[ toilet flushes ]
[ dennis ]
I don't know.
What are you doing?
I thought you were
cleaning the toilet.
What? Cleaning toilet?
No, that's what
charlie does.
I'm not doing
charlie work anymore.
Okay, dad said we need to,
so get back in there
and clean the stall.
Dee, dee-- will you
take it easy?
I got a little plan
to get us out of it.
You do?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, god, that's good news.
What is it?
Well, let's just say
I got a little date tonight,
And as soon as charlie
sees who it is,
No more charlie work
for me.
How does that help me?
I guess it doesn't,
really.
Mm-mmm. It sure doesn't.
You know, you should
come up with a plan
just like I did,
And then you can get out
of charlie work too.
Oh, you think I can't
come up with a plan?
[ door closes ]
-  [ country on jukebox ]
- hey!
- dennis, hey.
- got something for you.
What? Really?
Yeah.
Wow! Oh, thank you.
That's really nice.
Can I take your coat?
Uh, are we staying here?
No, no. I just
want to have a look
at what you're wearing.
[ laughing ]
okay.
All right.
So... What do you think?
Yeah, okay. That'll work.
Are you not wearing makeup?
I'm wearing makeup.
Really?
Yeah.
Do you have any more?
No. I didn't bring makeup.
Mmm.
Uh, okay. That's all right.
Let's go say
good night to charlie.
Come on.
Uh, I don't think
that's such a good idea.
Oh, no, no, no.
He's totally fine
with the situation.
It's cool. Come on.
Really?
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
[ door opens ]
[ laughing ]
hey, buddy.
Please knock if you're
gonna be coming
into my off--
What ya doin'?
Uh, I was doing
some office stuff.
Oh, yeah?
Well, listen, uh,
we are gonna hit the town,
So we just
wanted to pop back
and say good night.
Looks like
you got everything
under control back here.
- yeah, I do.
- that's a nice house of cards,
charlie.
Actually, no.
I was doing some business stuff
'cause I'm the manager now.
Great. Well, we're out of here.
Don't work too hard,
okay, bud?
- good night, charlie.
- yeah, good night.
- could you, uh,
give me one second?
- yeah.
Thanks.
[ chuckles ]
okay, listen.
Here's the deal.
I'm gonna bang her tonight,
probably around 10:30
or so.
Now, I really don't
wanna do that,
So all you have to do
to stop me is call
my cell phone-- by 10:30--
And say, "dennis, you don't
have to do charlie work
anymore."
- you're not gonna
get away with this.
- oh, yeah, I will.
I'll get away with it.
10:30, okay?
[ whispering ]
10:30.
Gonna blackmail me?
You gonna blackmail me,
dennis reynolds?
You ready?
I'm ready. Let's roll.
Hey-o!
What's up, buddy?
Hello.
What's that?
It's your dad's hair.
Gross.
Yeah. Is charlie here?
Yeah, man.
What's up with you?
You seem flustered.
Is charlie--
he's in the back office.
I wanna talk to him.
Okay. Go talk to him.
Okay.
Great. Yeah.
Uh-- bye, dennis.
See ya.
Charlie, I have
a real dilemma on my hands.
Normally I would never talk
to you about these things
because you're so unreliable,
But dennis, dee and frank
are all directly involved,
and I gotta tell somebody, man.
I am bustin'. Okay--
[ inhales ]
Dennis's mom tried
to have sex with me.
Interesting.
Yeah, man, she got naked,
she came on to me--
That woman is straight crazy,
but I think I wanna bang her.
I know I shouldn't do it--
- I think you should do it.
- what?
An opportunity like this
only comes around
once in a lifetime, right?
- right.
- you'd be a fool to let it
slip through your fingers.
Yeah, that's what I'm thinkin',
but it's dennis and dee's mom.
Well, that means
that no one ever, ever
is gonna find out.
- that doesn't make sense.
- it doesn't have to make sense.
- you're right. I'm gonna do it.
- [ both laughing ]
Okay. Okay.
Oh, this is good.
This is good.
Oh, oh, oh--
I gotta meet frank.
I gotta give him his hair.
You go, 'cause I gotta
plot, and I gotta think.
Oh, great.
Get out of here. Go.
God, this is good!
Dennis's mom.
Yes, he is. I'm busy.
I want my job back.
- look, I'm-- what?
- I want my job back.
Well, I'm--
And you shall have it.
Oh, dee.
It looks like we both
need things from each other.
I am not having sex
with you, charlie.
[ chuckles ]
no.
It's not sex
I want from you.
It's sex I don't want
from dennis.
Hmm?
Mmm. So you gotta tell me
about all the shit
you been gettin' into.
You must have a police record
a mile long.
Oh, god. No.
Don't be modest now.
You remember all the shit
we used to get into?
Mm-hmm.
You remember that night
in the graveyard?
How could I forget?
[ groans ]
that slab was cold, baby.
It was.
And remember the time
we robbed a motorcycle
and ran it into the river?
Yes.
Well, you must be doin' shit
like that now, huh? Come on.
Well, I've slowed down
quite a bit once I met
my husband, carl.
Oh, you told me
you weren't married.
Oh, I'm not.
Carl passed a few years ago.
- oh.
- once I met him and had kids,
I pretty much stayed at home.
Carl had two children
from a previous marriage,
And then we had
five of our own.
Oh, shit.
Hi. I'm jenny.
I'll be your server
this evening.
Are you ready to order,
or do you need
some more time?
I think we need just
a little more time.
I'll be back in a second.
Isn't having children
a blessing?
What?
Isn't having children
such a blessing?
What the hell
are you talking about?
Well, I mean, when carl passed,
my children were an enormous
source of strength.
I mean, I thought--
whoa, whoa,
wait, wait, wait.
Angie, I'm gonna have
to stop you.
I'm sorry?
This is not gonna work out.
- what's not going to work out?
- you, me, talking like this.
- why? What's wrong?
- for starters,
you've got kids and shit.
And you talk about 'em.
You talk about your kids,
you talk about your
dead husband.
- I mean, it's kind
of bummin' me out.
- oh, you know, I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
It's just, maybe--
I think you're too old for me.
Frank, I'm two years
younger than you.
That's what I'm talkin' about.
I had a really good
time tonight.
I had a good time too.
Okay, what's the deal
with that?
What?
Why do you keep checking
your cell phone?
I've just been--
I've been expecting
an important phone call.
I'm sorry.
No. Good luck with that.
Wait, wait, wait.
Don't-- don't go.
I wanna go inside.
No. I'm not gonna
ask you inside, dennis.
Why not?
Because I really...
Like you.
Well, yeah.
I mean--
I really like you too.
Then let's just
take it slow, okay?
Oh-oh, wait.
Uh--
I... Love you.
[ laughs ]
I--
I kind of don't know
what to say.
I kind of don't want you
to say anything.
[ ringing ]
oh, uh,
hold that thought.
Yo.
[ charlie ]
I'm ready to talk.
Cuttin' it
pretty close there, pal.
I almost sealed the deal.
Just meet me at paddy's
and we'll work it all out.
[ laughs ]
sorry about, uh--
I feel like
maybe I was being
a little judgmental.
You're good.
[ laughs ]
okay. Well, let's go.
No. You were right.
I should-- I'm gonna go.
Yeah. I'm gonna go now.
We should take it slow.
You were right.
Really? Because I...
Don't need to now.
I think it's good.
I think it's real good.
Call me.
[ chuckles ]
Charlie?
You called just
in the nick of time, buddy.
I was--
Looks like we got
a blown fuse in here.
Better get on that.
Blown fuses count
as charlie work.
Oh, I don't think I'll be
changing any fuses
any time soon.
[ singsong ]
I know something
you don't know.
That was, like, the best
sex I've ever had,
mrs. Reynolds.
Like something
magical happened.
Hmm?
I was just saying that
that was, like, so special,
And, I mean,
it was like magic.
You're not gonna start
talking about your feelings
and shit, are you?
No.
[ chuckles ]
gay.
No. It's just that--
I mean, unless
you want to, 'cause--
No.
I got a better plan.
Okay. All right.
Uh, so can I
call you sometime?
I have your number, right?
No, I don't think so.
I know how to find you.
Why don't we leave it
at that?
Wh-- all right.
Did I do something wrong?
I mean, was the sex bad?
Don't worry about it.
[ whines ]
I can make adjustments--
'cause I've had to do
that before, and it
hasn't been a problem.
I'm shutting the door now.
Well, if I could just
have a kiss good-bye,
That would be...
Really great for me.
If I gave you a kiss good-bye,
would you let go
of the door?
Yeah.
Fine.
Oh, my god. Oh!
Yeah. It's a terrible thing.
It's a terrible thing for
you to see that.
I'm gonna kill him.
No--
I'm gonna kill him!
No. Wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What are you gonna do,
punch him in the face?
Throw him?
Work the body a little?
No, no, it's not gonna help.
I'll tell you why.
It doesn't "un-bang" your mom.
No, you gotta do
something worse--
Something much, much worse.
You're gonna have
to bang mac's mom.
[ man on tv ]
I thought I was.
Hi.
What?
- I'm looking for mrs. Mac.
Is she in?
- yeah.
I'm a friend of her son's.
I know you, dennis.
Oh.
Oh, my god.
[ groans ]
It's been a long time.
Haven't seen you in a while.
You look different.
I gained a little weight.
Is that what it is?
Looks good on you.
Yeah.
Do you mind if I sit?
[ muttering ]
So. Watching a little tv
outside, huh?
I like the fresh air.
Probably gets
a little lonely though
every once in a while,
Watching tv out here
by yourself.
[ chuckles ]
Every once in a while
you probably want a man, right?
[ exhales ]
someone to fulfill
your desires.
Oh.
Not interested.
Don't fight it, mrs. Mac.
Why don't we go inside
and have a little fun?
Don't find you attractive.
What?
I think you're
an ugly man.
You think I'm ugly?
Yeah.
I'm not ugly.
You're ugly.
Yeah.
Jesus christ.
What is wrong with you, woman?
You're saying that I'm un--
you don't find me attractive?
- no.
- and you're-- what?
Not gonna have sex with me?
No.
This is ridiculous.
I'm-- I'm out of here.
Wait. What--
what just happened?
I think you know exactly
what just happened.
No.
Yeah.
No, come on.
He did not try
to have sex with that woman.
Oh, he did,
'cause he's a dirty,
dirty pervert.
I'm--
I'm so confused right now.
Really?
Are you? I can help you.
Don't trust him.
But--
[ cell phone ringing ]
uh-oh. Excuse me.
I need to get this.
Okay.
Can you pop out
real quick?
[ ringing continues ]
really?
Yeah. It's personal.
You don't want
to be rude, so--
Excuse me.
Oh, my god.
Thanks.
Yeah.
[ charlie ]
how we doin'?
- cat's in the cradle.
- good, good, good.
- time to move to phase two.
- there is no phase two.
I'm not doing phase two.
I did everything you said.
It's over.
This isn't over
until I say it's over!
God. Sorry. Okay.
Relax, dude.
One more phase. That's it.
This is barbara.
Leave a message.
[ beeps ]
hey, uh--
not answering my calls.
I get it. You're busy.
You're busy.
It's a busy time of the week.
Um, listen, I think you should
give me a call back because
I know what you're afraid of.
You think frank and dennis
are gonna find out,
but they're not, okay?
I'm gonna keep my mouth shut
on this one.
And I know that you know
that the sex was good, right?
So I think maybe we should--
[ knocking ]
[ whispering ]
there's somebody at the door.
I'm just gonna ignore it.
I think that maybe
we should get together--
[ pounding ]
Oh, they sound pissed.
All right, listen.
I'll give you a call back.
All right.
- let's go for a ride.
- why?
Grab your coat.
We're goin' for a ride.
- are you going to kill me?
- what?
No. I just wanna go out
and pick up some younger chicks,
And I need a wing man for that.
Come on. Let's roll.
[ disco beat ]
[ frank ] how about the two
out there on the dance floor?
Go on.
Go on, break the ice.
Oh, come on, man.
Come on, man. Go. Go.
All right, all right.
Hey, how ya doin'?
I like your top.
Lookin' good. Mac.
Hi.
Hi. I'm frank.
Wanna get down? Huh?
What happened?
What did you do?
What are you talking
about, what did I do?
What was with that little move?
That move always works
with the ladies.
Frank, you have never gotten
a chick with that move.
What are you talkin' about?
That's how I got my wife.
Really?
Yeah. So don't go
blamin' the move.
The move works.
So, uh, what other kind
of things worked
on your wife?
- she likes money.
- so she likes money
and dancing.
Can we stop talking
about my wife
for a second here?
You're killin' the vibe.
Let me see now.
[ man singing ]
go for it, go for it
over there. Try the move.
You hang over here,
this side, while I--
go
go for it, go for it
hello, hello, hello.
[ chuckles ]
I'm frank. Remember?
go, go for it
go for it
oh
go for it, go for it
ooh
where'd he go? Mac!
[ knocking ]
go away.
We need to talk.
Dee, now's not
a good time.
Charlie is making me
have sex with him
to get out of charlie work.
- what?
- yeah, I know.
Really gross.
Am I the only
one around here
who's not getting laid?
Dennis, charlie is forcing me
to have sex with him.
Mac's getting laid.
You're getting laid.
Now even charlie's getting laid?
This makes me look terrible.
Well, you know what?
This is all charlie's fault.
None of this would be happening
if dad didn't put him
in charge.
You're right.
I'm gonna kill him.
No, no. Whoa.
You ought to do
something worse than that--
something much, much worse.
[ doorbell rings ]
Oh! Hello, dennis.
Hello, mrs. Kelly.
You look wonderful.
Thank you.
Oh. Oh, my!
[ chuckles ]
Well, uh, it's good
to see you, dennis.
What brings you by?
I wanted to bring you
some chocolates.
Thank you.
Do you mind
if I come in?
Okay.
Oh, no.
That son of a bitch.
I know it.
No! No, he said
he loved me.
How dare he do that?
I'm gonna stab him.
Oh.
I'm gonna stab
his face off.
No. No, stabbing's bad.
You need to do
something worse--
Something much,
much worse.
You gotta sleep
with charlie.
[ whining ]
Shh. Shh, shh, shh.
I'm sorry, sweetie.
I just don't find you
sexually attractive.
Are you kidding me?
You don't find me
sexually attractive?
What in the hell is going on?
What is wrong
with you people?
I am sexually a--
I am sexually attractive.
I am an attractive... Man.
[ sobs ]
Bam.
[ sighs ]
what the hell is that?
$443.
Listen, mac, let's just
end this right now.
I only slept with you
to piss frank off.
Afterward I felt like
I was gonna throw up.
So frank makes you
want to throw up?
No. You're not listening.
It's you that makes me
want to throw up.
Oh. So you don't want
to be my girlfriend anymore?
Jesus christ.
Wait a second.
Hold on.
Wait! I'm confused.
So you don't want to be
my girlfriend anymore?
- hey.
- oh, shit!
No, mac, it's okay.
It's all right.
Listen, uh--
okay, let me explain.
Just let me explain.
No, no.
I understand, okay?
You do?
Yeah. Look, I-- I think
I know how you're feeling.
Oh, man.
That is such a relief.
Check this out. I--
[ groans ]
[ both grunting,
groaning ]
You've done well.
Thank you--
And your date
with the waitress
is all set up.
Oh! Mmm!
That is so wonderful.
I have to ask you though--
How did you know that
your mom wasn't gonna
sleep with dennis?
Hmm.
[ laughs ]
Guess I kind of
overlooked that detail.
Okay, time for phase three, dee.
No, charlie.
You said there were
only two phases.
This one's easy.
Okay. Phase three complete.
It looks good?
You look really good.
You sure?
Yes.
You're all done?
I'm all done.
You look great.
Thanks for helping me out.
You're welcome.
The waitress is gonna
be here soon.
I'm gonna go back to
bartending, and you will
go back to handling poo-poo.
Yeah, okay. Phase four--
no! No.
I got a quick phase four.
Charlie--
Let me squeak
a phase four in.
I won't-- you can't--
There's no squeaking
of phase-- no. No.
Okay, fine!
It's over. Okay?
Thank you.
You are hereby released
of all charlie work.
Hey, guys, uh,
can you do me a favor
and not get too drunk?
All right? 'cause I got
some kegs that I need
changing.
Uh, there's, like--
you know what?
- there's some rats
down in the rattraps.
- yeah.
Hello, gang!
You're lookin'
at the new frank.
Ooh!
I've still
got the moves
I've still got what it takes
What the hell is she doing here?
"what the hell
is she doing here?"
really?
Really.
I'll tell you
what I'm doing here.
You wanna know
what I'm doing here,
shit-for-brains?
I had sex with your dad.
That's right,
I had sex with your father,
Because, just like you,
I like my sex old
and ugly.
And with fake hair
on their heads that falls off
when you're having sex with 'em.
It just falls off
because that's what
you do, dennis reynolds.
You like to have sex
with old people.
And you said
that you loved me!
You said, "I love you,"
and so I thought,
"okay, I love you too."
How do you show love?
You go and have sex
with old people.
So that's what I did too!
[ voices speaking backwards ]