_
Come on, this way.
Clear the room.
All clear, nobody's here.
It sounds like it got quiet out there.
Yeah.
Shit! Frank! There's somebody here.
Is anybody here?
Speak up... we will shoot.
Wait, hold your fire, Frank!
It's just a kid.
Hey, boy.
Is that water for us?
Jesus Christ, Frank,
you just killed a kid!
Eh.
Jesus Christ!
Oh, my God.
I'm gonna give him CPR.
Now, is he blowing someone?
What is happening?
- Yeah, looks like it.
- Jesus Christ,
Frank, he was just trying
to give us water, man!
Forget it, he's dead.
You can't go around killing kids!
Think about his mom and his dad.
How long they been playing this for?
Oh, dude...
three straight days.
They've been playing this
- for three days?
- Yeah, absolutely.
Jesus Christ, have they slept?
No. No, they've just been
wandering around the bar,
blowing kids, doing whatever
they're doing, you know?
- Frank, behind you!
- Is this where we're headed?
I mean, as a world? Know what I mean...
as a society?
Hey, uh, have any of you
seen my guy yet?
Oh, what is this, now?
- What? Who?
- Huh?
- What do you want to tell us? Just tell us.
- Oh, I just
totally hooked up with this super hot
stripper soldier last night.
He's swinging by.
- Oh, you're dating a stripper.
- Mm-hmm.
Wow, gross.
Gross? If you guys started
dating a stripper you'd
be bragging about it
for days. I meet myself a Channing Tatum
and suddenly it's gross?
A what... a charming taint man?
What words is she trying to say?
- Uh, she's talking about Channing Tatum.
- Oh.
- He's an actor.
- What do I know him in?
- Well, he-he plays G.I. Joe.
- Oh!
- G.I... Oh, G.I. Joe's the shit.
- G.I. Joe. - Yeah, yeah.
- Well, then say G.I. Joe, don't make up a name.
- All right, you know what,
whatever. It doesn't matter. Anyway,
we had this really amazing connection
and the sex was so meaningful,
both of us wept tears of joy.
- Makes me want to throw up.
- Yeah.
- Just what happened.
- You know what I think is happening
right now? I think the guy's
coming by because you stole his watch.
Oh, right, you jacked
his wallet or something
so he'd come over and you-you...
- Yeah.
- Right? Just to get him to talk to you again.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Hello. Hey.
- Hey, Mike.
Hey. Thanks for calling me.
- Yeah. Thanks for coming by.
- So you have my watch?
- Oh...
- Yeah. Just diving
straight into that, huh?
Listen, um, I'm really glad
you called, though.
I really wanted to thank
you for last night.
Thank you for last night.
Yeah. It's like, we were
having sex and the whole time
- Yeah.
- I was like,
"What's become of me?"
You know,
all I do is I strip all night, I play
video games all day,
I have meaningless sex
with strangers.
My own daughter won't even
talk to me, you know? So I was
like... "Damn."
And I realized I hit rock bottom.
Oh.
And that's why I was crying.
Oh. Right, yeah.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. But don't-don't take it personally.
No. Because it... Why would it be?
- All right, cool.
- It's...
- Yeah, cool.
- Cool, 'cause it really
helped me realize that I got
to give that lifestyle up.
- Oh...
- So thank you.
You're welcome.
Um... I don't remember your name.
Dee.
Dee?
- Yeah.
- Cool.
Now, can I get that watch, or...
- Hey, Dee, I think he just wants his watch.
- I think he needs his...
- Yeah, I understand.
- Yeah.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
- synced and corrected by sot26 -
www.addic7ed.com
Rock bottom? Me?
Uh, hey, buddy, how about when
your daughter stopped talking to you...
Maybe that was your rock bottom, okay?
I'm not rock bottom.
You know what I am? I'm a rock.
Dee is a rock.
In fact, I'm the type of gal
who makes men's lives better.
Hey-o! You guys mind if I shower
in that leaky urinal again?
Well, that... Don't count that.
That's not a good example.
No, I got... I got to do something
about this, goddamn it.
I am gonna fix this problem,
'cause I'm gonna
tell you something right now:
Sweet Dee is a rock.
Goddamn it, Frank, you shot a woman.
- Who cares?
- Jesus Christ, man,
- I got to stop. This is too real.
- What, what?
I got to take a break, dude.
It's driving me insane.
Come on, how are we gonna
win if you keep quitting?
I don't care!
- Lot of storm-outs today, huh?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- This is pathetic.
Dee can't handle a little rejection.
Mac's banged up
over a goddamn video game.
- Yeah.
- It's...
stripper guy is traumatized
because he gets to take his clothes off
in front of a bunch of horny ladies.
- Yeah.
- And then he has sex with one disgusting bird.
- Come on, man,
- that's not trauma. That's not real trauma.
- Nah. It's not even
- that bad.
- I mean, if... if anything,
that's insulting to people
- who have experienced real trauma.
- Yeah.
- I think it is. Yeah.
- I mean, like
you, for instance.
Uh, me?
Well, yeah. Sure, man.
I mean, you grew up fatherless.
You were raised by a woman
who was basically a prostitute.
Well, the father stuff was real.
Yeah, without a doubt.
Got some daddy issues there.
And-and you, too. I mean,
like, you know,
what happened with you...
with Ms. Klinsky, the librarian.
I mean, you were raped.
- Ah. No. St...
- And tha-that's got to affect you.
- That's trauma.
- Will you stop?
Why do you guys br... no.
That wasn't a rape, okay?
- It was.
- That was a mutual... No, stop. Like...
She's an older woman,
you were a younger...
A woman can't rape a guy.
- An older woman can rape a younger...
- It's not...
- Doesn't matter. That's not the point.
- Oh, yeah. Right, right.
- This is separate, yeah.
- Look, it's...
It's not the point. The point is,
yeah, fine, I'll do it.
You'll do what?
I'll strip. Yeah.
Huh. I didn't realize you
were talking about that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Huh.
- You know,
if this Mike fella wants to walk away
from an amazing stripping career,
hey, I'll take up that mantle.
You know, frankly,
I'm a little disappointed
in myself for not thinking of it before.
You know? It just makes sense.
Right, yeah.
Here's the thing, man.
I can't do it without you.
I need you to get my back.
Oh, uh, you want me to strip with you?
Oh, oh, no, no, no, no, no.
I-I-I... no, I just literally
need you to have a look at my back,
you know,
make sure there's no moles
or, like, unsightly hairs,
bumps, zits, you know,
- that kind of thing.
- Ah, yeah...
And then, you know, get after it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'll clean you up.
All right, all right, I can do that.
- Cool.
- Cool, man. You be my boy?
Yeah, I'll be the boy.
Well, just be my... L-like my bag boy.
You know, carry around my-my lotions,
my oils, my scents, my razors.
Cool, man. Chill, chill.
Yeah, that's cool, right?
- Yeah, that's cool, bro. Cool.
- Cool.
_
Frank, where are you, man?
I can't see.
Jesus Christ.
Oh, who's there?! Oh...
Hey, boy.
How you doing, man?
No! Baba!
_
Mother!
Oh, shit!
Oh, no, man!
I'm so sorry, man.
Hey, son.
Dad?! What are you doing here?
How did you get in the game?
Guess we...
won't be having that catch
after all.
You were gonna have a catch with me?
I was, but...
you killed me, son.
I... love...
Wa-Wa... Wait! Wait, Dad!
Who do you love?
Dad, who do you love? Wait.
Dad, who do you love? No, Dad! No!
What the hell?
Oh, was that a dream?
Dennis?
Oh, my God, man,
I just had the weirdest dream.
- What?
- Frank.
Look, I-I... I can't sleep.
I'm having nightmares.
- Dead kids, dads.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, Mac.
Slow down. What are you saying?
I got to quit the game, dude. I can't
- do this anymore.
- No, no, no.
Don't quit just yet.
- Look, have a drink and calm down.
- Okay, fine.
I'll calm down. I'll-I'll
drink some whiskey or something.
Yeah, stuff it down with brown.
That's the best way to deal with things.
Okay.
Kid's a mess.
Goddamn it, Charlie,
we're 30 minutes late, man.
I'm so sorry I cut your
back so many times, man.
- What happened?
- I was nervous, dude.
- Why?
- I've never, like, cut such a muscular back.
- Thanks, man.
- Yeah. Oh, dude, your back looks great, man.
I'm working hard, dude.
Dude, you're putting the work in,
and it's showing, man.
- Thank you so much, man. I really appreciate that.
- Yeah, right, right, right, right.
But just let's not
talk about it in there.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Don't bring it up.
Can you walk me through
what your guy is again?
Okay, so here's the deal, man.
Who do girls want to have sex
with more than anybody else?
- Jugglers.
- Jug...?
- Dudes who can, like, juggle things.
- I know what a juggler is.
- You know, with the fire sticks and the balls.
- Yeah.
No, they don't want to
have sex with a juggler.
They want to have sex with their dads.
- Weird.
- Yeah, it is weird, so I'm a dad.
Oh. Okay, cool. Oh, and I'm your boy.
- All right, that works.
- Well, no. What? Why would you be my boy?
Oh, you said I was gonna be your boy
'cause I have daddy trauma,
and then, I didn't realize
I was gonna be your boy
in there, but that works great.
No, that doesn't make any sense.
How would you be my s...?
I'm their dad.
How could I also be your dad?
We can't all be related. Christ, Charlie,
you're not making any sense, man.
Yeah, I mean,
you could have a lot of kids, I guess.
I got to say, though,
I'm looking inside there,
and this isn't making sense to me.
I mean, these are all older women.
Might be
a little bit hard for me to
pull off the dad thing at all.
- That's not a good play.
- You know,
I'm getting a bad feeling
about this, man.
Hey, man, do you think
maybe that's 'cause
- of your librarian trauma?
- You're talking about Ms. Klinsky?
- Yeah, she was an older woman, and...
- What? No. There was...
Let's not talk...
Can we stop talking about trauma
- and-and-and cuts on the... on peoples' backs?
- Yes.
And let's... It's not sexy, okay?
- Okay, yeah, well, then let's split.
- Okay.
- All right, let's go.
- All right, man.
Are you the stripper?
- Oh, uh, yeah, that's him.
- Uh...
- What, are you 40?
- Yup.
Fine. You guys'll do, I guess.
Y-You guys? No. Sorry. I'm just the boy.
- The what? - Just...
- Sorry. I'm-I'm his boy.
Well, you're not my boy.
He's not...
Are you gonna stand out here
and talk like little bitches,
or are you gonna come inside and
take your dicks out for money?
Daddy?
Just don't call me Daddy.
Yeah, my generation...
we drank our problems away.
But since you softies like
to talk about everything,
I figured this was a good thing to do.
A PTSD support group, Frank?
Yeah, yeah. Maybe you'll get some help,
- we can finish the damn game.
- What's up, dicks?
What the hell are you doing here?
Well, because I am a rock and
not a rock bottom, I decided
to reach out to Mike and see
if I could get him some help
with, uh, some of these issues
he's been having.
I'm confused.
Is this a PTSD meeting for vets?
Mm-hmm, yeah.
You're a military guy, right?
No. It was just my stripper character.
Really? Oh, I just figured you based
- your characters off past experiences.
- Why?
Okay, look, I-I'm not gonna
pass myself off as a vet, Frank.
- Yeah, I don't feel good about this. Maybe...
- Well, then just don't talk.
- But...
- You don't have to talk. Just sit down.
Okay, everybody, let's grab a chair,
let's get this started.
- Probably not gonna call on you anyway.
- Okay, right off
the bat, I can see we got some newcomers
here today. You guys
want to introduce yourselves?
Ugh. Goddamn it.
Uh, I'm Frank.
I've been around the block,
seen some action.
I was in 'Nam for a while.
Private sector mostly.
I did shoot a couple of dinks
who tried to jack some
sneakers off the factory floor.
No big deal.
I don't feel nothing about it.
I'm just here to support my buddy.
Uh...
Hello. I'm Dee. I'm a rock.
I'm here with this guy.
There was a bit of a mix-up
about his military credentials,
but, uh... whatever.
Now he's under the delusion
that he's hit rock bottom,
you know, and I just don't see
how that's possibly true, so,
we're gonna straighten
that up while we're
sitting here today, you know.
Mac's being a pussy!
He doesn't want to fight anymore!
I'm not being a pussy.
I just don't want to
kill women and children.
How do I get him
to stop thinking of them as real people?
Mike's embarrassed about his dancing,
and I just... I don't get that.
I don't... How is that
rock bottom behavior?
You know? Think of Channing Tatum.
Can you please explain
Channing Tatum to him?
- I'm not sure I follow...
- Oh, yeah. He's G.I. Joe.
Mac can't sleep at night.
He's having erotic nightmares and shit.
- He doesn't know what's real anymore.
- Yeah.
Mike's embarrassed about his
video game-playing, which makes
no sense to me, 'cause you know what?
Video games are hard.
- You ever play Fallujah?
- Beat it five times.
- You want to play with me?
- I'm actually trying to get away from that.
Well, what if he paid you?
Ten bucks an hour.
- 20.
- Deal.
- Wow. Really?
- Well, will you look at that?
Now we're getting somewhere, huh?
- Yeah.
- That couldn't have happened
without your rock, could it?
Wait a second, Frank. What about me?
You're out. Dishonorable discharge.
I'm sorry.
What is happening here?
Doesn't matter. We're done with you.
- Yeah, we're good.
- Yeah.
- Hey, son.
- Dad?!
What are you doing here?
I broke out of jail and
came straight to see you.
- Because you love me?
- 'Cause I'm gonna kill you, son.
Oh. Oh, no!
What...? What-What's happening?
When did I get here?
How long have I been asleep?
You got here, like, five minutes ago.
You've been asleep for 35 seconds.
Oh, Jesus Christ,
I'm-I'm losing my mind.
- I mean, I'm actually going insane.
- You know,
we're all having a little
bit of a hard time right now.
- Yeah.
- But we got to fight fire with fire,
and Charlie and I refuse
to be defeated by this.
We're gonna win this war.
What war?
- The war on women!
- Women, man!
There's a war on women?
Can I get in on that?
Bro, it's been raging
since the beginning of time, bro.
- Oh.
- And we're losing ground.
Phone!
- Hello.
- Ah, yeah.
Uh, yeah, is youse Daddy and the Boy?
- Uh, y-yes, it is. Boy speaking.
- Oh.
Yeah. Uh, I hear
youse are re... rule good.
Well, yeah, that-that is true.
Well, I've got a party for you.
- Um, Daddy wants to speak with you.
- Yeah.
Yeah, this is Daddy.
What's-what's the gig?
Uh, yeah, a giant party.
Tons of sorority girls.
Sorority girls.
Oh, sorority girls. Nice.
Did you just lick your hand?
Yeah, that...
that sounds good. Um, listen,
a few new ground rules, though.
I'm a bad dad now. And, uh,
the Boy's also gonna be dancing with me.
Okay. Uh, whatever. Uh, uh...
Yeah, we need Mike. We need him.
- Mike? Why do you want Mike, Dee?
- What? You knew it was me?
Of course I knew it was you.
Who else does accents so poorly?
The accents were terrible.
- The accents were terrible.
- All right, look, I just...
I want him to have fun,
make a ton of money,
party with a bunch of sorority girls,
you know?
I need to show him that
this is a great life.
This is not a rock-bottom life.
We'll do it at Paddy's.
It'll be a win-win.
- Make a ton of mon...
- Mmm.
Yes. Okay.
What? Hello?
Goddamn it.
This is good.
This is... th-this is good.
Young girl sorority girls.
It's, like, age-appropriate for me,
you know? Not like
those perverted librarians.
- Cougars. Whatever, man.
- Yeah.
And it's gonna be on our home turf.
Like, Paddy's.
- Whoa. And with Mike, we'll be like a...
- Oh.
We'll be like an elite stripping
dance force, like a unit, man.
Dude, dude, dude, dude,
- we're gonna look good, man.
- Yeah. Yeah, man.
We're gonna win this war.
- Oh, hell yeah. Oh, yeah.
- We're gonna win this war on women.
You know what, Mac,
maybe we could use you after all.
- He's asleep.
- Yeah, he's out.
_
It's amazing!
I can't believe they have zombies
on the final level!
I love zombies.
Ghouls, too. I love ghouls.
Right now, if we can just
make it to that second box
over there,
we can grab the all spark coin
and we can win the game.
Frank. Frank.
Frank!
Oh. What happened?
- Where am I?
- Oh, you're in the back office.
You passed out playing the game, dude.
We dragged you back here
so you could sleep.
Oh, Mac. I think I was too hard on you.
I think I got PTSD, too.
- Oh, no. We don't have that.
- Huh?
Yeah, I actually slept about
ten hours last night, dude,
and I feel great.
I think we were just suffering
from sleep deprivation.
Well, where's Mike?
I want to finish the game.
Oh, we finished the game.
Yeah, like, right after
you passed out,
Mike and I just got in there.
- Dude, it was awesome.
- Do you want to do it again?
No, I don't want to play anymore.
Well, where's Mike? I'll do it with him.
He's out, too. Yeah, he's doing
some weird stripping thing
with Dennis and Charlie.
I only woke you up
'cause I figured you'd want to see it.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I really appreciate you getting me
this gig. I mean, truthfully,
I don't think I was ready
to give this lifestyle up.
Of course not. Why would you?
You're really good
at dancing.
That's nothing to be ashamed of.
Listen, you like video games?
I got you paid for it.
You're a great stripper?
I got you this gig.
- And you know what I'm gonna do for you next?
- What?
I'm gonna reunite you
with your daughter.
- Oh, man.
- Yep.
Look, I really appreciate
everything you've done.
- It really, really means a lot to me.
- Eh, well,
you just needed your rock.
Fire it up.
- Smell good? Everything poppin'?
- All right. No, feels good.
- Look good?
- I don't know. What do you think?
- You like how it smells?
- It looks good.
- And you can't see any of the blood.
- Okay, good.
It's all patched up good.
- What do you think about my prop, hmm?
- That's really cool.
- A little kid licking that up there.
- Wait, what-what am I smelling?
Cheese.
- Is that made of cheese?
- Yeah, yeah.
And then I painted the rest with,
like, magic marker and stuff.
Oh, Christ. Why did you make
a cheese lollipop? It stinks.
- For-for my nerves. Yeah.
- That smells horrible.
Oh, God. There's nothing sexy
about cheese. Put it away.
Ladies, are we ready
to party tonight?
So am I.
All right.
We're gonna see some skin
tonight. Yeah.
Scars and all.
This, actually, is a real scar, too.
And I got a good story behind that.
This is, uh...
They took out the kidney, actually,
from the fron... A Chinaman.
And he did not know
how to do it, I'll tell you that much.
Cricket was a bad idea, huh?
Yeah, I know.
But we needed that, like, you know,
- McConaughey emcee-type.
- Yeah. But looks like we got
AIDS Dallas Buyers Club McConaughey,
- not Magic Mike McConaughey.
- That is what he looks like.
- It's a good crowd, though. It's a good crowd.
- He's... Yeah.
All right, well...
That was the first time
that I really thought,
"Hey, I might actually, uh...
I might die, and...
and no one's gonna remember."
All right! Hey!
Let's, uh, keep it movin'.
Keepin' it real, keepin' it sexy,
and takin' back the power,
let's give it up for Daddy and the Boy!
Hey, Boy, let's have a catch.
Over here, Pop.
Hey. Good throw, son.
I love you, Dad!
- I love you, too, son.
- Oh?
And even though I never
even said it enough.
What is this?
I wasn't a good... Shh!
I wasn't a good father to you,
and-and I regret that now.
No, that's fine, because now
is our chance to connect.
This is super weird.
Hey! Shush, all right?
This is our thing.
We have the power. You don't talk.
All right, you know what,
Dad, don't listen to them,
'cause we're gonna win this war.
This is not sexy!
Just take something off!
You know, you take something off!
All right, look,
it's too hot for baseball.
I'm gonna take my clothes off now.
I think.
- Okay!
- Yeah, now we'll take our clothes off.
Yeah!
Wait, wait, son, don't.
Don't. They're laughing.
Don't take your clothes off if
they're laughing. We have the power.
- It's not a joke!
- It's not a joke, all right? This is sexy.
Oh, stop, sto... Oh, you know what?
You might want to check your programs
'cause I'm bad dad now.
I'll take you to your goddamn room.
- I'll bend you over my knee.
- Take your dicks out!
All right, listen to me. This is it,
this is what you were made for.
Now you get out there
and save the day, soldier.
This is about a father and a son
- whose relation...
- Oh, come on!
And now the moment
you've all been waiting for.
Soldier boy, Mike.
♪ Everybody got 'em,
everybody got 'em ♪
♪ E-E-Everybody got 'em,
e-e-everybody, everybody ♪
♪ Everybody got 'em,
everybody got 'em ♪
♪ E-E-Everybody got 'em ♪
♪ E-E-Everybody, everybody ♪
♪ Everybody got 'em,
everybody got 'em ♪
♪ E-E-Everybody got 'em,
e-e-everybody, everybody ♪
♪ Everybody got 'em,
everybody got 'em ♪
♪ E-E-Everybody, every... ♪
- Dad?
- Oh, Janie?
- Oh!
- Your cock was in my face!
Oh, God, I didn't mean to!
I didn't mean to!
You're disgusting!
My finger touched your asshole!
Never talk to me again!
I got you!
I got you. I'm your rock bottom?
I'm your rock...
That's your rock bottom,
sticking your dick in your
daughter's face, you son of a bitch.
- Why would you do that?!
- Get out of here!
That's my daughter!
Oh.
Yes!
- Wow.
- Jesus Christ.
- Wow, Dee, that was dark.
- That's like the darkest thing you've ever done.
You know what that was?
- That was your rock bottom.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. - Hmm.
- Whatever.
Feel good.
I don't want to talk about it.
I don't want to talk about my thing.
You want to talk about your thing?
- No, no, let's not.
- You know what we should do?
Let's just, uh... let's just get drunk.
- Yeah, come on.
- Let's not talk about trauma.
- Or deal with any of that shit.
- Woo.
Let's just have a good
time and get drunk, huh?
Stuff it down with some brown.