Come on, hurry up, guys.
I want to get a good seat.
What do you mean you want to get...
Charlie, this is
a sexual harassment seminar.
There are no "good seats."
Where are you going?
- Up front.
- This is so unfair.
I mean, I'm not saying it
doesn't happen to, like,
loads of women all the time,
but I don't harass anybody,
so why am I here?
Because some Internet
warrior put Paddy's on a list
of unsafe places for women
and we can't have that, okay?
- Not in this climate.
- Right.
Ugh! You kids and your climates.
Back in the day,
I banged all my secretaries.
- Frank.
- That's the way you did it.
You hire some girl with no experience,
you bang her, you promote her.
It's a win-win situation for everybody,
except for the wives.
Frank, modulate your volume, okay?
This is serious, okay?
The future of Paddy's depends
on us completing this seminar.
You guys should be really worried.
I'm not worried about anything, man.
If anyone should be
worried about weird shit with women,
it's you, bro.
The only reason we're here
is because you DENNIS'd someone probably
and she put us on the list.
We're only here 'cause of you.
Yeah, you perv. You happy now?
- You happy?
- Happy?
You guys, this isn't about me.
I don't know if you noticed,
but women are on a little
bit of a rampage right now
and anyone could be
taken down at any moment,
so, you know, no,
I'm not happy right now.
Who could possibly be happy right now?
Hey-o!
Who's ready to party?!
♪ Time's up, time's up, time's up ♪
♪ Time's up, time's up, time's up. ♪
_
Hello. I'm Kate.
And I want to begin today
by addressing the reason
that we're all here, the so-called
"Shitty Bar List"
of unsafe places for women.
Ah, yes. Uh, just a quick question.
How many points do we need?
I'm sorry, points?
Yeah, how many points
do we need to score
to get our name taken off the list?
Oh. No, there's no points.
Everything is graded by points, right?
I mean, otherwise, how could the Eagles
have won the Super Bowl, right?
All you have to do is
complete the seminar
and then your bar will have
its name removed from the list.
- There you go. Simple.
- Yeah, but our-our name
shouldn't even be
on that list 'cause, like,
we don't really have any history
of misbehavior at Paddy's Pub.
Well, I'm sure a lot of people
here today feel that way,
but I encourage you
to keep your minds open...
And your dicks in your pants.
Ma'am, that kind
of language is inappropriate
in a professional setting.
That's one of the things that
you'll learn in the seminar.
Uh, yes? Do you have a question?
Statute of limitations.
Okay. I'm just trying to get
through the introduction here,
but since you asked,
the federal law is 300 days
from the last act,
depending on the state and...
Sir, are you leaving?
- Frank!
- What?
They got nothing on me past '92, tops.
Hold on a second there.
Uh, pardon me, Kate, but, um,
aren't some states considering
doing away with the statute
of limitations altogether?
Some states like, uh, Nevada?
Yes, that's right.
Can they do that?
It's possible. Yes.
Nevada, huh?
Ah, it's getting warm in here.
Uh, got to make some calls. Shit.
You can continue now.
I promise you there will be
no further interruptions.
Right. We're gonna jump
right into the group work.
Half of you are gonna go with me
and the rest will be led
by my associate Alan.
Hello, everyone. I'm Alan.
Oh! Here comes the boss man.
- Finally, a dude.
- Yeah.
Yeah, okay, cool. He's in charge.
Uh, ma'am?
Could we go with Alan, please?
Actually, I think
we should split your group up.
That's, uh, that's gonna be
a lot harder for me
- to keep tabs on you guys.
- Don't worry, Dennis.
I'm gonna make you so proud.
I'm gonna work really hard
and get all the points and...
What is with you and the points?
There are no points.
We established that.
Well, that's how the Eagles
won the Super Bowl.
I know that's how the Eagles won the...
but this isn't the Eagles. Okay?
- This is a seminar.
- Go Birds, though.
- Oh, go Birds, go Birds.
- All right, fine, go Birds. Yes.
I know. Go Birds.
Get your hand off my knee.
Look, just sit here and do nothing.
So, in this room
we're going to be
talking about harassment
in the workplace.
And thank you to Elliot who's
agreed to play our boss.
I'll just need another
volunteer from the group.
- Oh! Oh! Alan!
- Alan! Alan! Alan!
- I'll do it.
- Uh, so, uh... - Alan! Alan!
Sir, would you mind
just jumping in for me?
Thank you.
Um, great. So just read from the script
and I'll jump in as and when.
"Good morning, boss."
"Hello, Johnson.
Have that report on my desk by 5:00.
- "Hey, did you see the boobs on that new intern?"
- And stop.
Now, can anyone tell me what
the boss did wrong there?
Yeah. He mumbled his lines.
I didn't believe a word
out of his mouth.
Uh, no, sorry. I mean in the scenario.
- He-he used vulgar language.
- That is correct.
B-But she didn't hear it.
This is just locker
room talk between guys.
Now, that's actually a
common misconception, okay?
Lewd comments can be
a form of harassment
even if directed to a third party.
But it's not for her. It's about her.
No, sorry. It's-it's actually,
it's the employee who's
talking to the boss
that is the one that was offended.
- What? Why?
- No, no, no, the employee
- would find it hilarious.
- Yeah.
I mean, not this guy
'cause the boss sucks at telling jokes.
Well, also, we really don't
know how funny the joke is yet
'cause we haven't seen the girl's boobs.
Can we see them?
Okay. Uh, let's... let's switch gears.
Maybe try a different scenario.
Thanks, gents.
Just, uh, uh, take a seat.
Um, so, uh, Mac,
what is it that you do at the bar?
- I am the head of security at Paddy's Pub.
- He's our doorman.
- No, he's just like our gay guy now.
- No, well...
Great. So, you check IDs.
That-that sort of thing.
- He should.
- Not once has he ever checked an ID.
- It's one aspect of the job.
- Yeah, he should.
Why don't you, why don't you hop
up here and we'll do a little scenario
that-that might be a
little more familiar to you.
- You are very tall.
- Yes, I am.
Now, should I take my
shirt off for the scenario?
Because I feel like
standing next to you,
they're not gonna be as intimidated,
but if I were to take my shirt off,
they would be intimidated.
I'm not in the scenario.
- We're good. We're good.
- Yeah, we're okay.
- We get it. We get it.
- That's him doing his gay guy thing.
So, uh, can we also
get a female customer?
- Ooh, yeah.
- A volunteer?
I will be the young, female customer.
"Young, female customer."
Great, good. Yes.
Okay. Well, um, just, uh,
do your job as you would normally
and I will, um, you know, jump in
if you cross over into any gray areas.
Okay. So what's my character?
Uh, you're just trying
to get into the bar.
Yeah, but why?
To get a drink, I suppose.
Why? I just drank
three beers on the way over.
You don't show up at a bar sober.
What a waste of money.
What are you gonna...
Just you're trying to get into the bar.
- I'm here for revenge.
- Okay. Sure.
Alan, what's my character again?
- You're the doorman.
- Right.
And how many drinks
have I had at this point?
You are... you're not in the scenario.
- I've had five.
- Okay. Marvelous.
Let's, uh, let's begin
whenever you're ready.
Excuse me, sir, have you...
- Whoa!
- Wow.
Jesus Christ.
Why did you do that?
Oh, well, well, she came at me,
- and it was sort of my instinct.
- That was amazing.
- That was great, right?
- You got me, like, a foot off the ground.
- A-Are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah. No, it doesn't hurt.
Did it-did it make you feel humiliated?
Did it make you-make you feel small?
That's what it is,
it made me feel teeny-tiny.
- Like Thumbelina.
- That's what I was going for. Thumbelina!
- That's the highest I've ever gotten.
- He's never gotten me that high before.
You're lucky I haven't
called the police.
Why-why would you call the police?
Oh, wait. H-Hold on.
Is that sexual harassment?
No, that is sexual assault.
- Really?
- Assault?
No. Dee, Dee. I did not assault you.
Please tell Alan that
I did not assault you.
Well, now that I've gotten a
little distance from the event.
Wha... No, Alan,
we do this kind of stuff all the time.
W-Charlie, would you tell him?
- He's gone.
- You do this all the time?
Y-You've got a big problem, all right?
She could press charges.
- Could I?
- No.
No! Dee. No.
- He just said I could, so...
- Oh, God.
It just, i-it...
did somebody turn up the heat?
Yeah, you sweating?
You sweating a little bit, Ronald?
- Yeah?
- No, it's just the climate.
The term "sexual harassment,"
it wasn't coined until 1975,
- by a woman named Carmita Wood.
- Carmita Wood. Oh. I'm sorry.
- Sorry.
- You really know your history.
- Well, this is important stuff.
- Oh, please.
- God, get lost, Dee.
- No way, I'm on a roll.
- So who could tell me...
Hey.
Is it sexual harassment when a man
constantly calls his
female coworker a bird?
That depends.
Is that a sexual innuendo of some kind?
Just a big dumb flightless bird.
Well, it's not very nice,
but it's not sexual harassment.
Nice try, you dumb bitch.
Um, Kate, if I may, yeah.
Um, federal law really only recognizes
two types of sexual harassment:
quid pro quo and hostile
work environment.
That is very good, Dennis.
- Thank you.
- No, no, don't do that.
This man is a monster. Believe you, me.
- What?
- He is the worst person I know.
Got to protect me on this, Larry.
I... start with the secretaries.
Oh, Jesus Christ, Frank. Pants.
I was sweating through my clothes.
It's this damn climate.
Sir, that robe is inappropriate.
- And I don't think...
- Hon, I'm on the phone, you see?
I don't know.
I bought her a Camaro. No...
You know I don't go Chinese.
I don't know why, I just don't.
Korean?
Oh, put her on the list.
I really did a number on her.
Yeah...
Why don't we take a break?
Got to get your shit together, Frank.
- You...
- Oh, I wish I was dead.
These vultures are
picking my carcass clean.
Whoa, Frank. Hey, stop talking.
- Where'd you get that robe?
- Upstairs.
I got to get one of them, man. Nice.
Whoa. Wait, Jesus, Mac.
What the hell happened to you?
I'm gonna be honest. The
first half has not gone well.
- You got exposed, too?
- Oh, yeah, he did. Big time.
He did a role-play thing, it went bad.
Wait, role-playing thing?
Y-You were supposed to do nothing.
I mean, n-now you're all
sweaty and twitchy?
Well, it's-it's so hot in here.
I mean, I feel like
they crank up the heat.
Oh, they cranked it up. I'm roasting.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Which one of you just grabbed my ass?
Did you see that? Did you see...
T-that is a problem for us.
T-Their powers are growing. Okay?
Now, we got to start taking
this more seriously, okay?
Can you guys just go back in
there and do nothing, okay?
Just don't say or do anything.
Can anyone tell me
the two types of sexual harassment?
Oh. Oh, oh.
Uh, uh, flirting and groping.
No! Uh, groping and-and dick pics.
Yeah, I-I know that sending
dick pics is one of them.
You're kidding. Christ.
- I got to shoot some texts.
- Actually,
it's quid pro quo and
hostile work environment.
Would you please stop interrupting me?
- Ooh, ooh, burn.
- Please... And you.
Could you please sit down?
No, it's cool. I'm on your side.
There are no sides.
Shit, I just looked at her tits.
- Frank! Don't tell her that.
- Okay, don't panic.
A passing glance is
not sexual harassment.
Oh. I like your tactic here.
Get them all horny with your titties.
That's when they make their mistakes.
Ma'am, that's victim blaming.
No, I'm blaming Frank.
He's been staring at your boobs
this whole time. Still doing it.
Frank!
What? I'm not allowed
to like things anymore?
- It's a compliment.
- How is that a compliment?
Well, they're not that great.
Make her feel good.
- Hey, hey, hey. Don't let them get to you.
- Okay...
Okay? Your tits are fine.
Okay, everybody,
if, uh, you could take a seat, please.
So now what we're gonna do is, uh,
imagine a-a hypothetical scenario,
uh, based right here in Philadelphia.
So, uh, i-imagine a-a woman,
we'll call her "the waitress,"
who works at a local coffee shop.
Now, i-in this particular instance,
this waitress
is being harassed by
one of her customers.
He's following her home from work, uh,
digging through her trash
and calling her repeatedly,
until she complains
to her boss about it.
Now, the boss does nothing.
Can anyone tell me who's
legally at fault here?
Ooh. Wow, what do you think, Charlie?
I-I think The Waitress is.
Y-You know, 'cause,
for-she doesn't realize
that, like, true love
is in front of her stupid face.
- Well...
- Why would she say that's an assault?
Hold on a second.
Now, this is just a-this is just
a hypothetical, uh,
scenario that he's painting.
He's not getting
the whole big picture, right?
- Well, of course, it's a hypothetical.
- I know, but maybe
she, like, only thought like she
wasn't into him, but then, like,
15 years later,
when she needed a baby, like,
really bad,
and she'd been in and out of, like,
- a women's shelter, he banged her.
- Sorry.
That-that doesn't mean that
the customer didn't harass.
All right, well then,
I think all of the customers' friends
harassed her, too,
because they all banged her.
- I mean, he did.
- That's true.
Oh, well, don't bring me into th...
This is a hypothetical scenario.
I'm not involved.
- Neither are you.
- She also did hand stuff to Mac.
She did. I-It wasn't very good, though.
All right, look, are you trying
to tell me that no matter what,
it's always just gonna
be the customer's fault?
It is, in fact, the boss's fault.
The boss.
Well, that makes sense.
I always hated Seth.
- He's a real creep.
- Well, you don't know his name
because this is hypothetical,
and he didn't say t-that...
Well, it doesn't matter anyway,
'cause she just said
what I-what I did to
her wasn't harassment
because Seth did it to her.
Sorry. I...
Can I just make this very clear?
Okay? What the customer did
was harassment.
- Right.
- Yes. If it were you.
And so, take in the information,
but don't take it personally.
Uh, yeah, technically, don't,
like, I get, like, a free pass
and stuff, 'cause I mean,
I was molested.
Ah... W-Well, now,
actually, that is true.
He did get molested by his uncle Jack.
His-his uncle Jack got
to him pretty good.
- No, Uncle Jack never molested me.
- Oh.
- I dodged him.
- Oh, no, he got you. He got you.
- He got you big time.
- You weren't there.
- You wrote a whole play about it.
- Yeah, you did write a play.
- I got molested by Dee.
- What?
What? Oh, c-that's ludicrous.
No, it's true. Like, a couple years ago,
she banged me,
and I didn't want to do it.
- There you go.
- Wait, wait. You had sex with Charlie?
- Oh, God.
- You had sex with Dee?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, yeah.
We, okay, it was a mistake.
- Yeah, I'll say.
- I-It... I regret every second of it,
- but it was consensual.
- It was not!
I totally wanted her to stop, and, like,
I was very intimidated
by her larger frame.
- Oh, yeah, I can see that. Yeah.
- So, you know.
I have a petite frame. I...
i-it's a Thumbelina frame.
- I don't... Not to me.
- Y-You didn't tell me to stop.
Yeah, and I kept saying...
And you're like, "Shut up!
Stop talking! Be still.
"Let me do my thing.
I can't, I can't get off
with you moving and talking and shit."
Oh, shit. Yup. That's ringing a bell.
- Jesus, Dee. Ugh, God.
- All right, but yeah.
Either way, It does...
I can't molest you, you know?
It doesn't work that way
'cause I'm a woman and you're the man.
Right, right? Back me up, girlfriend.
Actually, a woman can sexually
harass and even rape a man.
Is that what happened here?
Actually, maybe.
No, no, no, no. You don't,
you don't just throw around
the-the "R" word, Kate. It's hot, right?
Yello?
What? Then find her through
the abortion records.
Can the group from Paddy's
Pub please focus up.
You guys have been very disruptive.
Well, maybe
you should explain it more better
because I'm totally confused about...
Maybe if you stopped interrupting.
Maybe if you two stopped
sucking a fat dick.
- You do suck a fat dick.
- You've sucked a dick through this process.
What? Are you kidding me?
After all of this,
I ended up firing her?
Oh, my God.
Hey, Larry?
How soon can you get to the Hyatt?
My dong fell out. Some woman saw it.
Well, goddamn it.
All right, calm down, calm down.
Everybody take it easy,
everybody take a deep breath.
You know, we're gonna get through this.
I think, look, Kate,
you two are clearly a little
in over your heads here.
Right? Yeah.
You're never gonna be able to rein in
this particular group,
so I tell you what.
I have some experience running, uh,
little educational seminars like this,
so why don't I take
over for a little bit.
You guys, scoot.
All right? On your bikes.
- Here's a statistic for you:
- _
100% of men are capable
of being sexual harassers.
And 100% of women
are capable of being sexually harassed.
Now, am I saying that all men
are sexual harassers?
No, no, no, no. No, no.
Of course not. No. Absolutely not. No.
Yes, some men are, uh, well,
they're-they're sexual harassers,
but they don't represent all men,
you know,
just like all women aren't represented
by a few bad ones, you know.
Women like, uh...
You know, and of course...
And then we got...
Point is,
that gender really doesn't
have anything to do with it.
There's really only one
thing that determines
whether a person will be
accused of sexual harassment,
and that is...
ugliness.
Let me explain.
Now, see, here's a,
here's a graph of ugliness
as it relates to time.
Now you see how the,
how the arrow plunges
pretty steeply downward as
your ugliness increases.
Now I want you to
imagine a scenario for me
where this man walks into work one day,
sees a woman, and says,
"I like your dress."
Oh. Mildly sexual,
but innocuous enough, yeah.
Now imagine the same
sentence spoken by this man.
Yeah.
Suddenly, you're very uncomfortable.
We're all uncomfortable
just looking at him now.
Because he's gross, he's ugly,
he's a little bit of a monster.
Now is it this man's fault
that he looks this way?
No. He was, he was born this way,
but the point is,
I know it's not my fault, you know.
Is it your fault? I don't think so.
It's certainly not the woman's fault,
you know?
The point is, know your place,
monster man. Your time's up.
Yeah, I know what you're thinking.
You're thinking,
"How do I know if I'm ugly?
Well, if you're not sure,
probably best to assume that you are.
Everyone in this room is.
I-I did a scan.
Now here's the part where you say,
"But, Dennis, I can't be ugly,
I'm rich."
And, yes, money can offset
and reduce ugliness,
but it actually increases your risk.
You see, a construction worker,
he can can catcall women
all day long, right?
And he gets away with it
'cause nobody gives a shit,
but a rich guy...
A rich guy's fun to take down.
Time's up.
"But, Dennis," you're saying,
"I can't be ugly, and-and it
doesn't matter because I'm gay."
Well, guess what, pal?
You-you are ugly,
and it doesn't matter how much
you work out.
It's never gonna change that fact.
You've also objectified tons of men,
including me.
You know,
you got to stop kissing me, man.
I don't want it.
I don't want you touching me at all.
Okay, it's never gonna happen.
All right?
Not willingly. Your time's up.
"But, Dennis, I can't be ugly.
I'm a hopeless romantic."
But no, you're-you're not.
Okay, you're-you're a sad,
pathetic wretch of a man,
so desperate to be loved
that you'll actually go rifling
through somebody's garbage.
And there's nothing...
nothing more unattractive
than desperation.
To... No, not him.
No, talking about you. No.
Not him, either. Yeah, I am talking
about you. You know what,
never mind. Your time's up.
"But Dennis...
I-I... see, I can't be ugly, all right?
I'm a woman."
Well, no, women can be ugly,
and you are one of them.
One of the ugly ones.
You're lanky, and your hair's...
well, it looks like a wig.
Yeah. What's going on?
Is it a wig? Doesn't matter.
Your time's up.
But guys,
I got some good news for you.
Okay? It's not a crime to be ugly.
But you can't be ugly
and sloppy.
So, take me, for example.
I'm neither. Yeah, you see that?
That is 11% body fat.
Now, the only place you're gonna...
- What year was that photo taken?
- No, no, no.
Not taking questions right now, Mac.
So just... Yeah.
Point is, I keep my body tight.
But I also keep my life tight.
I got the tapes. I got the receipts.
They're all time-stamped and coded.
After every encounter, I received a text
confirming each partner's
consent and enjoyment.
Now, you may ask, "Well...
would a woman really-really
text that, Dennis?"
Their phones did.
- _
I got the documents to prove it,
so don't try coming at me.
But some of you...
you just haven't been careful enough.
So you're asking yourself,
"What can I do to save myself now?"
You got to clean up your act.
Otherwise, you're going down,
and you're gonna take me down with you,
and I ain't going down.
You understand?
I've been telling you this for years,
but you refused to listen.
And so that's why I had to
find a way to make you listen,
which is why I created
the Shitty Bar List.
What?
That's right.
I made the spreadsheet,
I posted it online,
and I even hired these two
bozos to host the seminar.
Wait, you hired us?
You're a monster.
Oh, yeah? Prove it.
Oh, wow! I feel like we should clap.
- Yeah.
- That was pretty good.
- That was awesome.
Yeah. I'm gonna be honest,
I didn't follow most of it,
- but so cool, man.
- Yeah.
Pretty drastic move
to publicly expose us,
but I see why you did it.
Yeah, but it's true.
I mean, women are out to get us.
Well, well, no, no. Women are right.
I mean, men are monsters.
We're constantly harassing them.
I'm just saying we need
to be more careful
so we don't get accused.
And we should probably
stop harassing them.
Uh, well, you know, I don't know.
One step at a time.
We don't want the whole
system to collapse,
- you know what I mean?
- Ease-ease into it.
- It'd be chaotic. Yeah, yeah.
- Ease into it.
Yeah, yeah.
You guys want to go grab some margaritas
- by the pool?
- Oh.
- I do.
- Booze.
- I'm ready for some booze.
- Oh, yeah.
- Let's go.
- Yeah. - Me, too.
Oh!
- Oh, "MeToo."
- Very good.
- That's great.
- Very good, and for a woman, a good joke.
Hey, you guys think that
Alan guy's got a big dick?
- Oh, yeah.
- Huge.
I saw it in the bathroom.
I sought it out.