All right, well, that about does it,
which means we are officially
- on island time.
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah, baby. Whoo-wee!
- Here we go.
- Island time.
- Ah, Frank.
I'm so excited about this concert.
- Thank you for the tickets.
- Yeah.
- Oh, I love Jimmy Buffett.
- Oh, yeah.
And those Parrothead broads, they're wild.
- I noticed that, they're nuts.
- Yeah, yeah.
- They are wild.
- I hope he plays "The Piña Colada Song," man.
- Oh, yeah, that's the best.
- I gotta hear it.
Yeah, I wish he would, too, but he won't,
'cause that's, uh, that's not Buffett.
- Huh?
- Yeah, no. H-He does.
It's, uh, the one that goes,
- ♪ If you like piña coladas ♪
- ♪ Coladas ♪
♪ Getting caught in the rain. ♪
Yeah, no, I know the song, I know the song,
but it's sung by a man named Rupert Holmes.
- Who?
- Are you sure? I feel like that's Buffett.
We've been going to see
Buffett for 20 years.
Have you ever heard him play it?
No, but he's not gonna play all
of his hits every single time.
Yeah, no, he is. That's what he does.
That's actually the only thing he does.
And that's just not one of them,
but, hey, listen, buddy,
you want to hear that song, you go ahead
and request away. I won't stop you.
♪ If you like making love at midnight ♪
♪ Mm, mm, mm,
and you've got half a brain, ooh. ♪
Oh, I hope he plays that one.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. We all do.
- Yeah, he won't, he won't.
- W-Were you in the women's room?
- Mm-hmm.
- Well, don't do that. Don't use my bathroom.
- Why not?
'Cause it's my bathroom, and you're a man.
Oh, no. Well, now, as a gay man,
I just feel more comfortable
in the ladies' room.
Oh, come on, the...
with the gay thing again.
Like, look, it makes me uncomfortable
that you're in there using my bathroom.
How about that?
Look, the whole men's and women's
bathroom thing is antiquated.
- Maybe you're antiquated.
- Maybe I'm...
Get off me! Get off me!
- Get him off me!
- Settle down.
Don't. Come on. L-L-Listen...
I know, I know, listen.
We always do this. We...
We always get in some major
tiff right before Buffett,
and then, you know, it just, it just ruins
- the whole island vibe, you know?
- Yeah.
Come on. We're not doing that this time.
All right? This whole bathroom issue
is a simple problem with a simple solution.
So why don't we just sit here
and let's just figure it out.
_
All right, now we're talking.
I tell ya,
there's never been a problem so big,
couldn't be solved by a late night
and a little Chinese takeout.
We should've got cheeseburgers.
Well, Frank, you know, I'm saving
my cheeseburgers for paradise.
- I get it.
- That is Buffett, that one, right?
- Yeah, that's Buffett.
- That's Buffett, okay, cool.
Uh, if I may go first. I'd like to go first.
Oh, are we doing the whole stand up...?
- Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. He's gonna do it.
Now, guys, I believe that as a gay man,
I should be able to use the women's bathroom
because I feel more
comfortable around women.
- Okay, why?
- Well, "A," we both like dudes,
and "B,"
we both find women's bodies disgusting,
- so there's no hanky-panky.
- Well, that tracks.
- Yeah, sure, that makes sense.
- Yeah, yeah.
Done! I'm using the ladies' bathroom, right?
N-n-n-n-n-n... My turn.
- My turn, right?
- Oh, do you have to...?
- The floor is yours.
- I thought Mac just solved it.
- No. No, no.
- No. - All right.
Okay, "A," not all women like dudes...
lesbians,
for example...
and, "B," I find you disgusting.
I don't want men pooping next to me.
- Would you let a trans woman go in there?
- Of course I would.
- But not me?
- No, not you, because you're a man.
You're a gay man, but you're still a man.
I don't know why you're being such a bitch
about this, Dee.
I've been pooping next to you for months.
- What are you talking about?
- You've been in the stall next to me.
I-I recognize you from
those pink heels you have.
- I don't own pink heels.
- Yes, you do.
The ones with the straps that,
that makes those giant feet
look so dainty and cute.
Mac, I don't know what you're talking about.
Mm, uh...
Okay, um...
All right, uh,
I think I can actually explain this.
Uh, Charlie, I do hope
that the explaining you're gonna do
is about why this bathroom
is so much cleaner than ours.
Don't worry about it, this is the last time
you're gonna be in here.
Charlie, what is taking so long?
Give me a minute. Give me a minute!
Uh...
Oh, there they are.
Those are the pink heels
I was talking about.
Charlie, are you a cross-dresser?
No. I just like to use
the women's bathroom,
because it's, you know,
it's quieter, it's less crowded.
And very clean.
Yeah, and, look, I-I just,
whatever, I slip on the heels,
in case someone looked under the stall.
I didn't want anyone to be uncomfortable.
- That's it.
- Okay. But what's with the wig?
Come on.
Don't make me do the whole thing.
The wig is just in case
someone peeks over the top.
How about the dress, bud?
Goddamn it. It...
- Oh!
- Whoa. Whoa.
Okay, okay. Look, the dress just ties
the whole look together, so, you know.
You are a cross-dresser.
No, I'm not. Look, I was raised
by a single mother, you know.
And we were always on the go, and sometimes,
we'd be at, like, a museum,
or, you know, a stadium,
and I'd have to go to the bathroom,
and my mom wasn't
gonna put me in the men's room by myself,
so she carried around a dress with her.
She would slip it on,
and I would go in and out
of the women's bathroom
and no one would notice.
And then, you know, as the years went by,
I just got more comfortable pooping
with a dress, so whatever,
it's not that weird.
- Hold on, though, it's very, very weird.
- It is so weird.
Look, lots of people do it. It's...
- I doubt it.
- I don't know anybody.
- Uh, no.
- Not one person on the planet.
It is what it is, I mean,
it's the only way I can poop, so...
- Oh, okay.
- I guess it is what it is.
- Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
- It is what it is, and it is very strange,
but it does bring up an interesting point.
You see, Dee, you did mention moments ago
that you would be comfortable having
a transgender woman use your bathroom.
Of course I would, so what?
- Well...
- No. That's not,
that's not the same thing,
he's not transgender.
Well, no. He's-he's not transgender,
but he identifies as a woman when he poops.
No. No. Goddamn it, you're only saying that
'cause my bathroom's nicer.
No, no. I-I think, I think Mac is right.
I think this system is antiquated,
and I think...
- Is that, is that a hand dryer?
- Oh, damn.
- Yeah, there's a hand dryer in here.
- Oh, goddamn it.
Well, let's vote. All those in favor.
- Aye.
- No. Goddamn it.
Nice. Okay, well, I knew
we could solve it, guys.
- This is great.
- And then should we also change the signs on the doors
to reflect that it's not a boys' room
- and a girls' room anymore?
- Right. Yeah, no.
We'll pop some new signs on there real fast.
You know, so it's clear that
any gender can use any bathroom.
- Yeah, yeah.
- How hard could that be?
- The dress is making me have to poop really bad, so I'm gonna...
- Okay, let's do it.
- Oh, goddamn it.
- Gotta poop, gotta poop.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. So, I'm sorry,
what's wrong with this one again?
Well, I think it's confusing,
is what the problem is.
- Mm. Mm-hmm.
- Like, maybe we need words or something.
Well, also, like,
what's with the floating starfish
trying to eat the rock?
- That's a baby.
- That's a baby?
- Yes, that's a...
So, now what's happening,
you got wheelchair guy's back there
throwing babies around trying
to get them in wheelchairs?
- It's confusing.
- Okay, all right.
So what if I cover up the baby,
how about now?
I don't get it.
Now it looks like you either got to be
in a wheelchair or a
he-she to go poop in there.
- No, no, no, no, Frank, come on, don't say "he-she."
- What?
- It's hermaphrodite.
- Oh, nope.
Dee, you can't say that anymore, either.
- It's intersex.
- Well, this is all confusing.
Why do I have to keep learning new things?
How about this?
We'll call the bathrooms gender neutral.
That makes me uncomfortable,
because I'm not neutral
- about my gender.
- Mm.
- So now you're uncomfortable, okay.
- Okay.
We put one sign on each door,
both of them say "gender fluid."
Right. 'Cause that-that implies,
like, you're this,
- you're that.
- I don't know. I don't like thinking about gender fluids.
Like, just, uh, it's a gross image to me.
- All right. Well...
- You know what? Look, look.
It's just all so confusing.
You know, we got to make this much simpler.
I have an idea,
if I could just go do one that I think will
- clear it all up.
- Great. Go for it, buddy. Hop to it.
All right, do it, yeah.
- Quick.
- Is the Internet working?
- Hmm...
- Well, hang on. Hey.
Yes, but you stay off it. You stay...
- No. No.
- No, no. I'm just...
You crashed our last three laptops, man.
- You are not doing it again.
- Bring it out here.
Do it out here where we
can see what you're doing.
- No, I'll do it in the office.
- Do it in front of us.
It'll take me, like, two minutes.
Two minutes.
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
- You go fast.
- _
- I'm-I'm finished.
- I'm finally finished.
- Oh, God. It's about time. - Goddamn it.
- He's limping.
- Are you chafed?
- He's chafed.
- Huh? Oh, yeah. Super chafed. Hey, do you know
how to get Russian
malware out of a computer?
- No. - Wait.
- Then the computer's broken.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. - Aw!
- Yeah, but the sign's done.
- All right, man.
Let's see what you got.
What do you think?
Well, I don't know what I'm looking at.
Yeah. What-what am I seeing here?
It's just dicks.
- No. There's... I mean, yes.
- Oh.
There are a couple of dicks, but...
- It's mostly dicks.
- That's a lot of dicks.
- Oh, now... now all I see is dicks.
- Mm-hmm.
No, there's also pictures
of road kill and roast beef sandwiches
to accurately depict
what a vagina looks like.
- Okay.
- Anyone else uncomfortable?
All right. Moving on.
All right.
I'm just gonna go back to the office.
- No, you stay here.
- No. No, no, no. No!
You are not going back to the...
- Yeah.
- All right, all right.
So, this...
I think this covers it all, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think that. There's the man.
- Uh-huh.
- The woman.
- Mm-hmm.
- That's the he-shes,
or the interspecies, whatever it is.
- Yeah, whatever you said.
- And this is Christians,
- Muslims.
- I assume
the dollar sign is meant to represent Jews?
Well, it ain't the Mormons.
- Uh...
- Let's not get into that.
Okay, you know what?
- Why-why are we bringing...?
- I was against it. Yeah.
Why are we bringing
religion into this at all?
Because I want to know who's in there,
- because it'll make me feel safer.
- Oh, goddamn.
Can we please put two signs on the doors?
- Both signs say "toilet."
- Yeah...
- Oh.
- There's a toilet in there,
and that's all you really need to know.
- That's a good point. I think that would work.
- Could say "toilet,"
- and then it's kind of your choice which one you use.
- Just "toilet."
That actually does work.
- I feel like that totally works.
- Yeah. - We solved it?
- Okay, great. We so...
- Did we do it? - We solved it!
- We solved it!
- Oh! Right! God!
- Let's get the hell out of here.
- All right.
I think it was my idea, but, yeah.
Oh, you son of a bitch. Just go.
- I think I said it first.
- Just go.
You guys, you go,
and I'll-I'll lock up, okay?
I've had Chinese food. It wants out, so...
- Yeah.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Why aren't you using the good bathroom?
Well, 'cause I'm about
to do some real damage.
I don't... I don't want to do it
in the good bathroom.
Well, I'm-I'm uncomfortable with that.
- How?
- So close.
We were so close.
Well, because I just don't
want to share my bathroom
- with a bunch of broads.
- What happened, Frank?
- We decided we were all cool with it.
- We were fine.
I didn't know she was gonna smash in there.
A woman is not a lady when
she's dumping up a john.
Also, this brings up an interesting point.
We should probably confine Dee's damage
to, like, one bathroom or the other,
you know.
Otherwise, I'm gonna have to clean both.
Charlie, you're the janitor.
You should be cleaning
both bathrooms regardless.
- He hasn't been.
- Clean both bathrooms! - I do it.
Yeah, all right.
Well, now you're just, like,
kind of getting off-topic here, you know.
I have an idea. The guys should be able
to pick whichever bathroom they want.
- Dee has to stay in hers.
- What?!
- All in favor.
- Hey, that's majority rules.
- Get out of here.
- Yeah, yeah.
- There you go. Solves it.
- No. No, no, no.
Absolutely not. No. You guys
can't take away my right to choose.
- Oh, you want to go there?
- I do want to go there.
My body, my choice.
It says so in the Constitution.
- Okay, well, the Bible says...
- Wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Guys, don't do this. No, come on.
It's crazy. All right.
Don't make this about abortion.
Guys, we always do this.
We veer wildly off-topic,
and the next thing you know,
we're having some ridiculous
argument that has nothing
to do with what we're trying
- to solve, you know.
- And then tempers flare.
Exactly. We're talking about
evolution all of a sudden.
Then we're arguing about racism
or whether or not ghouls exist.
- They do, though, 'cause I've seen one.
- No, they don't.
- No, they do.
- You-you've never seen them.
- Yes, I have seen them.
- No, you haven't.
- Yes, I have!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- No, wait! Hey, stop! Hey, stop!
- Charlie!
- You stupid twink!
- I'm a bear! I'm a bear!
- You wish you were a bear!
- Take it easy, guys.
Stop! We're off-topic. This is not Buffett.
This is not...
We're not being very Buffett right now.
- That was not Buffett at all.
- We're not being very Buffett.
- It wasn't very Buffett of me.
- It's not Buffett, man.
All right, all right. Oh! I got an idea.
It should just be about what's
going on in there, right?
What if we have
separate bathrooms...
for separate bodily functions?
Oh, like a piss room and a shit room.
Yeah. Exactly, okay? And, uh, we just
put very simple labels on the door.
Room number one for when
you got to empty your balls,
and room number two for when
you got to empty your butt.
Pee is not in your balls, but... yeah. Okay.
No. I don't think it's gonna work because
nobody can shit when everybody
knows you're shitting.
- Why not? Everybody shits.
- Yeah.
Yeah, but it's a shameful
act that we all do in secret.
- Well, that's true.
- Even dogs know that.
You ever see their eyes
when they're doing it?
- They know.
- Hmm.
- They look at you like this.
- Yeah.
Yeah. They're ashamed.
Yeah, well, guys,
it's a system that invites abuse.
I mean, who here would use
the piss room to shit?
No, that's the whole point,
is that you just pee in it.
- I wouldn't do that.
- In the shit room, you shit.
Yeah. No one's gonna do that.
- Pee over there.
- Really?
Yeah. I'd-I'd poop in the pee room.
I would poop immediately in the pee room.
100% of the time I will
shit in the piss room.
- You're totally right.
- Actually, don't like this idea.
See? There you go. I rest my case.
Yeah. But you know what?
Maybe people would be
a little less inclined to cheat,
and they wouldn't feel ashamed,
if they had a little bit more privacy.
Like, what if the partitions
went all the way down to the ground?
- Hmm.
- Yeah?
And you created sort of a dome of privacy.
- So you're closed in.
- You're closed in.
You know what you could do? You could add
a scented candle in there for the smells.
- Right.
- And some noise to cover the sounds.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yes.
A loud noise, like screaming.
- Mm-hmm.
- Or just music.
Let's do music.
Guys, we're making progress.
This is great. I'll tell you what.
Uh, Dee, why don't you go grab some cardboard
- for the partitions.
- Yep, yep.
And, um, I'll order us
some breakfast burritos.
- It's getting to that time.
- 'Cause I'm getting hungry.
- Yeah!
- Tasty. - Extra bacon for you?
- Okay, okay. Yeah.
- Extra bacon, baby. - All right.
The screaming's kind of cool, right?
It's better. It's better.
Works better than the music.
- I never would've thought.
- Yeah, yeah.
The music, it was like,
I felt like I could hear maybe
- a poop or a pee happening, but the screams are...
- Right.
And I honestly,
I feel like I'm not even in a bathroom
- right now.
- Yeah. Here you are eating a burrito.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- In a bathroom.
- Oh! That was great.
- Yeah, how'd that go? Yeah?
I did something in there.
I'm not gonna tell you what, though.
Well, there's no need.
I couldn't hear a thing,
- and I can't smell a thing, so...
- Yeah.
Hey, Frank, how's it going in there, man?
The walls are too high.
I don't know where to aim.
- Aim? Aim-aim at the bowl. The toilet.
- You just aim at the toilet.
- The same spot.
- What are you talking about?
- Ah! - Whoa! Hey!
- Whoa! Goddamn it.
Never sneak up on a man like that,
especially when he's at his most vulnerable.
Why do you have a gun on the toilet?
I always carry a gun on the toilet.
Otherwise, I can't make.
Well, now I'm very uncomfortable.
Well, tough titties.
I got the right to defend myself.
It's in the Constitution.
Have you ever read the Constitution?
Yes.
No.
This is wild stuff.
There's a part in here
that says that freed slaves
are only three-fifths of a person.
- It's wild. Yeah.
- Really? It says that in there?
I can't imagine where you're going
with this, Frank.
Well, I was figuring that if we handled
this problem like the Constitution,
that would mean
that white landowners
would get a full bathroom.
Everybody else gets three-fifths.
How do you use three-fifths of a bathroom?
Piss in the sink.
I beg you to stop using the Constitution
in the way that you're using it.
Listen. Frank just gave me a good idea.
- Hmm.
- Okay.
Reparations.
Look, minorities have been treated
like shit in this country
for so long, right?
So, I say we give them the good bathroom.
You know? I mean, for years and years,
they've been oppressed.
The least we can give them is, you know,
a nice place to piss and shit, right?
And we got to put up a sign
so that they know their place.
Now, are-are you proposing
that we put a sign
on one of the bathrooms that says
"minorities only"?
What does the other sign say?
- "No minorities allowed."
- That's crazy.
- Do you hear yourself?
- That's bad. - You hear where
you're running into trouble there, right?
No, no, it's super progressive.
- No...
- Yeah, i-it's a bathroom
- for women, non-whites, and gays.
- Uh...
Oh, oh!
Oh, I get it.
And I-I'm 100% on board.
I agree. I'm with you.
Wait a second, Dee. So now you're okay
with Mac using your bathroom?
Yeah. As long as the majority of the people
aren't taking a shit in my bathroom, sure.
Okay, well, let's just go ahead
and vote for it. Ch-Charlie?
W-Wait, wait, wait. Hold on a second there.
Before you vote, uh, Charlie, uh, you know,
consider this... there's-there's no shame
in doing what's best for the majority.
I mean, that is what a democracy is, right?
It's trying to please the greatest number
of people in a country.
- White people.
- Please don't help.
Okay? Yeah. Uh, what I'm saying is
that you're never gonna be
able to please everybody.
It's just... There's no way,
you know what I mean?
And, of course,
everybody wants their own little piece
of paradise, right? I like mine with...
I like mine with lettuce and tomato.
♪ Heinz 57 and French fried potatoes. ♪
- Mm.
- But that's just me, you know?
There's a small minority
of people out there,
they like their
cheeseburgers with pineapple.
- Oh, yeah, I know. Get the hell out of here.
- Ew.
- Gross.
- What are you thinking? You know what I mean?
But there is a minority out there,
and that's how
they like it. But are we saying that,
for those people's sake,
we got to have every single hamburger store
in the whole country offer pineapples
on their cheeseburgers?
I don't think that's right.
Mm-mm. We ought to take it
off the pizza, too.
Hawaiians are savages.
Okay, you're not helping, all right?
Your racism is making...
I hate when you're on my side.
Mm-hmm. Okay, all good points,
you know, strongly made.
I like the hat.
I was focused on that most of the time.
But I-I'm kind of leaning towards you.
I don't know why. It might be the shirt.
Look, majority rules may have
worked in medieval times,
but we live in a civil society now.
And societies are judged on how
they treat their most vulnerable.
See, we have to give voices
to those who have no voice.
- He's right...
- Shut up, Dee! I'm talking!
Women are always... Goddamn it.
Look, what I was saying
was that we need to protect
those most marginalized, okay?
We need to change our attitudes.
We need to change our latitudes.
And we need to vote for a
minorities-only bathroom.
Okay, uh, also good,
strong points there made forcefully.
I was distracted by the shiny shirt.
That's cool.
I liked when you snapped at Dee.
It was annoying when she chimed in.
Um, so maybe I'm leaning towards you now.
I don't know.
- Okay, well, then that means we're all voting for...
- Oh!
Wait, wait, wait!
I just looked up the demographics of Philly.
It says here that this city is 54% women
and 68% Christian.
- Whoa.
- Which means that Mac and Dee
are in the majority.
- Wait, wait, wait, is that true?
- Uh-huh.
It also says that 52% are black,
which means white men,
like me and Dennis,
are in the minority.
Uh-oh, we're minorities,
which means that,
by your own argument,
we actually should get the good bathroom.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait! I-I'm gay,
so that-that still means
that I'm a minority.
Yeah, but are you more gay
than you are Catholic?
I don't know. They're at war.
It's all very confusing. Where...
What does it say about transgenders...?
- Less than one percent.
- Yeah.
So what am I?
You are white.
Okay, and I'm a...?
Man.
And that would make me...?
- In the minority.
- Which means I go towards...?
Us. Y-You know what?
Frank, you explain it to him.
I'm gonna... I'm g... I'll-I'll kill...
- I'll-I'll smash him and, uh...
- You get the good bathroom.
- If I come with you? Okay, it was clear...
- Yes.
It wasn't totally clear before,
- but I get it now.
- It should've been.
Oh, boy. Yeah, okay, so yes.
- So all those in favor of doing the actual right thing
- I got it.
and giving the minorities the good bathroom,
- let's go ahead and raise your hand.
- Yeah. Hey!
- Okay, all right! Great, hey.
- Okay.
- Finally, a win for straight white men, right?
- Great.
- Now we're talking. Yeah.
- Yeah! Finally, something for us.
- We got it. Yeah. Something for the guys.
- Something for us. Okay.
- Yeah, let's go to Buffett!
- All right, we're gonna...
- Anybody want cheeseburgers?
- All right.
- I'm gonna get the grill ready.
- Well, yeah, hey, if I'm headed
- to paradise, I'm gonna want a cheeseburger.
- Let's roll!
- What-what are you guys doing? Let's go.
- Let's go.
We're not going.
What do you mean you're not going? What?
You used Buffett's words
to promote discrimination, dude.
It's not cool.
No, but you guys have to go. I mean,
you're the only two other
real Parrotheads of the bunch.
I mean, Frank's just going 'cause the
chicks are wild. You know what I mean?
- And, Charlie, he doesn't know what's going on.
- I know.
- Yes, I do.
- He has no... No. What are the songs?
- What's another Buffett song?
- ♪ Aruba, Jamaica... ♪
- That's Beach Boys.
- It is.
- I don't know the songs.
- Yeah. That's the Beach Boys.
Well,
there's no sense in going to Buffett
if we're not... we're not all gonna go.
Then we're not going to Buffett.
♪ If you like piña coladas... ♪
Please don't, Charlie. It's too... it-it...
- It hurts too much.
- I thought you... Come on, man.
I thought you said it wasn't Buffett.
Yeah, but i-it's close enough.
You guys ever listened to
the lyrics to that song?
- It's super dark.
- Is it?
- Mm-mm.
- Yeah, it's about
a guy trying to cheat on his wife.
Don't tell me that, man.
It's, like, such a happy song.
You know? Who doesn't like piña coladas?
I don't.
You know, they're not my first choice.
Just as a woman on the go, I got to be able
to really put 'em back,
and if you drink those too fast,
- you'll get that-that frozen headache.
- Hmm.
As a straight man,
I actually love piña coladas,
but I don't like getting caught in the rain.
It flattens my hair. Yeah.
And you guys know how
great I look in leather.
- As a gay man, I do.
- And that's what's so annoying about you, Mac.
- That's not really a gay thing. That's just a you thing.
- It's so annoying.
What about that bullshit about
making love until midnight?
I mean, as a senior citizen,
I can't get it up past 6:00, 6:30, tops.
- Mm...
- Really? - Oh, geez. I got that
- to look forward to, huh?
- Really.
You know, as a straight man
who poops transgender...
- You got to just let that go.
- I'll probably stop doing that.
- It's not a thing.
- It's time to stop doing that.
I guess, you know, guys,
when it comes down to it,
we all identify very differently out here.
You know? But in there...
in there, we're not so different.
In there, we're all the same.
In there, we're all just disgusting,
vulnerable, ashamed.
Like a bunch of filthy animals
dumping in a shithouse.
It's the one common thing
amongst a-a king and a pauper.
- Right.
- You know? We all got to take a shit.
Yeah, right.
Why are we trying to make everyone
feel comfortable in there? When the truth is
no one's ever gonna feel
comfortable shitting next
- to another human being. It's just awkward.
- Well, if we're never gonna get
anybody to feel good
about shitting together,
how are we gonna solve the problem?
Hold on a second. Hold on. Listen.
- If we're all the same in there...
- Uh-huh.
then why don't we just focus
on treating other people
the way that we want to be treated?
Dee...
we were just talking,
- and you just barged right in.
- Yeah, shut the fuck up.
- Shut the fuck up.
- Like, interrupting and talking nonsense.
- That was, like, so pretentious.
- Yeah.
- Something very pretentious about it.
- We were talking.
- I really feel like we're right in the...
- All right. Okay.
Hey, you know what, guys?
I think I may have just come up
with a solution for our bathroom problem.
Uh-huh.
- Yeah, that'll do it.
- There we go.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's perfectly clear.
- We did it.
Guys, if we leave right now,
we can still make the concert.
- Whoo...! - Let's do it.
- Buffett! - Ooh, let's go.
♪ If you like piña coladas ♪
♪ And getting caught in the rain ♪
♪ If you're not into yoga ♪
- ♪ If you have half a brain ♪
- _