[ charlie ]
I think what mac's
trying to say...
Is that it's probably
the greatest movie
of all time.
[ dennis ]
that's 'cause it is.
Rocky iv is not
the greatest movie
of all time.
Dee, what do you consider
to be a good movie?
I don't know, like,
million dollar baby--
oh, come on.
Are you kidding me?
That is ridiculous.
Come on. It won an oscar.
Rocky iv
has stallone in it,
And he bashes
a russian's face
to all smithereens.
Lifting anvils and shit,
and pulling trucks
through the snow.
Million dollar baby
is totally unrealistic.
Girls can't fight.
They don't have muscles.
It's true.
Okay, that is
a horribly sexist
thing to say.
It's not sexist.
It's just truthful.
Girls can't
pull trucks
through snow.
Can you pull
trucks through snow?
I absolutely could.
You can barely walk
in the snow.
[ man ] excuse me.
Time out.
Is the truck
parked in neutral?
- hey!
- what, dude?
Empty your pockets.
Now.
Okay.
Hey, let's just all
stay calm.
[ groans ]
Nice friends.
Maybe... One to two
inches of snow?
One to two inches--
and a ford f-150.
Right. In park,
but no emergency brake.
Maybe I could pull it
four feet.
I'd give him four feet.
I'd give him five.
What's with the gym bag?
Just got back from
a "boxercise" class
at the gym.
"boxercise"? What kind
of queer shit is that?
- I'm learning self-defense.
- you wanna learn self-defense,
you come to daddy.
I mean, all during the '60s,
before I met my whore wife,
I was a boxer.
They called me
frankie fast hands.
Frankie fast hands, everybody.
Yeah, keep livin'
in the past, dad.
Is this about that stupid
million dollar baby
movie, dee?
No, actually, mac,
it's about being left
with a mugger...
Because my chickenshit brother
and his friends ditched me.
- you ditched your sister?
- absolutely.
With a mugger--
the guy had a knife.
Of course we did.
What were we supposed to do?
If I was there,
I would have used
my frankie fast hands technique.
Technique don't mean
shit out on the streets.
Guys have knives.
Yeah. In boxing, there
are rules. On the streets,
we ain't got no rules.
[ together ]
ain't no rules
out on the streets.
- you guys got no rules
on the streets, you.
- oh, please.
Will you stop talking
about the streets,
You three jackasses,
like you've been there?
I mean, any underground
street fight in philadelphia,
you'd find tons of technique.
- you think you could teach me?
- in a month I'll have you
kicking all their asses.
Right. See you then.
Dennis, I have
an idea.
[ shouting, chattering ]
Well, this is awesome.
Yeah. This is amazing.
There's blood everywhere.
It's beautiful.
Yeah, and we were totally right.
These guys don't have technique.
They get all cranked up
like animals and beat
the christ out of each other.
Look at all this money
being thrown around.
Dude, we gotta get in on this.
Oh, yeah.
Really, I think it's about who
can take the biggest beating.
Yeah.
[ man ]
get up!
You know who can take
a really good beating?
Charlie.
Here she is--
the old gym.
[ sniffing ]
smell that?
That's the smell
of hard work.
And feet.
That's the smell
of big dreams.
The smell of glory.
It smells like feet.
And feet.
Does smell like feet.
Frank?
Oh, shit.
Frankie fast hands!
- [ chuckles ]
- holy crap. I knew it was you.
I haven't seen you in years.
Hey-hey-hey,
frankie, it's me.
Bobby thunderson.
Yes. Yes. Yes, bobby.
Look at you!
You... Really
let yourself go.
Oh-oh, are you trying
to get back into
fighting form?
No, I'm actually, uh,
teaching my daughter
some self-defense.
Holy-- holy shit, man.
I'm training my
daughter too.
Hey, what do you know?
Hey, look at her.
Look at her over there.
Look, look, look.
Oh!
Amazing.
Hey, she's pretty
too, huh?
Like her old man, huh?
[ chuckling ]
Well, it's really nice
seeing you, bob.
Yeah.
Hey, don't listen
to everything
this guy tells you.
You don't wanna get knocked
out in the first round.
[ cackling ]
Oh, my god, that's
an annoying sound he makes.
Ass... Hole.
Yeah, asshole.
Okay, don't listen
to anything he says.
He's a real creep.
All right, now.
Here, we're gonna
start weight training.
First things first--
squats.
Okay. That's it.
Uh, that looks
really heavy.
Look. This is not gonna be
a half-assed workout.
We gotta really get into it.
It's gonna hurt.
Yeah, but I can't lift that.
Just position yourself under
the bar and listen to me.
Here's what you're gonna do.
You're gonna take all
the weight on your neck.
Then you're gonna
jam your legs down
and hyperextend your ankles,
And then shoot back up
and lock your knees
in place.
Not one of those things
sounds right to me
at all.
Look. You wanna fight
like a man?
You gotta train like a man.
Now, come on.
Gimme a squat.
Ready. Go!
[ groaning ]
oh, my god!
Go. Keep it up.
Daddy, I can't.
It's-- I can't.
Keep it up. Keep it up.
At least I got the one.
Right?
Yeah. Get out, get out,
get out.
We got a lot
of work to do.
[ charlie groaning ]
[ mac ]
good, good.
Ah!
Mm-hmm.
[ moans ]
what are we doing?
Charlie, you're, like,
the toughest guy we know.
Yeah?
So nobody can
kick your ass, right?
Practically invincible.
Yeah.
Yeah, what's
your point though?
Well-- so here's
what's gonna happen, pal.
Dennis and I
are gonna train you...
To be an underground
street fighter.
[ laughing ]
what? That is brilliant.
Yeah, it is.
Okay, what's
the first step?
First step is getting
that shirt off.
Yeah, let's get that shirt off.
Why would I do that?
That shirt's just gonna
weigh you down.
Yeah, and rocky never
wears a shirt when
he trains,
So let's just go ahead
and rip that bad boy off.
I think I'm gonna wear it.
That's ridiculous.
You can't train
and wear a shirt, dude.
Now it's becoming
this whole big thing.
It feels a little gay.
It's not gay.
Just take your shirt off.
Why can't I just get, like,
all excited and passionately
rip it off in the moment?
Why can't you just
take your shirt off for us?
Just drop it for now.
All right, all right.
Uh, maybe you should
punch something.
There you go.
Yeah, you should
punch something--
Why don't you punch this board?
Okay. Hold it
steady for me.
Watch your eyes.
All right, come on.
[ groaning ]
oh!
Oh, that's--
[ groaning ]
That looks like
it stings.
Oh, my god.
What's that made out of?
It's a board, so it's,
you know, made out of wood.
It's, like, particle board.
It's, like, harder
than wood, dude.
No.
It's actually
softer than wood.
Yeah, it's a lot
Petrified wood.
What happened, man?
I thought you were--
I don't know.
I wasn't drunk enough.
You should be drunk for this.
We should all
be drunk for this.
Let's get really drunk.
All right.
Yeah. You know what?
I'll get some beers.
Come with me.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let him go.
Mmm.
I don't know
what happened.
Mmm. Mmm.
Mmm.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Deandra,
we've been at this
for days now.
It's like you have
no motor skills.
Just grab that bar
and jerk it down
behind your neck.
Hey! How's the chip
off the old block doin'?
Bobby, not now, okay?
Hey, your old man ever tell you
how we fought back in '61?
They billed it as
"beauty versus the beast."
[ cackles ]
Wasn't much of a fight.
First-round knockout.
[ blows raspberries ]
he went down like a--
wait, wait, wait.
Hold on a second.
What's goin' on
with you, thunderson?
What, are you trying
to humiliate me?
Uh, I think you did that
to yourself 40 years ago.
You know damn well
you hit me after
the bell.
That was a cheap shot.
What are you-- you know,
excuses are like assholes.
Everybody's got one,
and they all stink.
Oh, yeah? You wanna go
at it right now?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You wanna
settle this now?
Let's do it right here.
Let's settle
this son of a bitch
right here.
Hey, hey. Take it easy here.
Jesus. Show a little class,
will ya?
Geez. Look, I'm an old man.
I don't fight no more.
I let my daughter
do my fighting for me.
And maybe in
a couple years, when
this little graham cracker...
Might have the stuff to compete,
maybe we'll see.
Wait. You know what, asshole?
Why don't you go to hell?
Dee, stay out of this.
No. This guy has been
all over us since we walked in.
I tell you what, jerk.
Why don't you take
you big mouth,
And go someplace else
with it?
Listen, little buttercup,
I'm just bustin'
your old man's balls.
You don't have to get
your panties in an uproar.
Oh, my god.
Are you standing there?
Come on, move.
That guy is such an asshole.
Don't blame it on him.
You're not makin' any progress.
I'm goin' to get
the jump rope.
- men are such pricks.
- oh, tell me about it.
I bet you're real tired
of them pushing you around.
Oh, god,
you have no idea.
If only there was a way
that you could be...
Physically tough enough
to intimidate men.
I'm sorry.
Do I know you?
Let's just say I provide
a much-needed service
around this place.
Step into the shadows
and, uh, we'll talk.
[ knocking ]
yeah?
[ mac ]
mac and dennis, dude.
Open the door.
What?
It's mac and dennis.
Open the door.
[ dennis ]
open the door, bro.
All right, guys.
Hang on a second.
It's like, uh--
It's like 11:00
in the morning here.
We don't care.
Open the door.
Surprise, bitch.
- [ laughing, chattering ]
- you're hittin' me with that?
Charlie, let's be honest.
Punching boards
isn't your thing.
But that's okay.
Yes, that's okay,
because for you...
It's not gonna be about
inflicting punishment,
It's gonna be about
having punishment
inflicted upon you.
We need to smash things
all over your body.
Yes!
No.
Yes.
We need to build up
your tolerance to beatings.
Hence the smashing.
We used a trash can, but
dennis wanted to use a chair.
I think he's ready.
- that's way too excessive
at this point.
- that guy's ready.
He's not ready for a chair.
I'm tellin' you,
he's ready.
Hey! Guys!
I can handle a chair.
Go get a chair.
See what you're doing to him?
You're getting him
all worked up.
He's the toughest
guy we know.
Yes, he is, but he--
Hey, mac!
Get a chair,
smash it on my back.
That's the right attitude.
He's got the right
attitude.
I'll tell you what.
Charlie, go put on
those little short-shorts.
Let's take things
to the next level.
Yeah.
But first things first.
Let's get good and drunk.
Let's get drunk!
[ whooping, laughing ]
Whoa!
Whoa! Whoo!
[ cheering ]
drink this. Drink this.
Now, just to be clear,
these aren't steroids, right?
No, no, no, no.
Of course not.
These are
performance-enhancing
supplements.
Okay, so how long before
I start to notice something?
This is the good stuff.
You'll feel it
almost immediately.
But I should warn you,
you may experience
some mood swings,
Some irrational thinking
here and there,
But it is
nothing compared
to the long-term effects.
Which are what?
You ever punched a guy so hard
in the eye he swallowed it?
I'll get some water.
How you feel, man?
You drunk?
Yeah. I'm pretty wasted.
Great. So what
do we smash first?
I wanna smash a crate.
- yeah, a crate on his back.
- why don't you punch me?
Punch you?
What?
I'm probably
gonna get punched a lot
in the tournament, right?
Yeah. All right.
Okay, that's a good point.
Let's punch him.
Pop that shirt off,
and we'll start punching.
Oh, my god. Really?
Yeah, man.
- every time I'm gonna take--
- [ chattering ]
Why can't you just
take it off?
Just take it off.
- you're ruining the moment.
- what is with you
and the moment?
You know what?
Forget it. Forget it.
Who do you want
to punch you first?
I don't care.
- that was good.
- well, you caught me
off guard.
[ groans ]
[ laughs ]
that was a big part of it.
That was the same spot.
The same, exact spot.
Yeah.
Charlie, if we
keep this up,
you're gonna be...
The best underground
street fighter ever, bro.
Okay. Okay. Deandra.
Just 10 more minutes.
No, no. That's it.
Dee, that's--
I love it. I need more of it.
It's dangerous.
Enough. Enough.
Come on, what the hell
has gotten into you
the last couple of days?
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
You think I can't
do this by myself?
You think I'm on something?
"on something"?
Yeah.
I never said
you were on something.
Then don't. Don't start.
Hey, now we're talkin' here.
She's a killer.
You're goddamn right
I'm a killer.
You look like a holocaust victim
in pageant makeup.
- I will eat your babies, bitch.
- bring it!
- nobody's eating babies.
- hey, you lookin'
to spar, little girl?
No. No fight.
She's not ready.
Oh, I'm ready.
No, you're not ready.
I'm ready!
Let me eat her babies.
- what about next Friday, huh?
- yeah. How's Friday?
- you're crazy.
- how's Friday to you?
What's the matter,
"frankie fat hands"?
- you're afraid she's gonna get
knocked out just like you did?
- hey!
Get this lion off of me here.
No!
No! You stop it.
This is my fight.
Do you understand me?
I'm sick of men
getting in my way.
This is my fight. You hear me?
- you hear what I'm saying?
- maybe we should leave
these two alone, huh?
Okay. We'll see you
next Friday, huh?
"beauty versus
the beast ii."
[ cackling ]
Come on, brianna.
Here we go.
You're not ready
for this fight.
Oh, I have an idea, dad.
Why don't you shut
your fat little monkey face
and hold the bag?
I'm gonna paralyze this bitch.
[ man ]
try to be best
'cause you're only a man
and a man's got to learn
to take it
try to believe
though the going gets rough
that you gotta hang tough
to make it
history repeats itself
try and you succeed
never doubt
that you're the one
and you can have your dream
you're the best
around
nothing's gonna ever
keep you down
you're the best
around
and nothing's gonna ever
keep you down
you're the best
around
nothing's gonna ever
keep you down
down
fight till the end
'cause your life will depend
on the strength
that you have inside you
oh, gotta be proud
standin' out on the cloud
when the odds in the game
defy you
try your best
to win them all
and one day
time will tell
when you're the one
that's standing there
you've reached
the final bell
you're the best
around
[ shouting ]
nothing's gonna ever
keep you down
you're the best
around
nothing's gonna ever
keep you down
you're the best
around
nothing's gonna ever
keep you down
down
whoa, whoa, oh
you're the best around
nothing
nothing's gonna ever
keep you down
you're the best
around
[ shouting ]
nothing's gonna ever
keep you down
you're the best
around
[ laughing ]
nothing, nothing
nothing's gonna ever
keep you down
Yes, dad, I know the fight
is in a few hours,
all right?
I'm trying to find
my goddamn headband.
Is that okay?
Is it okay with you
if I find my headband
before I come down there?
Is that all right
with you, dad?
Jesus!
Why didn't we get
the orange one
like I said?
This one might as well
be goddamn camouflaged!
Oh, good.
Are you happy now?
I just punched a hole
in my wall!
[ sobbing ]
Are you sure
you're okay, dude?
[ whining ]
no, I'm not.
I start thinking, you know,
and it makes--
[ growls ]
it makes me so angry.
[ laughing ]
What am I saying?
Okay. Were gonna go--
We're gonna go sign you up
for the fight.
- yes!
- and you stay here
and eat your eggs.
Have the-- have--
make sure you eat
some of the sandwich.
- yeah, you can just meet us
down there, all right?
- can you meet us later?
Meet you later?
Can I meet you later?
- are you gonna meet us?
- yes, I'm gonna meet you
there later!
All right.
[ growling ]
[ laughing ]
All right, sign here,
here and here.
And what is this?
These are waiver forms
in case your fighter is
seriously injured... Or killed.
Oh, we don't care
about that.
Sign away.
What's the, uh,
fighter's name?
Clown baby.
- clown ba-- clown baby?
- yeah.
- you mean like a baby clown?
- not a baby clown.
A clown ba--
It's like a baby--
it's like a clown
that is a baby.
I said cl-- clown baby.
Mm-mmm. You said baby clown.
- I don't even care.
- yep.
"clown baby"?
What in the hell kind
of a name is clown baby?
Bro, it's perfect.
Nobody's gonna bet
on a guy named clown baby.
He's gonna be a huge underdog.
Which means we stand to make
even more money off him.
Exactly.
Oh, that's brilliant.
Hey, pal, 500 bucks
on clown baby.
Oh, dennis. 500?
That's all we got, dude.
You saw charlie.
We turned that kid
into an animal.
Oh, yeah? Call me
a holocaust victim?
Say you're prettier than me?
Okay, maybe that part
might be a little bit true.
We'll see how pretty you are
as soon as I punch
a hole in your--
Wha--
Where the he--
Who took my shit?
I might have
had some.
What did you just say,
you little bitch?
I might have had some
of your pills or whatever.
Oh, yeah?
I am gonna punch a hole
through your face.
I'd like to
see you try that.
Yeah?
[ table rattling ]
Ooh, you're gonna die!
Oh, I am gonna
rip your face off--
You're gonna die!
Make a shirt out of it,
and I'm gonna wear it.
I'm gonna take one second
to take my shirt off,
and then you're gonna die!
[ grunts ]
What the--
hey, listen, lady.
You wanna beat up
on your little boyfriend,
you go do it somewhere else.
Watch the car.
[ snarling ]
Dude, where the hell
is your fighter?
He'll be here.
He'll be here when?
Soon!
Okay, you have five minutes
to put a fighter in that ring.
Okay.
[ mouthing words ]
just got off the phone
with charlie.
Well, where is he?
He's in jail with dee.
What?
Apparently they got all hopped
up on amphetamines...
And beat the shit
out of some guy
in front of the bar.
Amphetamines?
Yeah, like, steroids
or something. I don't know.
Damn it, charlie.
Look at the dude
he was supposed to fight.
He's the scrawniest--
I know! Charlie would
have killed that guy.
We're gonna miss out
on all this money.
Anybody could kick
that guy's ass.
I know.
Come on. You could kick--
you-you could kick
that guy's ass.
You think?
Oh, my god. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, you're, like, the second
toughest guy I know.
I did bash charlie good
a couple times.
You almost hurt him once.
With the bottle?
Yeah, and that's next
to impossible.
That was good.
You're-- you're good.
I am good.
Yeah.
Tell you what. Um--
why don't you go stretch out.
I'll talk to the bookie
and let him know
that clown baby...
Has arrived.
Let's do it.
All right.
Goddamn it.
- frankie, what's the deal?
- she got arrested.
Ah! I knew that skinny bitch
would chicken out.
So we'll never get the fight.
That's a shame, frankie.
Lot of unanswered questions.
You want your fight?
You got your fight.
You and me, right now.
Well, I-- no.
What? Daddy, you can beat him.
Come on.
- you're next.
- it'll be like the old days.
I will kill you.
I will knock your nose
off your face.
You wanna knock something,
you knock it off of me.
That's right.
All right,
you got a fight.
Greg, get my gloves.
I'm sorry, bro.
Yeah, well, sorry's not
gonna get our money back.
He was so fast.
You should have moved around
a little more and tired him out.
We have nothing.
I don't know
what to say.
I gave it my best.
Yeah. You know what?
Your best wasn't good enough.
- hey, you have the time?
- aw, not you again.
We don't have any money.
We just lost it all.
Empty your pockets.
Hey, meth-head.
Are you listening to me?
We don't have any money.
Do it,
or I will kill you both.
Okay, here you go.
Look. Empty.
Now you.
I don't have anything.
Do it.
I don't have--
Just empty your pockets.
No. I'm not emptying 'em.
I'm not even gonna--
I don't feel like standing
in this alley all night.
It's a matter of principle.
A matter of principle?
- I don't feel like standing
in an alley with a meth-head.
- I'm gonna stab you, man!
For the love of god,
empty your pockets.
Okay.
- what the hell is that?
- give it to me.
You give us a second.
Where did you
get that money?
I had to change the bet--
a little.
You bet against me?
I bet against you.
Why would you
bet against me?
It was the right move.
I mean, you got
your ass kicked.
Why wouldn't you tell me?
I could have taken a dive.
I wouldn't have had
to get my ass kicked.
Mac, it had to look real.
Were you gonna
tell me eventually?
Yes.
Yeah?
I was going
to tell you eventually.
Yeah?
You know what?
Stab this son of a bitch.
Oh, wait a second.
Oh, come on, mac.
Don't be like that, man.
You would have done
the same thing.
Come on, don't act
like a baby.
Please don't stab me.
Bash this ugly jerk's
face in, daddy.
Your last chance
to chicken out.
That ain't gonna happen, bobby.
I've been waiting for this
for a long time.
All right, frankie.
Seeing that we're
a couple of old men here,
I think we should
lay down some ground rules.
Now. Number one.
[ groans ]
[ loud crunch ]
Holy shit!
[ voices speaking backwards ]