- Where is it? It was right here.
- _
- I cannot find it. And by the way, Mac,
- what're you even talking about?
- _
The word is superstition,
not "stupid-stition."
I know what the word is, Charlie.
I'm saying your green man
suit is a stupid superstition.
Oh, really?
Then why do the Eagles keep winning?
Also, by the way, dude,
uh, you're a Cowboys fan,
so shut the hell up.
I'm not a Cowboy fan, I'm a Tony Romo fan.
And he retired, so now I bleed green.
- Go, Birds! Go, Birds!
- All right, well, I'm not
going to the Super Bowl without it.
I got to find it.
Yeah, don't make us late,
Charlie, all right?
I-If you can't find it,
you can't find it, you know?
The-the fans have no effect on
the outcome of the game, anyway.
- Do you know how football works?
- Yes.
That's right, your voodoo bullshit
is not gonna mean anything if...
Wh-What's going on with your eye?
Uh, nothing, I got a,
I think I got an eyelash in it.
Well, you're, like,
scratching it, and it's blinking.
I just, I slept on it funny.
What the hell is the holdup here?
Frank, this is why
I wanted total control
over the guest list, all right?
The eyes of the world are
gonna be on Philadelphia,
and I want to show them that we
are not just degenerates, okay?
And that is why I'm very
nervous about these guys.
Chug! Chug! Chug!
Hey.
Chug! Oh!
Do me a favor, hold that corner right there.
- What's this?
- Uh, I got to put up a sign.
I want people to know
we're closed for salmonella
because of the Super Bowl.
Okay. First of all,
how is "salmonella"
the only word you spelled correctly?
And second of all, which is it?
Are we closed for salmonella,
or are we closed 'cause of the Super Bowl?
It's very confusing.
- Look, do me a favor? Okay? Just go find green man.
- Yep.
Please? Please, thank you.
- Charlie. Here, eat this asparagus.
- What?
No, I can't eat that right now.
That-That's not right.
It's not part of my rituals.
Okay, do you know what's not right...
is that we are trying to start a family,
- and you're not taking it very seriously.
- Okay, no, I hear you,
but what I need to take seriously right now
is the Super Bowl, okay?
And that means sticking to my color system.
All right? I wear green. I don't eat it.
I'm green man. I eat brown,
preferably, uh, milksteak
with a little light char to it.
And I drink yellow, because beer is yellow,
and that is what has been
working all season long!
- Oh, my God.
- I don't want to talk about this right now.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Where're you going?
- Huh?
Got to find green man.
Why does no one understand this?
Nobody cares about your
stupid superstitions.
- Dude, just get off my back, all right? Let me find it.
- No.
Man, look, I just wish one time
you would not make everything so difficult.
Yeah, and you know what?
Sometimes I wish you'd just disappear.
Yo, check it out. I got one last surprise.
This is very nice.
Party bus!
- No way.
- Fully stocked.
- There it is!
- You found it! - MAC: All right.
- You found the damn suit. Can we go now?
- Nice.
Where the hell is green man?!
Where is it?!
Well, I just can't find it,
so I'm gonna have to, like,
buy a new one on the way up there.
Who knows if it's even
gonna have the same powers
as the other one did. I...
Where is everybody?
Guys?
_
Honey?
Hello?
Mac?
Dee?
Frank?
I made my friends disappear.
I made my friends disappear!
Hey, Frank!
I'm going through your stuff!
Hey, Mac!
I got your...
sticky Bible!
Dee!
I'm going through your stuff!
Dee, woof!
I don't know why I'm screaming.
This doesn't hurt at all.
Countdown to the game. And start the clock.
E-A-G-L-E-S!
Eagles! All right, boys.
I'm home alone in the bar, you know?
It's all me. This is, like, my bar now.
Hey, cheers to you
and the big game, boys, right?
Really cool, too, man.
Those, like, those uniforms
look really cool on you.
You guys look, like, really strong.
I am a little bored.
What the heck?
Hello?
Mac?
Dee?
Frank?
Is this a joke?
Cricket?
Uncle Jack?
Is this a joke?
It's only my imagination.
Okay.
So, he tries to punch me. He misses.
- Oh.
- He misses. What an idiot, huh?
Yeah.
I got it.
- Hey, idiot.
- What?
Read the sign.
"Closed for salmonella because Super Bowl."
Well, which one is it?
Is it closed for salmonella,
- or is it closed for the Super Bowl?
- I don't know.
Burglars.
Thi-This is my bar.
I have to defend it.
Ah, I know.
_
Ooh, ooh, that's a gusher.
I got to stop the bleeding.
Help! Help!
Oh, shit.
Uh, okay. Okay.
Oh, God. Oh, this is gonna suck.
Oh! Shit!
Okay.
It's time for the Super Bowl.
Super Bowl.
Oh, man.
What?
How is the game starting? Uh...
How did I lose an entire day?!
Oh, shit, I got to get the TV on!
Oh, shit. Hey, uh, help?
Oh, who am I kidding, man?
No one's gonna leave their TVs right now.
My colors.
I-I didn't do my color rituals. Guys,
you're gonna lose the game because of me!
I'm so sorry I let you guy...
I let you guys down, man. I didn't...
Oh, I blew it.
It's gonna be my fault.
Hey. Hey there, fella. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Be careful.
Don't-don't... don't go by the traps.
Don't... Come here, come here, come here.
Come here, come here, come here.
Come here. I got you.
You're gonna be okay.
'Cause I know what it's like
to be caught in a trap now,
and it's not okay.
I won't let you get caught in a trap, okay?
You're so cute and tiny and...
and brown.
Healthy-looking fellow, huh?
Ah. The brown is down.
The brown is down.
Wasn't too bad.
Eagles must have scored. It's working!
All right. All right, let's get that TV on.
I ate my brown, and it worked!
I ate my brown!
Although I got a feeling that's gonna
come back to haunt me later.
No, right now.
Never, ever, ever, ever, ever eat a rat.
Oh, man, that sounds
like the Pats scored, huh?
Okay, I-I just got to keep
going with my colors, right?
All right, that's what I'm gonna do.
I'm-I'm gonna keep going.
I'm gonna... I'm gonna wear green.
I'm gonna drink yellow. All right.
Green. What's-what's green? What's green?
What can I...?
Okay, I got it.
Okay, boys, I got it.
Here's the play.
I'm not gonna let you fellas down.
I'm gonna untie my shoes,
I'm gonna toss them over the rope.
That's gonna lower that
green paint can down to me.
Shoes goes up.
Soar like an Eagle!
Aah! Okay, boys,
I'm not gonna let you down.
Soar like an Eagle! Yeah!
Oh, shit.
Okay, plan B.
Oh, no. Okay.
Bear with me.
All right.
Let's chew through this bad boy.
I'm gonna chew through it.
There we go. Okay.
Here we go.
Oh, no.
All right.
I'm just gonna have to catch it.
One...
two...
three.
Okay, I'm green.
That's...
Nice. Sounds like it's working.
All right.
Got to get some yellow.
Got to get some yellow!
Got to drink some beers, boys!
I'm coming, beer!
I'm gonna get my yellow!
Oh, shit!
I'm stuck.
Oh!
Not enough yellow!
Where the hell am I gonna get some yellow?
Oh, God.
Oh, this is awful.
You can do it, Charlie.
You drink that yellow.
You got us here!
Now finish what you started.
Whoa. Hey, dudes.
Finish your color rituals.
Okay. Here goes!
Go, Eagles!
Oh, that was rough.
Now turn on that TV.
Yeah!
Oh!
I don't think I can get there, boys.
You watched every game this season...
you can't miss
the end of the most important one.
Oh, come on, man.
I did the color rituals. Isn't that enough?
The only reason the Eagles made it this far
is because of your superstitions.
The rituals.
They say you're caught in a bear trap.
They say you lost two quarts of blood.
They say you're hallucinating!
Who's "they"?
Everyone who didn't believe in you.
And I got two words for them: (bleep) 'em!
- Right!
- You've got this, Charlie. You're an Eagle.
- Yeah!
- Now go turn on that TV!
Yeah! Here I go!
- Yeah, come on, Charlie. You got this.
- Come on, Charlie.
- Come on, Charlie. Come on!
- Pull that chain! Pull it!
Yeah!
- Come on, Charlie. You can do this, baby.
- Let's go.
Oh, glass!
- I stepped right on the glass!
- Yeah,
- but keep pushing, man.
- No pain, no gain!
Okay. I got it.
- Oh!
I forgot about that one!
Why would anybody do that to anybody?
Fight through it.
Fight through the pain!
- Come on, come on.
- Move, move.
Oh, I forgot...
- Oh!
- Shit!
Come on, man. You got it. You took
that one, eh? Keep going, Charlie.
- Come on, Charlie.
- Pull that chain!
- Pull that chain! Pull that chain!
- I am pulling,
- you big fat assholes!
- Pull that chain!
There's some slack in here. Pull it.
There you go.
Come on, Charlie.
I can't do it!
I can't do it.
No, no, it's too hard.
No, the trap. It was designed for animals.
Yeah. So?
You're a human, dude.
Use your thumbs.
- What do you mean, use my thumbs?
- There's a release lever
on the bottom. Thumbs.
What?!
Well, why didn't you tell me
there was a release lever?!
You bought the trap, Charlie.
I only know about the release lever
because you know about the release lever.
Y-You get that, right?
Yeah, no, I-I totally get that.
- He's not getting it.
- We're-we're not real. - No, I get it.
Quick question: where is the release lever?
- It's on the bottom!
- The bottom of the trap.
- Yeah. You set it up.
I see it. Okay.
Oh!
Patriots with the ball at their own
- nine yard line.
- Oh!
Oh, Brady's got the ball. The ball... What?!
Brady's got the ball
with time on the clock!?
Oh, shit, what happened? What changed?
Yeah... you're gonna
- have to get back in that trap.
- Yeah.
Aw, come on, man.
You just told me to get out of it.
Yeah, that was before Brady had the ball.
Does it have to be the same leg or...
- Yeah.
- Same leg. - Damn it!
Are you sure this is gonna work?
Every single thing that every fan does,
at home or at the stadium,
makes a direct impact in the game.
Aw... shit.
_
- synced and corrected by sot26 -
www.addic7ed.com