Okay, now put your arms back.
You're like a...
you're like a rocket ship, okay?
Now left.
Now right. Now left.
Now right. Now go lower.
- Oh, come on. Come...
- Can you guys go lower?
Dennis, is this really necessary?
Mac, you have
the tendon dexterity of a sow,
so yes, it's necessary.
Guys, we're about to embark
on the most important 24
hours of our lives here.
Okay, it's important
to stay limber and loose.
Uh, yes. Very good, Charlie.
- Can we just start?
- No, we can't just start, okay?
Preparation is the key to victory.
- Oh.
- Yes, Charlie.
You're really nailing this today.
I got my eye on you. Okay.
Now, does everybody know
what they're supposed to do?
Yes. Dennis, I know exactly
what you told us to do.
I've memorized it. I know where to be
and when to be at all times.
Okay, good. Yeah.
Needy and desperate for approval,
but, uh, good. Charlie.
Now look at that. You see that?
With one little gesture,
he tells me everything I need to know.
That wordless display of
confidence earns my confidence.
Don't. I did it already.
You're so desperate.
- I thought it was cool.
- Okay, now, listen. Guys, guys.
We have exactly one
day to pull this off,
so everything needs to be
executed to absolute perfection.
And, gentlemen, if we do that,
well, the world is our oyster.
Don't say "oyster." Say "clam."
- The world's our clam?
- Yeah.
- I like clams better.
- You like clams? Well,
- that doesn't sound very good.
- They're both shellfish,
- so it's kind of the same, isn't it?
- Yeah. One's disgusting,
- and one's delicious.
- Yeah, okay.
- I personally prefer barnacles. You know what I mean?
- Oh.
- Yeah, there's some meat in there.
- I like abalone.
- Well, okay, guys.
- Abalone's interesting.
- I'm a clam person.
- Seagulls...
- Oh, mussels. What about mussels?
- All right, guys.
Let's not get into a whole thing.
We're getting derailed, okay? Uh...
We can spend the whole day talking
about which shell creatures
we do or don't prefer
or enjoy at any given moment.
That's not what we're doing here.
Okay, look, we put in the work.
Right? We're ready.
We've done our dry run.
And if we put our minds to it,
nothing, absolutely nothing
can stand in our way.
- World is our clam.
- Bring it in, boys. - DEE: Oh!
♪ Uh, Dee is in the house ♪
♪ Uh, Dee is in the house,
uh, Dee is in the house ♪
♪ Uh, Dee is in the house. ♪
- First things first, we got to ditch Dee.
- Oh, shit.
- Yeah, let's ditch her.
- Guys,
I am so excited to get started.
Get started on what?
Oh, my God. You forgot.
Oh, that makes it so much better.
Oh, guys.
From noon today until noon tomorrow,
it's Dee Day.
- What?
- Oh, my God.
- No. - I completely forgot.
- Oh, shit.
- No, I...
- No, wait, wait, wait.
I know, I know.
See, we did all your days,
and now it's my turn.
So that means, for the next 24 hours,
you got to do everything
I tell you to do,
and you got to listen to me.
And you can't complain,
otherwise you're gonna get
one of these.
And I tack another day on.
- Dee, please, please don't do this to us.
- Oh, you better
cram your insults in
now while you got...
oh, few more seconds left, guys.
You...
Dee's a bird!
- Dee Day begins in three...
- Dee's a bird! You're a bird!
- ...two... - You're a bird!
- I hate you, bird!
- You're a stupid...!
- ...one.
_
As we all know, you guys
just love to talk and talk about
why men this and why God that
and on and on and on and on.
And I-I can't even begin
to count the number
of pointless monologues I've
been forced to sit through.
But not today. Today, it's you
who will be forced to
sit and just listen.
And my first topic?
My feelings.
- That's fair. - Yeah, I'm into it.
- Thank you.
- I'm excited.
- Thought you would be.
Now, when I wake up
in the morning, I feel sad.
And I feel sad for a very long...
Today of all days,
and now I'm being forced
to listen to her feelings?
I won't do it. And who cares
about her feelings anyway?
Nobody, that's who.
What about my feelings?
Now, that's interesting, okay?
Plus, the plan.
We can't afford to waste a second,
and these pea-brains are
probably forgetting their parts
with every second that passes by.
Uh-oh.
I'm forgetting my part of the plan
with every second that goes by.
Dennis is gonna yell at me again.
Hey, why was Charlie
outshining me earlier?
I mean, what's that all about?
It's like he wants
something from Dennis.
But what?
Attention? Love?
Why'd he throw me that look?
Does he want to replace me?
Is that what's going on?
What the hell does he want?
I'm pretty sure Dennis has candy.
I heard a crinkle in his pocket
that sounded like the
wrapper of a candy.
I gave Mac a look to let him know
that I figured out Dennis has candy.
Hopefully, if we nail this plan,
he'll give us some candy.
I want that candy.
You know who eats raw shellfish?
Seagulls, that's who.
Clams you bake. Clams you fry.
Pop a rubber band around them,
stuff them full of bread,
boil them shits for an hour.
There's a million ways
you can prepare a clam.
"Make the world your clam."
Just sounds better.
And that, I believe, is the reason
for all of this toxic masculinity.
- Would you agree?
- Huh?
- Yes. - Yeah. Well...
- A-Absolutely.
- Yeah, absolutely.
- Yeah. Everything... - Absolutely.
Everything you were saying,
we were totally listening.
- That's totally true.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, cool.
Um, I'm gonna go take a quick squirt
'cause that beer just
went right through me,
and then we'll move
on to the next thing.
- Thanks, Dee.
- Sounds fun. - All right, Dee.
- Sounds fun.
- Yeah, Dee, this is gonna be great.
- I'm looking forward to it.
- This is really cool.
- So excited. So excited.
- I'm enjoying this a lot.
Goddamn bird!
- I'm gonna...
- Where's the scream pillow?
Yeah, yeah. No, no, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Guys, wait.
We can still pull this thing off.
I-I just came up with another plan.
It was actually based
on what Dee just did.
She just went to the bathroom.
See, everybody's got to take a dump
at least once in every 24-hour period.
This got me thinking, right?
So, at some point today,
each and every one of us will
have to take a shit, right?
We're gonna have to go find a bathroom,
and at that point,
you will go and execute
your part of the plan.
- Sounds good. That's good.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- See what I'm saying? All right.
- Yeah, yeah.
So, Charlie, now it is time
- for you to take your shit.
- Is there time?
- Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Okay, great. Nice.
And then, Charlie, go poop,
and then we'll get started.
What? No, that's not
what he's talking about, Mac.
What he means is that it's time for me
to go to the school, break in
using my old janitor's key, right?
Go into the nurse's office,
'cause he's probably
still on his lunch break.
Make the call. Call the valet.
Let him know that his kid's "sick"
and needs to be
"picked up from school" ASAP.
My man. With that kind of focus,
we're gonna be able to
pull this thing off.
- Yes! - Way to go.
- Yeah! And then when he's there,
- that's when he poops.
- Wrong!
- Totally wrong. Just go, Charlie. Go.
- Okay.
A-And keep this kind
of good focus in mind
when it comes to what's
inside your pants,
'cause I want that, man.
Okay. Yeah. All right, great.
- I want what's in your pants.
- No, no.
All right.
Okay. Where's Charlie?
He had to take a shit.
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
- And I, too, have to take a shit now, as well.
- Oh, what?
No. What, now? No.
Well, make up your mind,
or I-I do the horn.
- Okay. It is a bit of an emergency.
- No, it isn't.
He... You can, you can hold it.
He's gonna hold it.
Knock, knock, knock.
Hey! How you doing, old Terry?
Old buddy, old pal!
Do I know you?
Ah, come on, it's me!
It's Charlie! Remember?
I used to be the janitor
here a few years back.
Yeah, well, I got fired
on account of a relationship
I was having with a Juggalo child,
you know.
That's not the point.
The point is though
I got my old job back.
I'm ready to have new
relationships with the children.
And in case you're wondering
how I got in the building,
that's how.
Oh.
Right.
And if memory serves,
you usually take your
lunch break about now.
So how about you pop on out,
eat some lunch,
and I'll clean up your office.
Oh, uh, I ate already.
Did you?
Lunch is at noon. It's 12:30.
Oh, yeah. Look at that there.
You know what happened though,
Terry, was I got a little
held up on account of it
being Dee Day and all.
- It's not D-Day.
- You know what?
Actually, Terry, I should tell you this.
Um, I saw some kids breaking
in to your car outside.
I ride a bike.
Yeah. That's what I meant.
They were breaking on
in to your bicycle.
Kicked it in half.
Filled it with horse manure.
- Kind of a prank, I guess.
- Yeah, I don't believe you.
Well, only one way to find out.
Better pop outside, take a peek.
My bike is fine.
One step ahead of me, aren't you, Terry?
Okay, you know what happened?
Dee Day just threw everything off, okay?
So I'm just gonna slide on in here.
Maybe I'm gonna make
a little phone call.
No big deal.
And I'm not gonna make a phone call.
I'll just have some candy, then.
And I'm not gonna have any candy
'cause candy's for the kids.
Terry, this has been
an unfortunate, uh...
Hey, can I use your phone
and pretend to be you?
No.
Okay. That's strike three
on my, uh, count.
Uh, I'm gonna fuck your bike up, Terry.
- What the hell is this?
- Charlie, you would not
- believe what we're doing.
- Oh, my God. What is that?
Ladies just doing
it for themselves. I'm just playing.
- I'm Martina Martinez.
- Oh, no.
You don't have to do the accent anymore,
Frank. You're offstage.
- Oh, my God. This is so racist, right?
- It's insanely racist.
We didn't want to do it, but you know,
Dee's humor is so lowbrow.
Oh, my God. What is she...?
Uh, she wants to do
a whole retrospective
of her stupid characters.
- Wrote a play about it.
- Her characters suck!
- I know!
Charlie, thank God you're here.
- Go get into costume. We're up next.
- Dennis.
Oh, Dennis, uh, you're offstage,
so y-you don't have to
do the accent anymore.
That's why you suck
at everything, Maxie.
I say if you're gonna
do a racist stereotype,
you best do it right.
I mean, that's a bit much, but you know.
- Oh, uh, where are we with the phone call?
- Uh, no.
I wasn't able to make it.
I was not able to make the call, guys.
- What?!
- I'm sorry. Okay, look.
Here's what we'll do.
I'll-I'll go to the valet myself, okay?
I'll go to the restaurant.
I'll get the key.
I-I can make it work, Dennis, all right?
Don't get mad.
- Who's desperate now, Charlie?
- Shut up, Mac, you racist!
I'm not racist! She's racist!
She's the one that's racist!
- She's making us do it.
- Hey, turkeys! - Shh. Shh.
- What's the holdup in there?
- No, no, no, no. Goddamn it.
Look, uh, you stay here, Charlie.
Um, Mac, Frank, you go down there, okay?
Um,
you're not on again till the second act.
- I won't let you down, Dennis.
- Great. Go, go, go.
- Go.
- Go, go, go, go, go.
- Oh, man.
- Charlie. Charlie, go get into your costume.
- We got to learn a song.
- What? A song?
God.
The glue on these teeth is insane.
I would never be able to
get them off and on in time.
Ah, this makeup is making me sick.
- I'm... I feel awful.
- It's not the makeup, Frank.
It's the bag of clams you made
us stop before we came here.
The clam is fine.
If w-we got a bag of oysters,
those would've made us really sick.
Whatever, dude. Just focus, all right?
The councilwoman's gonna
be here any second.
Yeah, well, what do we got to do now?
Charlie screwed up the
whole thing with the valet.
Now how are we gonna get her keys?
- All right, well, I got a plan.
- What?
Now, when the valet
gets into the next car,
I want you to go to your car,
and I want you to ram him, all right?
Nothing crazy, but
it's got to be believable, all right?
Then, I'll step in as the valet.
I'll get the councilwoman's keys.
I'll go get a copy made.
I'll be back here ASAP.
I have, I have a suggestion.
I mean, if you want...
if you want it to be
really believable...
the car accident...
then I think you should do it.
I mean, I'm not saying out
loud why you should be the one
to have the car accident,
but I think it would play much better.
I do appreciate that you're working
on your prejudices, Frank.
I, too, am trying
to become a better man and...
but I just...
I-I-I really think that, unfortunately,
- it is a better plan.
- It's a good plan.
So, uh, I'm just gonna
go ahead and do that.
Oh! Oh!
Okay. Okay, he's coming. Oh, good.
- You go get the keys. I'm gonna go do the acc...
- Okay.
- Are you okay?
- I'm-I'm... I'm just so sick.
This makeup is making me...
Okay.
Hello there. I'm the valet.
I'll take your car.
- Oh, are you okay?
- Oh, yeah.
I'm-I'm... I'm fine.
I'm aces. It's just...
It's just that I got a
little skin thing going on.
But I-I... I may get sick,
but it won't be clams.
It won't be the clams,
because if it was clams...
...clams and I was sick,
it would be all over the pavement.
Uh, uh, I'm sorry,
but is there someone else
- that can take my car from me?
- No. No.
- He's gone. He had a car accident.
- An accident?
- Oh, my God. Oh, geez.
- Yeah.
- Oh. Oh.
- Yeah, there it is.
- That was it. Yeah.
- God. Um...
- It's not the clams!
- Oh! Uh, yeah.
I'm telling you, it can't be the clams!
It don't make no sense! No, don't go.
It's not the clams!
♪ For the love of God ♪
♪ Paddy, don't you see? ♪
♪ Your love is all I
ever wanted to be... ♪
- "For me," idiot.
- Uh...
♪ Wanted for me. ♪
Ha.
Okay. Then you do the...
- Do we have to?
- Yeah, I mean. Yeah.
Well, I don't know.
Did you want the horn?
Let's just get it over with.
Plant one on me, Covington!
Goddamn it. Yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, I-I'm looking here in the script,
and it says that they kiss,
"with the quivering lips
of two souls desperate
to taste the juices of passion."
Did that seem like that to you guys?
- No.
No, me, neither. Okay. So do that, then.
Gladly.
♪ My love ♪
♪ There's only you in my life ♪
♪ The only thing that's bright... ♪
Yeah.
Wow!
Okay.
Very nice.
Way better than I was expecting.
Goddamn bitch.
- Goddamn bitch.
- She's sick is what she is.
- Yeah, she's sick.
- That's a sick person right there.
And I know we're supposed to be
cool with this, 'cause, like,
that's where society's headed,
but I'm just... I'm not there.
- I'm not saying it's not right.
- I'm not ready. I'm not ready.
I'm saying I don't want to do it.
I don't want to do it.
What did you eat?
Why am I getting a weird taste...
I had cheese. I thought...
Well, I wanted...
Well, now you know how it feels.
Oh, I don't want to taste your cheese.
It's weird...
Well, I didn't want to taste
your cheese, either.
- Hey. How'd it go with the valet?
- We, uh, we struck out.
- You what?! - No good...
- Well, how are we gonna get
in the woman's apartment
without her key?
We got to get in that apartment.
We got to set that woman's clocks back.
- What's going on with him?
- Clams.
- Where'd you get clams?
- Did you eat bad clams, Frank?
- No, don't.
- Hey, guys. Ticktock back there!
All right,
just go finish the goddamn show.
- Yeah, by the way, she made us kiss.
- Yeah.
- She made us kiss.
- I'm not doing that. I'm not doing that.
All right, let's just get out there.
I don't want to be doing this all week.
- Hey, you guys really did kiss?
- Yeah, but don't get excited.
- That's not fair.
- But we didn't like it.
- Just go.
- Dennis, you should come out with us.
- No, no, no.
- Get out! Just go and finish the show.
- Finish the show, all right?
- I'm not kissing you.
Okay.
So, in this scene,
Martina enters Tammy's massage parlor
looking for a full-body rubdown.
- What?!
- Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah.
And like all great plays,
this one is going to
have a happy ending.
Yeah, that was clams.
Oh, nothing like a day of bird-watching.
So peaceful. So relaxing.
- Wouldn't you agree?
- Huh? Oh, yeah. - Yeah.
- Really calming.
- And, yeah, it's, uh...
- It's great.
- Birds are m-majestical.
Ooh, fun bird fact.
The ostrich's eyes are
bigger than its brain.
- Huh.
- Do you have any thoughts on that?
- That's... cool.
- Good.
- Great bird. - It's a good bird.
- Ostriches are good birds.
Well, unfortunately,
I have to take another piss.
- I'll be back.
- Okay. - Okay.
See ya, Dee. We're just gonna look at...
look for some more birds that we love.
- Yeah, we'll keep on, uh...
- Yeah, just gonna...
Oh, my God, I want to scream "bird,"
I want to scream "bird."
- I want to scream, "Bird! Bird!"
- That would be so good.
- Do you want me to do it for you, Dennis?
- No.
Don't do it.
She's probably hiding behind a tree.
Yeah. What's going on with you?
Why are you so off your game today?
Well, I... Charlie
has been outshining me all day,
and I want to shine for you,
Dennis, so I'm just...
I haven't been outshining you.
I was just throwing you looks
because I wanted the candy,
but I was gonna share it with you.
- What candy?
- Dennis has candy in his pocket.
Okay, guys, can we get back
to talking about the plan?
- You have candy?
- Look, w-we're getting off track here.
- Dennis has candy?
- I heard it crinkle.
- Yeah, I want that candy, man.
- Yes, I have candy.
All right? Of course I have candy.
I keep candy in my pocket sometimes
so that I can get Charlie's focus.
It was working like a charm, man.
I was zoned in on
everything you were saying.
Yes, I know it was working;
the whole goddamn thing was working
till Dee came through with
this Dee Day bullshit.
Are we gonna get the candy,
or are you gonna keep it
- in your pocket all day?
- I'll have some candy. - Here's the candy.
- Yeah! Yes, I knew it.
- Oh, oh, oh! I want...
All right, all right.
- Wow.
- Children. Children.
- Good candy, good candy.
- This is good candy.
I don't need the candy anymore anyway,
'cause I have a backup plan.
We don't need the
councilwoman's keys anymore
to get into her house,
because we have me. All right?
So I'll peel off. I'll go seduce her.
She'll invite me into her house,
where I'll bang her as fast
as I possibly can, and then,
while she's cleaning up afterwards,
I'll set all of her clocks back,
causing her to sleep late
and miss the boat, okay?
So when Dee comes back, just tell her
- I had to go take my shit.
- Nice, man. All right.
- Watch out!
- Hey.
- Where you rushing off to?
- Oh, I-I got to take a shit.
- Do ya?
- Yeah.
- Okay. I'll let you do that.
- Okay.
- But real quick first.
I wanted to do something with you.
- I really have to shit, Dee.
- Yeah, this'll be fast.
- What is that?
- Oh, these are makeup wipes.
So that you can remove your makeup.
Makeup?
I'm not wearing any makeup.
Then it won't be an issue.
I mean, I'm wearing
a little bit of concealer.
Is that what you're talking
about having me remove?
Well, I'm talking
about the concealer, yes.
But I'm talking about
the rest of the makeup,
the tape you have behind
your jaw and your eyes.
I'm talking about the hair paint.
I'm talking about all of it.
What a nice restaurant this is,
filled with attractive,
professional-looking people.
You know what it is?
It's the kind of place
where you wouldn't want to
stick out like a sore thumb.
How are you liking it, Dennis?
Yes, very nice.
- Yeah?
- Yes.
Would you like to go introduce
yourself to some ladies?
No, uh, I-I'm okay. Uh, no.
Okay. I'll go round some
up and bring them to you.
- No.
- Yep.
Hey, don't mind her, dude.
Y-You look great.
Holy shit. That's her.
- Who?
- The councilwoman.
- She's right there.
- Who? Right there?
- Right there. That's her.
- Right there? Oh, shit.
- Oh, my God, this is incredible. What are the odds?
- That's her, yeah.
Dee has no idea how good this is for us.
- Dennis, go do your thing.
- This is great.
No, I-I...
- I can't. No.
- Buddy,
makeup or not, you are the Golden God.
It's all about what's in here.
Oh. Is your pec deflated?
Sh-She took his pads out.
- Yeah, he had...
- Oh, your pec pads.
- He had some pads.
- No.
Well, either way, man, you can do it.
You're our only hope.
- I can do this.
- Yes. - Yeah.
- Yeah, it's worth a shot.
- Yeah!
- That's the attitude. - Come on, man.
- You're looking good.
You got it. You got this. You got this.
- You got this. You got this.
- Go, go, go, go, go.
- He ain't got this.
- That's what his soul looks like.
Hi.
Did I frighten you?
Sorry.
Uh, I'm not, I'm not, uh... I'm Dennis.
Do you like hard candy?
I have candies. Oh, you know what?
Actually, I don't. Scratch that. I...
I threw all the hard candies
at those idiot children.
Uh...
Oysters or clams?
- Excuse me?
- Oysters, obviously.
You know?
- Mm.
- Plus, like, they-they...
You can, you can get sick off clams.
Like, I got real sick off
clams when I was, like...
Anything can make you throw up
if you're, if you're, uh...
if it's gone bad.
You know, my dad was,
like, throwing up off...
He's not really my dad, but you know.
Yeah.
But anyway, it's oysters for me.
Um...
Hey, uh, you know what? I just realized.
We don't have a lot of time, so let's...
We should get this over with.
Can I get your house key?
- What?
- We don't,
uh, have to have sex like this.
I can, I can...
I can put another man's face on.
If you give me your house key,
I can go to your house
and put on some of your makeup...
- Get away from me.
- Well, hold on a second.
Um, uh, we... I'm supposed to
be taking a shit right now.
- And so... Yeah.
- Dennis.
What are you doing to this woman?
Uh, it was my turn to take a shit,
and then I was gonna do it with her.
I am so sorry about him. Okay?
This man is clearly a monster,
and he will be punished accordingly.
G-Go wait for me over there, monster.
We'll find another woman.
It's Dee Day.
Just so you know, you look...
a lot better now, but you looked fine.
I just don't look good when
I haven't got enough sleep.
And I got a little nap in,
so, you know, I'm back.
- Huh.
- Anyway,
I bet you the city
council's voted already.
- Dying to figure out which way they voted.
- Oh, dude.
It doesn't matter.
Like, the bird bitch ruined everything.
- We had a plan. We had...
- Shh. Keep your voice down.
We may have lost this one,
but the most important thing
is that we don't get another Dee Day.
Oh, man. That's, like,
the 20th piss I took today.
- Oh, yeah?
- Well, hey, it's important
- to stay hydrated.
- Yeah.
Knock it off. Looks like
you guys are gonna make it.
And I have to say,
I am very impressed that you were able
to focus on anything other than
yourselves for one entire day.
- Well, Dee, it's been a real pleasure.
- Uh, we haven't
- made it yet, so... - We've enjoyed it.
- It's been really great.
And Dee Day ends officially in
three, two, one.
All right, let me have it.
Pile it on me.
- News. - Pile it on me.
- TV. TV. Yeah, put the...
- Channel 7. Channel 7.
- Put the news on. Put the news on.
- What are you doing?
- What channel? What channel?
- S-Seven? Seven?
- Yeah, it might be.
In a stunning upset,
local ordinance LC-103 passed today.
The controversial proposal
actually legalizes public urination.
- It passed! It passed!
It passed!
Oh!
- It passed anyway.
- Nice!
What passed?
Dee, we have been working for weeks
on a very intricate plan
to ensure the passage of that ordinance.
Yeah. All we had to do was
stop one city councilwoman
- from voting, that was it.
- Yeah, yeah. So we had
this ingenious plan to,
uh, get ahold of her keys,
sneak into her house and, uh,
turn all of her clocks back,
- mess with her phones a little bit or whatever...
- It was a good plan.
...so that she would sleep too late,
she would miss the vote,
and the ordinance would pass,
and it passed!
We knew that she would be
the one dissenting vote.
- So we had to stop her.
- Yeah.
- How?
- Oh, well, it's a group...
- Uh, well, yeah.
- There it is.
It's all men and she was the one lady.
- Men are free once again...
- We are free!
...to relieve themselves
where God intended.
You guys are idiots!
That's the most ludicrous
thing I've ever even heard.
Why didn't you just go
and slash her tires, like,
five minutes before she had
to leave for the meeting?
- Oh. Oh.
- What? Oh, yeah, just do that.
- Okay, yeah, just do that.
- Yeah, sure.
Dee, you know what?
You don't get it. Okay?
Women will never understand
what it's like to be a man.
Like, we just, like,
we need to piss in public, okay?
We need to hatch plans
that actually work.
Dee, your plan would not have worked.
Oh, yeah? My plan did work, jackass.
I got close enough to the
councilwoman in the restaurant
to steal her wallet, got her address,
and then replaced the
wallet without her seeing.
And then, in the middle of the night
when I told you guys
I was going to "take a shit"
like you were doing all goddamn day,
I snuck over and I slashed her tires.
You did? Why?
Did you see how many times I peed today?
I have a teeny, tiny, little bladder.
I want to be able to pee
on the street if I have to.
- Oh! You? - Ugh! Gross.
- In front of us?
- Just out there in the public?
- A woman? - Squat?
- Dee, you nasty.
- Nasty.
- Dee, you n...
- She's so nasty.
No, you know what?
You guys are just pissed
- because I outsmarted you.
- Oh, you outsmarted us?
- You're embarrassed.
- Dee, you spent the entirety of Dee Day
coming up with a plan
that eventually led
to us getting exactly
what we want, so...
- We scored.
- You're a stupid bird.
Don't even bother trying
to explain it to her.
Her tiny bird brain will never get it.
Birds don't understand plans.
What about this one? Dee's a bird.
- That's a good one.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ooh, ooh-ooh, ooh.
You should all probably
check your phones.
- Why?
- Oh, I don't know.
Just 'cause I pushed the
cuckoo clock ahead an hour.
No. Shut up.
Here's the problem, guys.
You just insulted me on Dee Day.
- No. - No, no, no, no. God.
- Oh, no, wait...
You know what that earns you?
Another day of Dee.
- Oh, no!
- No, no, no, no, no!