[ mac ]
well, then what would you say?
[ dennis ] she's a quitter.
[ dee ]
you know what?
I don't even care!
And that proves my point.
Because you don't care,
you never succeed.
- right. Failed.
- failure implies that she
actually tried to be an actor.
Okay, I did try.
It just didn't happen
to work out.
It's not your fault, sweetie.
You're just not pretty enough.
Oh, thank you!
That's my dad, everybody!
[ door opens ]
Great!
Okay, I just killed
three very large rats...
That were stuck in glue traps.
Good work.
No, no, that's not good.
I am done with rat detail.
That's by far the worst job
in the bar!
That's why we call it
"charlie work."
no, dude. Not charlie work.
There's an emotional toll
that comes out of this.
I mean, you kill one of those--
Are you kidding me?
What? What?
You're blowing smoke
directly in my face when
I'm trying to talk to you.
What is he talking about?
If you want to smoke, you
should have to take it outside.
- that's it. I'm done with this.
- it's a bar.
Yeah. It's a bar, dude.
Charlie,
I think you're right.
I think maybe we should ban
smoking in here.
What are you talking about?
That's completely ridiculous.
How is that ridiculous?
There are smoking bans
in a lot of states now.
Uh, yes. And it's
completely un-american.
If you don't like smoke,
then don't come into the bar.
I work in this bar.
I work here.
But that's because
you have the freedom
to choose to work here.
Smoking bans, they don't
protect freedom. They strip
'em away from smokers.
Look, I didn't go
to vietnam...
Just to have pansies like you
take my freedom away from me.
You went to vietnam in 1993
to open up a sweatshop!
And a lot of good men died
in that sweatshop!
Oh, my god!
You're out of your mind.
Look, look.
The point is that
if charlie took any time
to study in school,
He would recognize that the
constitution protects my freedom
to blow smoke all over his face.
You gotta be--
you don't know shit
about the constitution, man.
- he knows more than you two
un-american freedom haters.
- thank you.
Charlie, we hate freedom.
Ew, we hate it.
Hate it.
- I'm un-american?
- you're practically a vietcong.
Oh, is that right?
Okay, you wanna talk america?
You wanna learn a little
something about america?
Dee, let's roll out of here.
- where are we going?
- we're gonna go america
all over their asses!
[ man ]
it is time for the truth!
Five million people will die
this year of smoking-related
illnesses!
These body bags, these represent
the number of people...
That will die
in this city alone today!
It doesn't have to be this way!
Let's make smoking history!
[ applause ]
yeah!
Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah, man!
Yeah.
U.S.A., baby! Whoo!
That's what america's
all about, dee!
Yeah.
Right here!
This is the u.S.A.!
Oh, my god!
That guy really knew how
to pull an audience.
I tell you what.
Let's get in on this.
Hey, bro.
Great job out there, man.
Oh, thanks.
You really--
you had me like hook, line
and sinker with that--
It was awesome, dude.
It was awesome. So, look,
I want in on the cause.
Oh, okay. Just go
to the web site
and you can check out--
No, I don't want to do that.
I wanna be on the front lines
like you, bro.
- I wanna be, like, you know,
join the team or something.
- naw, it's really complicated.
- there's a lot of red tape.
You really can't--
- uh, excuse me, sir.
But just what in the hell
do you think you're doing?
Oh, dude. This is just
an acting gig.
Like, I'm not really
part of any cause.
- oh, you're an actor?
- mm-hmm.
- oh. But not a real one?
- what the hell is that
supposed to mean?
No, just-- I mean,
you're on the sidewalk.
Oh, right. Like you know
what you're talking about.
How old are you? Like, 40?
I live in new york,
okay?
Street theater is the only
organized artistic expression
that we have--
What a crock of shit, man!
You're living a lie, bro!
- dude, relax.
- oh, relax? Oh, I'm gonna--
You're gonna throw with me?
Little actor boy, you wanna
throw with a patriot?
- back off! Back off!
- I'm not 40.
- I don't need this.
- get in your van. Get in
your van and go, okay?
'cause I'll throw down!
I'll throw down
any day of the week!
Get in your little van
and drive out of my face! Okay?
Before I go america
all over your ass!
You know what?
Screw dee and charlie.
I'm sick of people telling us
what we can and can't do
with our own bar, you know?
What happened
to this country?
Why can't we stay open
past 2:00 a.M.?
Yes! And why can't
we sell booze
before noon on Sunday?
These are the kind of
puritanical restrictions
that are killing this country.
This is why people flock
to places like las vegas...
And new orleans
and spring break.
Because they're free
to go wild.
The girls go wild.
The girls in philly
need a place to go wild.
- right. New orleans was washed
away in that terrible storm.
- tragic.
We need to open up paddy's
as a haven for freedom.
Yes.
- a replacement for the
tragic loss of new orleans.
- we should have gambling too.
And we should have
gambling too.
Sure.
- I'm gonna get
the ball rolling.
- okay, great.
We will open up paddy's
as the most american bar
in all of america!
- a place with absolute freedom!
- with no gambling restrictions.
Yeah, sure, whatever.
Listen, dude. We should head
down to sorority houses, right?
Spread the word, you know?
Hand out some leaflets
or something.
No, mac. We should go
to the library.
The library? Why?
Yeah, because at sorority houses
you're gonna find nothing
but tramps and whores.
Those girls are
already wild.
Perfect!
No, no. Mac,
you're not listening to me.
We don't want
wild girls.
We want real girls
going wild.
It's important to see
the transition. You want
to watch the process.
Dee, what the hell
is the point of
this stretching?
Charlie, if we're gonna put
on our own demonstration,
Then your body needs
to be in tip-top shape
out there.
My body is in tip-top shape.
Well, maybe for a small,
fat person. Not for an actor.
Fat person?
A chunky-- chunky--
A chunky person?
Where are you getting that?
A husky person.
Since when? Oh!
Really?
You know what?
All right, forget it.
I'm not an actor anyway.
I know.
Yeah. Well, then
I'm a protestor, right?
I'm a patriot. Give me that.
Okay.
That's my bag.
What I need from you is for you
to feed me some lines.
I can feed you lines.
And then I'll go from there.
I just don't
need all the--
I can take over.
What do you want me to do?
Let's focus on
finding your breath.
What?
Where is your breath?
In my mouth?
No, it starts in your chest.
You got to focus
on your diaphragm.
What the hell's a diaphragm?
Right here.
Putting your diaphragm--
no. The diaphragm is a--
No. Really? That's all you know?
It blocks
the babies out.
Okay, yeah. That's what--
how'd you make it this far
in life?
Look, dee, this is ridiculous.
Let's just get out there.
Let's speak the truth.
Let's kick a little ass
america style.
We'll get all up in it!
I'm trying to protect you.
I don't want you
freezing up out there.
What? Freezing up?
Yeah.
All those people staring at you
and judging you...
And-and-and-and not liking
the stuff and talking about you.
Are you serious?
Yeah, I am.
Your body could betray you...
In any number of ways--
like how?
You know, one of--
locking up and maybe
throwing up and stuff.
- really?
- yeah. You want to
find your breath?
Yeah.
It's in my mouth.
[ together ]
one, two, three!
Hey!
Oh, my god!
You girls have gone wild!
You've gone wild!
You went wild!
You're wild!
Way to go!
You girls went wild!
Nice. This is what
it was like to have
a bar in new orleans, bro.
Oh, man! New orleans really
had their shit figured out!
Oh, they totally had
their shit figured out.
Yeah!
Except for the levees.
Right, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, and the evacuation plan.
Hey, oh!
Oh! You've gone wild!
You've gone wild!
You went wild!
This is what
america's all about!
This is america!
We have set up
an american utopia!
Yeah!
That could be
a bit of a problem
back there though.
[ chattering in vietnamese ]
[ mac ]
yeah, that could get weird.
Yeah, it's really smoky.
I didn't want to say it because
of the spirit of this whole
thing. But I think you're right.
It's a little much.
These fellows
don't mess around.
This is high-stakes shit.
You think you can get one...
Of these white broads to come
over and do a table dance
for alan and the boys?
No table dances, okay?
That's what we were
worried about.
Listen, frank. If you can
keep those guys as far jammed
into that corner as possible--
- push 'em into the corner.
- whoa, whoa, whoa. Segregation!
That's segregation! That's not
what this is all about.
America is a melting pot.
- but it might be good to
set up some boundaries.
- boundaries?
Sounds like it's coming
right out of stalin's mouth.
Stalin's mouth? That is not
what we're talking about.
We're just saying--
I don't know who stalin is.
Who the hell is stalin?
How do you not know?
Listen, man.
Just keep them under control.
You betcha. Oh, here.
They want you to play this
vietnamese music. They don't
like what's playing here.
Okay, listen. Compromise.
Tonight we keep things
the way they are.
Tomorrow night,
we'll play this shit.
Good. I gotta get back there
now because alan...
Is just about to bet
his wife's glass eye
in the next hand.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we are about to speak the truth.
We're not gonna spout a bunch
of words that are facts,
Like some big jerk from new york
who thinks he's great.
We're gonna show you
a dramatic interpretation.
[ clears throat ]
Hello, young man.
I'm a bigwig from big tobacco.
I work over here
at t.J. Boris. Can I offer
you a cigarette?
Goddamn it, charlie!
[ groans ]
[ vietnamese ]
[ chattering ]
Let's try and look
at the bright side here.
This music sounds like whales
raping each other.
It does. It does indeed.
But the t-shirts
are working.
Isn't that amazing? You ask
to see a woman's breasts
on the street, you get slapped.
You give her a free t-shirt
and videotape it, and
the clothes come right off.
I love this country.
Hey, yo!
Yeah.
Hey, sweetie.
You want a t-shirt?
Okay.
[ both ]
all right.
What? Why'd you stop?
What's wrong?
- what's wrong?
- what happened?
Whoa! Come on, pal!
Dude.
What are you doing?
You're blowing up our spot!
You're just standing there?
Take a walk!
[ sighs ]
maybe it's time
we set up some rules.
We can't do that. No rules.
Your father is killing
our freedom!
I know! I know!
Hey. Hey, you still want
that t-shirt?
Yeah.
Yeah? All right.
- okay, any time you're ready.
- okay.
Oh, what? What's wrong now?
Ruined again!
- whoa! Jesus!
- hey, man.
I thought you guys
were in jail.
Parole.
We heard you guys have
a, uh, "anything goes"
type situation here.
Can we get a couple glasses
of milk?
What? No.
No. You can't have milk.
You can't have milk. No.
Come on, man.
Oh, for-- you know what?
Get out of here.
Could you guys go over there
for a second? We gotta talk for
a second. If you could just--
What are we gonna do?
I did not see this coming.
We cannot have the mcpoyle
brothers in here creeping
everybody out.
What if charlie comes in here?
He sent them to jail. They
may be planning to stab him.
They bang each other,
dennis.
And they bang each other.
They bang each other's--
All right,
let's set up a couple rules.
We'll set up a couple rules.
Okay, guys, you can stay.
But none of your weird shit.
I don't follow.
All right, listen.
We've heard some things
about you two.
I'm not gonna get into
the specifics. We just don't
want it in the bar, okay?
It's a free country, bitch.
We may have a problem
on our hands, dude.
Do we have any sharp knives?
What?
These guys are maniacs. They
wanna start bettin' fingers.
Fingers?
What are you talking about?
If alan loses this hand,
he's gonna start chopping
off his fingers.
I've never seen anything
like it in my life!
This has gone way too far!
- this is getting ridiculous.
Your friends, they gotta go!
- bullshit!
You are killing
our freedom, man!
This is what
freedom's all about.
I'm living on the edge.
Okay, we're gonna find
a compromise here,
all right?
Uh, we'll take the bar and
you can have the basement!
Yes!
You want to put me
in the basement?
Yeah. You can do
whatever you want!
Anything goes in the basement!
- if I go in the basement,
I can do anything I want?
- anything you want!
- no holds barred?
There's no limits?
- no limits!
None.
All right.
I'll take the basement.
- great.
- and now, if you don't mind,
I'll take those knives.
All right. Get the knives.
Yeah. And use 'em.
[ sighs ]
What the hell
happened in here?
Looks like jonestown.
[ vietnamese ]
Oh, look who it is!
Come to join the party, huh?
- no. We came back to work.
- oh, have you?
I guess
the strike's over, mac.
The workers have returned.
Uh, I wasn't on strike, okay?
I still need to make a living.
What in the hell has been
going on in here? And where
is that music coming from?
From the basement. Frank
and the boys have been
rocking all night long.
- doing what?
- I have no idea.
But I bet it's fun.
We've had a line
of 50 people outside
every night.
Yep. See, our bar is
about fun and freedom.
I don't know if you guys
have ever heard of that.
Freedom?
Yeah. Stick around, bitches.
You might learn something about
the good old u.S. Of "a."
Hey, charles.
- holy shit!
- how's it hanging?
What? No! What? No!
What are these guys doing here?
Charlie, settle.
Yeah, man.
Chillax. We're cool.
Bump it.
No. I'm not gonna bump your--
please go.
No.
Please walk away.
Please walk away from me.
Walk away.
How could you
do this to me?
Okay, charlie. We don't want
them in the bar either, okay?
But freedom has a price.
The mcpoyles are
probably gonna stab me.
If freedom has its price--
I can't believe you guys!
You know what?
Let me kick down a little thing
to you that our founding fathers
kicked down to me.
It goes, "don't tread on me."
and right now you guys
are treading all over me!
Dee, let's roll.
I don't want
to go with you.
What?
Mm-mmm.
You're my actor.
I need you.
But you're so bad at protesting.
Come on, dee.
You're my actor.
I don't want to go.
Now you're treading on me!
I'm not treading on you.
Yeah, you are.
You're treading on me.
And you're not supposed to!
I don't want to go.
Are you kidding me?
Is everyone gonna tread on me?
Oh, my god. Okay. Okay.
I'm gonna rise up
I'm gonna kick a little ass
gonna kick some ass
in the u.S.A.
gonna climb a mountain
gonna sew a flag
gonna fly on an eagle
I'm gonna kick some butt
I'm gonna drive
a big truck
I'm gonna rule this world
I'm gonna kick some ass
I'm gonna rise up
I'm gonna kick a little ass
rock, flag and eagle
[ door opens, closes ]
so you're still trying
to be an actor then?
- shut your mouth, dennis.
- so now I can
call her a failure.
I am not a failure.
Dennis, what is it
that you call it...
When somebody tries to do
something but doesn't succeed?
Oh, yeah.
Uh, that would, in fact,
be a failure.
Dee's a failure.
Okay. You want
to see some acting?
You want to see some acting?
Guess what.
I am gonna act the shit
out of somebody's ass.
So here's the thing, artemis.
I know last time
we saw each other,
Things got kind of awkward
when you licked
my brother's face.
But I need some help
from an actor...
'cause I've been doing this gig
with my friend charlie, and
he is really bringing me down.
Oh. Not everyone
has the gift.
Hmm.
Want to smoke some hash?
No. Thank you.
So can you help me here?
What's the venue?
The sidewalk.
I don't do sidewalks.
Okay. See, that's
what I thought.
But then I realized
if you think about it,
Street performing,
it's the last true form of
organic artistic expression.
Is that so?
Yes. I think you and
I need to get out there.
We need to prove
to the world
that we still got it.
[ chuckles ]
sweet, sweet dee,
It's not something
you can lose, okay?
Right. So let's go
show the world.
Is there any nudity involved?
No.
Can there be?
I'll do it anyway.
[ country, slow ]
[ chattering ]
I don't understand this.
Mcpoyles.
Mcpoyles everywhere, dude.
Girls don't want to go wild
in this environment,
not even for t-shirts!
- hey, man. My sister wants
to ask you something.
- what?
- she's mute, dude.
- mute?
Okay, what?
She wants to show you
her boobies.
What?
No! No! No!
No. No.
Trust me.
They're top-notch.
Goddamn it! Goddamn it!
That is disgusting!
What is wrong
with you people?
That's your sister!
Hey, man.
There's nothing wrong with us.
We're just expressing ourselves.
Society has the problem.
Where do you keep
your pledge?
Get out of here.
Get the hell out of here.
Go away. Go with
your brother and sister.
Take a walk.
Dee, thank you so much
for this acting opportunity.
I can tell it is going to be
a glorious performance.
Those guys are full
of shit, artemis.
There's not 50 people here.
Focus, dee, focus!
But that's the reason
why we're here.
Those guys said there
would be a big crowd.
We'll draw them in.
All right.
Ladies and gentlemen, boys and
girls, please gather around.
You're about to see
an original
street performance.
Take yourselves
to the foggy streets
of london.
The year is 1888.
There's a killer on the loose.
His name, jack the ripper.
Two women walking alone home
from a holiday cotillion.
[ clears throat ]
I say--
Get out of here!
[ crowd gasps ]
If you come to this bar,
you're gonna get cancer and die!
What are you doing?
We're protesting the bar!
Attica! Attica!
Attica, man! Attica, man!
Attica, man! Attica!
What are you doing?
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Hey, man!
Tying off.
No! No! No!
Go tie off somewhere else!
I thought we could
do whatever we want.
Give me the hose.
Give me the little rubber hose.
Whoa, he's got a knife!
Okay, great.
He's got a knife.
Of course he does! Why not?
You know what?
Keep the little rubber hose!
Good luck with that.
Good life decision, man.
Mac, I think we gave people
too much freedom.
Yeah, you're right, man.
I'll call the cops.
No, no, no, no, no.
We can't call the cops.
That's admitting failure.
Dennis, we gave people
too much freedom.
That's the problem!
All they do is exploit it!
It's becomes anarchy. That is
not what america is all about.
No.
I mean, america is--
oh, my god!
Yeah.
[ gasping ]
Come on, dee!
Don't quit! Come on.
We just rocked out there, dee!
Oh, we did?
Yeah, we did.
Don't be a quitter. Okay?
I don't care. I don't want
to act anymore. I quit.
I want to drink.
That's what I would like to do
for the rest of my life.
Don't give up.
Why don't you leave me alone?
Can you imagine an america
where everyone just gives up?
I don't care.
Okay, great.
Let's just give up!
All right, charlie.
Have you come to gloat
and shove it in my face?
No.
No, it's okay. You can.
You know why?
'cause I give up. I'm living
in give-up america now.
What are you talking about?
- will you shut up?
- look at this!
I'm gonna be a smoker too.
You don't have to smoke,
charlie.
No, we can. You know why?
'cause we give up.
We live in give-up america.
I live in give-up america.
We're living in america--
hey, ryan.
How are you doing?
Look, man, I'm sorry
to interrupt you,
but if you're not too busy...
Showering in your
brother's urine or plotting
your revenge against me,
You mind lighting
my cigarette?
Thanks, bro. Hey, liam.
I'm sorry I sent you
to jail, man.
But any time you wanna stab me,
it'd be really great for me.
[ screaming ]
- that's what you get, charlie!
- whoa, hey! Get the hell
out of here!
- you get fork stabbed!
- get out!
- fork stabbed!
- [ both ]
get out!
And don't try to mess with us
'cause now we're even!
Get out of here!
Nobody messes
with the mcpoyles!
Oh, you had to make
a scene, charlie!
You had to run your mouth
in front of psychopaths,
didn't you?
-I just got stabbed with a fork!
-whose fault is that,
captain america?
- way to go!
- it's dee's fault
for quitting on me.
[ dennis ]
oh, it's dee's fault!
How is it--
Maybe it's your fault for being
horrible at everything!
Here we go with this again.
Everybody pass the buck!
Pass the blame!
Dennis, we have
to admit, it's over.
It's done.
We gotta get all
of these assholes
out of here right now.
Dee, you get everybody
out of the bar. Charlie,
you're a disappointment.
Come on. Let's go get everybody
out of the basement.
God only knows
what's going on down there.
[ sighs ]
[ men arguing, shouting ]
[ shouting in vietnamese ]
[ gun chamber spinning ]
[ vietnamese ]
[ cocks gun ]
[ gunshot ]
[ body thuds ]
[ men shouting ]
[ sighs ]
I'll call the cops.
Frank!
[ voice speaking backwards ]