But Miss Covington does not
govern the lady of the house.
If you'll have me as your husband,
that is what you shall be.
- Whoa!
- What?
Oh, my God. I did not see that coming.
Well, no... I mean, Lord Davenforth
and Anna the scullery maid?
I mean, that's... it's
kind of scandalous, really.
- Kind of scandalous?
- Yeah.
I usually hate this
old-time British crap.
- Oh, yeah.
- You know? But, like,
this-this show is amazing.
- Yeah.
- It's good. It's...
They actually knew that you would
love it 'cause of the algorithm.
The... the what?
The-the algorithm.
Yeah, all of our
previously-watched shows,
they go into a data bank, so
they can accurately predict
which shows you'll love moving forward.
So they knew what was gonna happen.
See, the algorithm, it takes thinking
- out of the equation, basically.
- Hmm.
Well, that's because math
and computers can think
better for us than we
can think for ourselves.
Yeah... ooh, shut up, shut up.
I-It's decided we're
watching another one.
Ah, I love that it does that, too.
Another thing I don't
have to think about.
You know what I mean? I-I...
What I am thinking about,
though, is the fish and chips.
The fish and chips.
- These snacks aren't cutting it.
- Where's Frank?
- I want substance. Where is Frank?
- Need something hearty.
- He supposed to be here...
- It is weird how, when
you watch stuff like this,
you feel like you want
to eat like the British.
Constantly want to eat like...
Cop! Cop!
- All right, fine.
- I'm filming this!
- Hey, hey, hey. Calm down!
- I didn't do it...
I came in to tell you there's
a suicidal man on the roof.
He's threatening to jump.
We have nothing to do with that!
Right. Well, the police are handling it,
but I need you to sit tight.
No one can enter or exit the building
until the situation is resolved.
- Oh...
- Okay. Thank you, ma'am.
- Thank you for your service.
- Yeah, we love,
- we love the police.
- Go blue.
Blue-Blue Lives Matter,
Blue Lives Matter.
Sh-Shit, man. You guys
know what this means, right?
What?
We're not gonna get our fish and chips.
Sync & corrections by Costa Dax
www.addic7ed.com
Shifting gears now, we have reports
of a developing
situation at Paddy's Pub.
- Oh, that's us. There we are.
- Hey. All right, there we go.
- We're on TV. Oh, my God.
- That's our bar.
A man by the name of Bryan O'Brien
is threatening to jump off the roof.
"Bryan O'Brien".
I'd kill myself, too,
if I had that clown's name.
You literally have the name of a clown.
- That's true, you do.
- All right, you know what?
This is moving a little too slow for me.
Let's-let's-let's click it back
- over to the show, yeah?
- Yeah!
Uh, whoa, h-hold on a second, Dennis.
Uh, this guy's gonna commit
suicide off of our roof.
I mean, shouldn't we do something?
- Us?
- Us do something?
- Why would we...?
- The cops are handling it.
- Yeah.
- Well, yeah, but I mean, look,
if he actually goes through
with it, that's a mortal sin.
I mean, maybe God is testing us.
He's not gonna do anything.
This is a classic cry for help.
If the guy actually
wanted to off himself,
he'd hop into a warm bath
and he'd do the old...
You know? North, south.
- Hmm?
He'd go "down the road"
instead of "across the street".
You know what I mean?
- I don't know what you mean.
- I have no idea what you mean.
The proper way to slit
your wrist is take a knife
and, ideally, you go from
metacarpal straight to bicep,
connecting with the artery
- the entire time.
- Oh, man.
- Oh, you've done research.
- Ugh.
- That is the most pathetic thing, Dee.
- No, I... I-I'm not talking...
we're not talking about me.
We're talking about him.
- Are we not? I think we're...
- We are now.
Okay, you know what?
The point is, I'm just saying,
the man has no intention
of offing himself, all right?
- This is a pathetic attention grab.
- Yeah, well,
it-it doesn't matter if he wants
do or he doesn't want to.
He's not gonna die
falling from that height.
Whoa. Hard disagree, pal.
You could absolutely die if
you jump from that height.
What? Dude, it's like three stories.
It's like basic science,
you know, like...
Uh, oh, I'm sorry. Let's
not bring science into it.
Okay? I mean, this is life or death.
This is God's territory.
All right? I mean, there is no science.
- All right.
- What do you mean...
What do you mean "there is no science"?
I mean, you were just talking
about how much you love
science and math for predicting
your television shows.
The... wh-why do you not
like it in this scenario?
Like, uh... do you either
believe in science
or you do not believe in science?
I am an American! I can
believe in whatever I want...
- I am also an American. Okay, though?
- ...in any given moment
based on what the argument
I'm trying to make.
- That is not an argument.
- Okay? You are not
a true American, Charlie.
I'm more American than
- you will ever be!
- You s...
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa. Simmer down, guys.
S... just simmer down, calm down.
All right? Dee, stop being so emotional.
Okay? So, guys,
I think I have a way that
we can solve this argument
without human emotion mucking it all up.
What we need is an algorithm.
Now, guys, we are living in a
data-driven world, are we not?
Yeah!
So this is my Behavioral
Predictor algorithm.
- Oh. There's words. Okay.
- Mm.
- So, first we have: "Could he?"
- No way, uh-uh.
- Then "Would he?"
- Nah. Cry for help.
- Mm-hmm.
- And "Should we?"
- Yes.
- Guys, please.
Shut the hell up!
I don't need your opinions.
Okay? 'Cause based on
the analytical conclusions
that we draw here, we're
gonna be able to come up
with a mathematically-accurate,
non-emotional answer
to all of our questions.
Okay? We just need to
think like a computer.
- Oh...
- Oh.
Like a computer does.
- I-I'm getting it now.
- Okay.
Exactly. So why don't we start
with "Could he?" Charlie?
- Okay, great.
- Do the thing.
All right. So, what we have here
is I made a little Paddy's Pub.
- All right.
- Ah.
And-and you got the, uh, the jumper?
Uh, I do. I do.
Uh, luckily I brought
an egg to work today.
- Oh! Look at that guy.
- All right, so when the guys falls,
we'll be able to tell,
based on the breakage,
what would happen to the jumper when...
- I think he's gonna smash.
- Y-Yeah, okay.
- Here we go.
- So, he's up here
and he's saying, "Oh,
- I feel so sad. Life is so..."
- Oh, yeah.
Oh.
Yeah, Dee, what would
you say in this situation?
Well, I don't think
he's sad, I think he's happy
to get off this merry-go-round.
Oh, my God.
- That's so pathetic.
- I'd never... I would never...
That you would know that.
- You've thought about it.
- You asked me a...
- You had that in the chamber.
- I'm talking about the egg.
- Here he goes. "Goodbye, world".
- Goodbye.
- Oh.
- Okay.
So I think he'll break a
leg, but, you know...
- Mm-hmm.
- ...he'll be okay.
Hmm.
If I'm being honest, I was
hoping his entire skull
- would just explode.
- Right.
I think we all were, Mac. We were hoping
- for a bit of an explosion. Yeah.
- Uh-huh.
Yeah, but I think what we
learned is that there's no way
that the jumper's gonna
die from this height.
You know? So there's no reason
for us to do anything about it.
Uh, I don't know about that, b...
I think the problem is, is that,
you know, an egg,
i-in this particular case,
a-a hard-boiled egg, it's not really
an accurate representation
of-of the human head
- and how it would behave under a fall.
- Yeah, that's true.
Now, Charlie,
do you happen to ha... I
know you've got more eggs...
- Yeah...
- Do you happen
to have an uncooked one?
Ugh. No. Unfortunately,
that was the only one I found.
Found? What does that mean?
Goddamn it, Dee, are you eating my egg?
Well, yeah. I got hungry.
- Oh...
- Uh, we never got our fish and chips.
You bitch. That was the
only one in the nest.
Nest? What? Charlie,
where did you get this egg?
- Where'd you get the egg?
- And why are you going around
stealing eggs from
goddamn nests in trees?
Well, it wasn't in-in a
tree, it was in a hole.
- Oh, no...
- Yeah. I mean,
it's, like, a rat's egg or something.
Can we get back to the task
at hand here? All right?
Okay.
Dee's eaten some sort of
a rat or a reptile's egg...
...of some kind,
- or whatever it is, but...
- Yeah.
...either way, we got to find something
that accurately represents
the human head, all right?
Otherwise, we're not gonna get
the explosion that we want.
Oh, you know what,
I might be able to get
Frank's secret casaba melon.
Mmm. Hmm?
Why does Frank keep a
casaba melon in the safe?
Hmm? I don't know, but he flips out
if I go anywhere near the thing.
Has he cut a hole in the rind,
and then put it back on, like a plug?
- Oh, yeah.
- Oh.
- Yeah, there's a little...
- You guys think he's
having sex with it?
- Well... yeah.
- He's definitely having sex with it.
Oh, that's...
Prob-Probably is.
- Yeah.
- Probably is.
- Hello.
Hey, guess what.
There's a guy stuck on
the roof of Paddy's.
Oh, no, he's not stuck, he's a jumper.
A jumper? You think you
could die from that height?
Uh, well, inconclusive. Yeah.
We'll have an answer for
you on that real soon.
Speaking of which, we
need your casaba melon.
We're gonna run a smash test on it.
Whoa, hold it. What, what, what?
Stay away from my stuff.
Don't put your hands near my casaba.
Yeah, hey, man, why do you have
a-a casaba melon in a safe?
You-you banging it?
It's none of your goddamn
business, Dennis.
- None of your goddamn business!
- Banging it.
- Yeah.
Damn it, I got to get in there.
Damn it.
Dennis is touching my melon.
No. I got to get in there.
Sir, move back. This
area's cordoned off.
There's a jumper on the roof.
You don't understand. It's my son.
He's gonna do something really stupid.
I got to get in there.
Oh, your son?
- Yeah.
- Come with me, sir.
- Okay.
- Step aside, please.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please keep a safe distance
- around the perimeter.
- All right, here we go.
Oh, okay, now, I think
this is finally gonna give us
that explosion we've been craving.
Well, yeah. Now, if we see splatter,
that's gonna prove that he
could die by jumping, so yeah.
Okay, ready? Here we go. Five...
Four, three,
two, one, ho...
- Cricket!
- Cricket.
- Where did you come from?
I was up on the roof
getting eggs from a nest.
What the hell? Come on, man.
Yeah, yeah, well,
I checked the hole, but it was empty.
- Oh, I got the one in the hole.
- The hole.
Hey, you know that you guys
have a guy up on your roof?
- Yeah, we know.
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
There's a guy, there's a jumper.
Guys, why the hell are you wasting
a perfectly good casaba melon?
We're trying to figure
out if the guy could die
from falling off our roof, so...
Oh, no way. No.
I've fallen off buildings
before; I never die.
And look at me. I'm doing great.
Yeah, but you're not
really a trustworthy
control group, Cricket.
I mean, you know,
you're sort of subhuman
at this point, you know.
- For sure.
- I don't know how
to squeeze that one into the algorithm.
Hey, I'm just going to, uh, take
the casaba and head on out.
No, you're not, Cricket.
- Get out of here, street rat.
- Go!
- Get out! Go.
- Fine.
Go get high in the
bathroom, or whatever.
Cricket actually just
made me realize something.
We already have data for this situation.
Maureen Ponderosa.
Now, she died from falling
off a much shorter building.
- Yeah, but you pushed her.
- No, no, no, they never proved that.
That was never proven.
It was never even proven
that she was pushed. Okay?
But it was, I have to say, fortunate
that she landed on her head, you know.
Or at least he certainly
made it look that way.
- He pushed her.
- Yeah, he pushed her.
No, I was following your threads.
Come on, you guys are nuts, all right.
Li-Listen, the point is, it's all about
how this guy falls, okay.
'Cause if he falls feet first,
he might break a couple bones,
sure, but he-he'll be fine,
he'll survive, you know what I mean?
That'd be more of a cry for help, right?
- Wouldn't you say, Dee?
- Oh, absolutely. Yeah.
- So sad that you know that.
- Stop!
But if the guy falls head first,
now that'd be a death jump.
Right? So the answer to the question
"could he die from jumping?"
Yeah, absolutely, if
he did a death jump.
Okay, you're right. It's how he falls.
Exactly, exactly. But
the question still remains:
would he jump, would he do it at all?
And for that we need to
understand his state of mind.
And for that, we got to
go back to the algorithm.
All right, so how does
one go about figuring out
what another human being would do?
Right? How do you truly
get to know someone?
- Just go through their trash.
- Sleep with them.
- Oh.
- Uh, talk to their priest,
then sleep with their priest.
Then blackmail the priest.
Then go back to the priest
and ask him to ask God
to forgive you for blackmailing him.
No. No.
You just, uh...
We're just gonna pull up Bryan
O'Brien's social media page,
and we're gonna comb
through that for any
pertinent information on his life.
Okay, so from what I'm seeing here,
he looks like a pretty normal guy.
Yeah, it looks like he likes to travel.
He was recently on a cruise.
Lot, lot of pictures
of food. I love that.
- Oh, I love that.
- Don't you love that?
- 'Cause I know what I ate.
I don't know... I want
to know what you ate.
It's a good reminder
that food is a thing.
- Yeah, exactly. Right.
- You know what I mean?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Okay, so it looks like
he's got a lot to live for.
- He's eating food.
- Mm-hmm.
Or-or-or is he?
Because is... is that just what
he wants you to believe?
You know, because we all
know that on the surface,
social media... it's a lie.
All right, so let's dig
deeper, shall we?
Now, clock the amount of baseball caps
this guy's wearing, and
with the tucked-in shirts,
it's a bit of a juvenile
look for a man his age,
wouldn't you say? I mean,
he's hardly a child,
but he's still hanging on to his youth.
That suggests to me that maybe
he's got some daddy issues.
- Mm-hmm.
- Abandonment, abuse.
Plus, he gave him a comical
name, like Mac's dad did.
His dad hates him as much
as Mac's dad hates him.
That's so sad.
No, my dad loves me. That...
No, my name's an homage.
- No, it's not. He really doesn't.
- My dad's name's an homage.
It's an homage to a hamburger clown.
But, uh, oh, look at this,
looks like he also, uh,
just got back from a cruise,
alone, to mainland Alaska. Oh.
- Lame.
- Where he met himself an edgy woman
at a conference, and she introduced him
to a whole new way of life:
parasailing, Chilean wines, a tattoo
of Spider-Man, butt-eating...
Butt-eating? Where are
you getting that from?
Well... there's a certain glint
in the eye, you know, a sparkle.
You can see that in someone's eye?
- Oh, Dee.
- I'm asking.
- Have you been eating butts?
- Of course she has!
- Nasty!
- You are too much today, Dee.
- I was clarifying.
- You're nasty.
- Too much.
- I just was curious.
But recently the girlfriend,
she's disappeared
from his pictures, which tells me that,
uh, she probably broke up
with him, you know, because
of all his father issues,
and 'cause he's an alcoholic,
and because of the copious
requests for butt-eating,
which, she was thinking was
more of a one-time thing,
and he was thinking, this is a
thing now, like, from now on.
You got him. Nice work, man.
- Yeah. Geez.
- That sums this guy up, I think.
All right, guys, so in summation,
algorithm-wise, what have
we learned here today?
- That Dee's a nasty fucking slut.
- You are so nasty.
- Okay, all right.
- You nasty!
- Disgusting.
- Definitely, definitely,
but also that the poorly named
Bryan O'Brien most definitely
would kill himself.
- No-no-no...
- So has your son exhibited
this kind of behavior before?
What? Oh, yeah, he's a
real deranged person.
This kid's a real whack job.
I'm afraid he's gonna do
something really stupid
this time. I got to get in there.
- I can't let you do that, sir.
- But-but, look, it might've been
my fault. I mean, we had an argument...
I assure you we're doing all we can.
We're trying to talk to him now.
- So just stay put.
- But-but, hey...
Excuse me, sir, I'm Jackie Denardo
from Channel Five News.
♪ Oh, oh, whoa. ♪
I hear you're the father.
I would love to interview you.
Baby, I'll do anything you want.
My son is actually a big fan of yours.
- Oh.
- I mean, it would
really get under his skin
if he knew I was standing next to those.
Uh, you. You.
Okay, guys, now we
are on to "Should we?"
Should we get involved
in this in any way?
Is it our moral obligation, as Mac says,
to keep this man from committing suicide
- and going to hell...
- What... I feel... I don't know.
I still think we just better, like,
- let the cops do their jobs.
- Mm-hmm.
Mm, I don't know. But
we've already established
that this guy could die and would jump,
so, I don't know, the chances
of the police getting in there
in time to-to stop this guy
are, uh, pretty slim.
And then we could be
known as a suicide bar,
and that's no good.
I don't want to be that.
Yeah, kind of grim. I'd probably
take my business elsewhere.
You don't have business.
Oh! What, uh, what if you
lean into that, though?
Right? Like, you don't make it
grim, but you make it playful.
Like, we start to name drinks
after jumpers or whatever,
like, uh, The Last Call.
The Jump Shot.
Lemon Drop.
- Right.
- Oh. There you go.
Cosmo-fall-itan?
- Oh!
- Very good.
We could become, like,
a hot spot for jumpers.
You know? We'd put their
pictures up, all around the bar
- to immortalize them, you know?
- Oh, yeah.
Turn them into martyrs.
That's cool. And we'd play
music. We'd play music.
Uh, "Highway to Hell". "Free Fallin'".
"Free Fallin'". Come on, man. That's...
You know what we could do?
We could lean into, like,
a-a haunted, a haunted house
- kind of bar theme, like... you know?
- Oh, well, I'm loving that.
- Yeah, that'd get my business back.
- You don't have business,
- Cricket.
- You don't have business, guy.
Basically, what we've concluded
is that it would actually
be good for the bar if
this guy jumps and dies.
Yeah? So the answer to the question
of "should we get involved?"
is... is actually yes.
- Huh? Why, though?
- Yeah, but-but
if-if we stop him, that would be
bad for the bar, right, Dennis?
W-Well... No, that's not
what I'm saying, though.
More importantly, that's not
what the algorithm is saying.
You see, we've already
established that this guy wants
to die and that it would
actually benefit our bar
if he dies.
Now, of course, from an
emotional standpoint,
we feel as though we
should get involved,
should save this guy,
but the algorithm is actually telling us
that that does not benefit anybody.
- Hmm.
- The algorithm is telling us,
mathematically, scientifically,
that this guy could die, wants to die,
and that we should help him do it.
That's just math.
- Oh.
- Hmm.
Well, it still feels a little weird,
but feelings are irrelevant
in the face of facts.
- Yeah.
- Is that what I'm hearing?
The feelings... feelings
just get in the way.
Now, but here's-here's
the only thing, though.
Like, if we were gonna
do something like this,
- like...
- Mm-hmm?
...you know, how would we do it?
Like, in the right way?
Do we need to do another
algorithm to figure this out?
Eh.
- Nah, I'll push him.
- Huh?
What's that?
Yeah. I'll push him off the building.
I don't give a shit.
This is such a difficult
situation for any parent.
Yeah.
If you could, would you like
to say anything to your son?
Oh, yeah. Look, you think
you can do whatever you want,
but what's mine is mine.
You don't have a call.
If I want to bang it, I'm gonna bang it.
Not that I am banging it, but I could.
And if it doesn't splatter to bits,
I'm gonna bang it later.
Because it's my property.
And what I do with my
property is my business.
- You got that?
- I-I'm sorry to interrupt,
but we have breaking news.
- Eh.
- I've gotten word
- the jumper is coming down.
- Oh.
I've been told he found out
his estranged father is here
- and he wants to come down and talk.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. He's call...
- He's calling me strange?
- Wait, wait...
You don't know what
this sicko kid has done.
Okay, Cricket, uh, here's a broom.
You probably sneak up there,
give him a little nudge,
and, uh, you know,
don't let anyone see you
- commit the murder.
- Whoa, uh...
Guys, can-can we just
not call it a murder?
Let's try to think of
it more analytically,
more mathematically.
It's sort of like a deletion.
You know? Like hitting
Control-Alt-Delete.
Bloop. He's in the trash.
- Oh, that's all it is, right?
- I like that.
- That works for me.
- Uh-oh.
Blip. He's gone.
Breaking news right now. Uh,
there's some clarification.
The jumper did not jump. He
did not jump from the roof.
He is coming down the stairs.
G... oh, dude, that's... What a gyp.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- We were gonna... we had a good plan.
Can I say something, though?
I think this is for the best.
Right.
- You know what I mean?
- Probably.
That's not the algorithm...
- Right.
- Like, we were going down a road
- I was not totally comfortable with.
- Ooh, ooh, ooh.
You guys want to go back
to watching our show?
- Let's get back to our show.
- Right?
The show.
- All right.
- Why are we watching this stuff?
- Okay. Yeah, okay.
- The guy didn't even jump.
That's boring.
Chet, what we are about to witness here
is a father being reunited with
his son after a harrowing day.
- Here he is now.
- Yeah. Hey...
This isn't my dad.
That's not Dennis.
I thought you said you were the dad.
Not of this sad sack.
I'm sorry, kid. Must've been a mix-up.
I got distracted by the
reporter's bagonzas.
Speaking of melons, there's a casaba
with my name on it in there.
Dear Anna, our time apart only
makes my heart grow fonder.
- In the dead of night...
- Oh!
Hey, you got our fish and chips?
- Ate 'em.
- Uh...
- You ate 'em?
- Wow.
Hey, wait, wait.
- Where's my melon? Where's my casaba?
- Oh...
It's right here, man. Why do you
care so much about this thing?
- What is the deal?
- Ah...
Yeah, what is the deal with that?
- Ugh.
- Oh.
- Ah...
- Oh, God.
Ugh!
It's where I stash my Maui Kush.
- You hide your weed in a casaba melon?
- Yeah.
In case the cops ransack the place,
you got to find a good,
unsuspecting spot
to stash your drugs.
Pot's pretty much legal now.
You don't really have
to stash it anywhere.
I-I don't think you
have to hide it, man.
When did that happen?
- Can you move?
- You're blocking our show, man.
Yeah.
- Come on, man.
- You're blocking the show.
I didn't know that.
What? You're still
watching that British show?
I mean, that's a bunch of crap.
- It stinks.
- Uh...
Uh, well, no, actually,
the algorithm told us that we like it.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Yeah. And-and, um...
- Yeah.
- I don't. You know what I mean?
Like, I can't follow what
they're saying most of the time.
Thank you for saying that.
I find it very boring.
- Okay, now, I...
- It is boring, right?
I hate the plot because it's absurd.
The plot is ridiculous.
- Right? The scullery maid?
- And their teeth,
I find them hard to look at.
The teeth are a little bit of
a mess, but mathematically
- we're supposed to like the show.
- Uh, yeah,
I know, but mathematically
we were supposed to kill a man today.
Maybe that's, like, part of the problem
of, like, taking the
humanity out of decisions.
Perhaps the science
just isn't there yet.
Hey! Where did we land on the casaba?
I-I think you can eat it, man.
I think we're done with it.
- Yeah, we're done.
- Yeah.
Oh!
- Yeah, baby.
- Eh.
I wouldn't eat it, Cricks.
It's full of loads.
Sync & corrections by Costa Dax
www.addic7ed.com