[ mac ]
hey-o! What is up, bitches?
[ dee ] I'm trying to
revamp my myspace page,
but dennis keeps criticizing...
Every move
that I make.
What is that?
What in the hell
is a myspace page?
It's, like, that friends forum.
These things are pretty awesome.
You create a profile,
put your picture on there--
Other people send you pictures
and want to be your friend.
Oh. So that's the saddest
thing I've ever heard.
You guys are losers.
How are we losers, dude?
Well, maybe it boils
down to this, smart guy.
Computers are for losers.
You're drinking a beer
at 8:00 in the morning.
Whatever, dude. Irrelevant.
[ dee ]
holy shit!
This guy's been
trying to contact me for,
like, two weeks now,
And I've just been
blowing him off.
But he's saying
that he's our dad.
Awesome. Crazy person.
Let me see.
No. Not awesome. Because look
at the pictures he's sending.
- oh! Oh, look at that!
- see?
That's your mom, dude!
There's, like--
There's, like, a ton of pictures
of this guy and your mom.
Oh, you know what?
He does kind of look
like you, dennis.
Don't jump to
any conclusions here.
This is bullshit!
You guys have two dads,
and I don't even have one.
Yeah! That is bullshit!
We don't even have one.
Wh-what are you talking about?
You have a father.
Yeah. But he's in prison.
He's been there my whole life.
It doesn't count.
That does count!
I never met my father!
Take it easy, all right?
This guy's not our dad.
I don't know.
This is really
freaking me out.
Look, dee,
this guy can't be our dad.
That's ridiculous.
Is it?
Is it any more ridiculous
than our dad having brown eyes,
Black hair and being 4'10"?
This is really
a nice place.
It's about time you kids
show me some respect.
It doesn't really have
anything to do with respect.
We just wanted to take you
to a fancy place so that
you would behave yourself.
- yeah, yeah.
- we need to talk to you
about something, dad.
- shoot.
- it's kind of disturbing.
You two aren't banging,
are you?
What?
No! What are you
talking about?
- that's disgusting.
- yeah. Yeah, it is.
Stay away from that
kind of thing. No good
can come of it. Trust me.
That's not what
we're here to talk about.
It better not be,
Because I don't want no--
[ grunts ] grandkids.
- I am not banging my sister.
- jesus christ!
What have I walked into here?
- oh, my god.
- you two aren't
having sex together?
No, we're not
having sex together.
What the hell is she doing here?
-sit down, please, mom. Sit.
-I am not getting pulled into
any sort of perverted sex talk.
- it's not perverted.
- banging your sister
is perverted, dennis.
I am not banging my sister!
[ sighs ]
god!
Can you just sit, please?
Please sit in the chair.
Frank.
Barbara.
Your turkey neck is looking
exceptionally attractive
this evening.
You have turned into
a retarded person.
You're a retard.
Can we use
some adult language,
just for a couple minutes?
Let's get to it.
There's this guy bruce
who contacted dee on myspace,
And he's claiming to be
our biological father.
We just wanted to ask
the question and just get it
out of the way.
Is there a chance that
that could be possible?
No.
Yes.
What?
Well, bruce who?
Bruce mathis?
- yeah.
- then, yes.
- there's a chance this guy
could be our father?
- no. Yes, he is your father.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Do we really have to
get into all of this?
- my god! Yes.
- yes, we really have to
get into all this!
Everybody settle down.
It's not the end of the world.
A long time ago, I met bruce
and we had this little affair,
or whatever you want to call it.
Long story short,
he got me pregnant,
and I had to make a decision.
Seeing as he had no money,
I decided that the best thing
for everyone...
Was if I didn't tell bruce
and let your father think
that the twins were his.
End of story.
End of story?
How could you do that?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Would you rather
I had them aborted?
- children, would you
like to have been aborted?
- I can't believe this.
I just can't believe this!
Okay, dad.
Keep your voice down.
You whore!
Keep it down, okay?
Please don't make
a scene.
Don't make a scene.
Sit back down.
Oh, no! I'm not gonna
make a scene!
I was just told,
excuse me,
That my horrible,
whore wife...
Has tricked me into
raising two bastards...
For 30 years,
and I'm being asked
to not make a scene!
Whoa! Oh, excuse me?
Oh, did you bang my wife?
Huh?
Did you bang my whore wife?
Does anybody here have
any illegitimate children
with my whore wife...
- that I should know about?
- jesus, frank!
Jesus! Jesus, frank!
Jesus, frank!
Jes-- oh! Jesus, frank!
My life is a lie!
Somebody's got to get stabbed!
Somebody's got to get sta--
No--
sta-- sta--
[ grunts ]
Let's get out of here.
[ mac ]
so, dad.
Kind of a funny story.
Turns out my friends got
some weird news the other day
about their biological father,
And it got me to thinking,
uh, about maybe, you know,
reconnecting with mine.
Uh-huh.
And, you know,
charlie never had a father.
And, uh, I thought that
maybe the three of us...
Could all become, like--
like, friends or something.
Really? Well, okay.
I'll tell you what.
Maybe I got something for you.
- it's a father-son
type of thing, huh?
- yeah.
You see, I got a little
business I been running in here
the last couple of years.
I was thinking of expanding,
and I'm gonna need some people
on the outside.
Some really badass,
tough guys.
I like where
you're going with this.
I think you came
to the right place.
What do you guys
know about...
Smuggling heroin
through your anus?
[ mac ]
you definitely look good.
That's not what I'm saying.
I just think you need to
tuck it in in the back.
In the back?
Yeah. You button
the top button and then
they tuck it in in the back.
It is tucked in the back.
Is it?
Is it bunchy?
It's not bunchy.
Let me see.
That's exactly it.
How do I look?
That's gonna impress
your dad, right?
It is gonna impress my dad.
You piece of shit!
You no-good piece of shit!
Whoa, whoa, frank!
What's going on in here?
What happened?
- I had a minor stroke.
No big deal.
- what's with the gun, dude?
I'm trying to find
the son of a bitch
who fathered my children.
- what? By doing myspace?
- yeah. And I did everything
they said to do.
I put a picture, a profile.
The thing won't tell me
where the bastard lives.
Did you send him
a friend request?
I don't want to be his friend.
I want to shoot him in the face.
Can you help me?
No. You--
yes, absolutely.
But no killing.
- needs to be killed.
- doesn't need to be killed.
He could take
a good ass whupping.
And we're down with that.
Are you crazy?
No, dude!
Give us one second here.
Charlie.
This is our opportunity
to prove to people
that we are to be respected.
No one is more respected
than dudes in prison, right?
Yeah.
And what are dudes in prison?
Hard?
Right. This is our chance
to get hard.
Okay. I just don't know if this
is the best way to get hard.
Of course it is.
This is totally hard.
You want to get hard,
don't you?
I want to get hard.
I want to get very, very hard.
Do you want to shove
heroin into your ass?
I don't want to shove
anything in my ass.
This is the perfect opportunity
to prove how hard we are and not
shove anything into our asses!
What in god's name
are you two talking about?
Frank, we're in.
Great.
[ gunshot ]
Oh, god!
This is so weird.
I'm really nervous.
I really hope
he's not an asshole.
I don't think I can handle
two asshole dads.
Are these my beautiful children?
I just-- I can't believe
what a miracle this is
after all these years.
[ both chuckling ]
oops.
You know, I loved your mother
more than I can say.
And I'm sure she had her
reasons, but she never told me.
Yeah. Well, this whole thing
is very strange for all of us.
Yeah.
We've got a lot to catch up on.
Yeah. Tell us
about yourself.
Yeah.
Where to begin, uh--
I met your mom here in,
uh-- in philadelphia.
It was just before I shipped off
to alaska with greenpeace.
I do a lot of environmental work
and work with kids.
Mm-hmm.
And we were in alaska.
And then we went to africa,
to the sudan.
We-- here.
This-- this is
my adopted family.
Oh.
[ dennis ]
you adopted them?
Yup. In fact, um--
huh.
Hello. Those are your brothers
and sisters.
Your family just got
a little bigger today.
It sure--
it sure did.
You want to know their names?
No. We'll do that later.
We'll do that later because
it's-- it's hard to remember.
Okay, thank you very much.
And anything here,
at all times, is yours.
Anything in my life is yours.
- these are cool speakers.
- yep. They're yours.
Take 'em. Take 'em.
No, no.
I was kidding.
It was just a joke, I think.
But if you want them, just--
uh-- africa.
Yes. Yes, africa.
Right? Sudan.
I went from the sudan--
I was in darfur.
We had a water-purification
program there. So much work
to be done there.
And then I-I--
I spent a little time
in afghanistan.
We were doing
a literacy program for women
who were resisting the taliban.
Well, for better or worse,
I came back here
a couple of years ago.
And I think it was for better,
'cause I'm doing this work,
Uh, starting some programs
for sacred cross hospital,
which I think is very promising.
And-- ah!
My story is boring. I--
What about you?
What are your passions?
You know, what are you doing
with your lives?
There's been a lot of--
Oh, so many things
we do.
Phases.
Oh, god.
Where do you begin?
Yeah.
- something like--
- I know. I know. It's--
- a lot of different--
- chapters.
- kinds of--
kinds of things.
- I want to hear anyth--
Just tell me chapter one.
Well, a lot of this kind
of stuff, right here.
Yeah.
These guys.
A lot of--
these guys
are important to us.
I guess the apple doesn't
fall far from the tree.
[ frank ]
son of a piece of shit!
Hey, you gotta
relax there, frank.
Seriously, bro.
You're gonna have
another stroke.
He won't make me his friend.
How am I gonna find him if
he won't make me his friend?
Be patient.
It's a process.
Yeah, bro. Come on.
It's been days.
I got no friends.
- stop saying that.
You have friends.
- I got you. I got this guy tom.
And that crazy woman who claims
we had a one-night stand
30 years ago.
Right, yeah.
Tom doesn't really count though.
He kind of, like, comes with it.
Screw this!
I'm gonna just follow
dennis and dee around.
Sooner or later, they're
gonna bump into this bastard.
And we're gonna just jump him
and beat him over the head
with a baseball bat!
Frank, come on.
They're gonna see that
coming a mile away.
Man, we need to be more devious,
more cunning!
Uh, that's not very hard.
That's some weak ass-buster
shit, bro.
This bastard
destroyed my lineage.
He must be smashed.
We're gonna smash him, friend.
We're gonna smash him good.
We know people.
Look, frank, uh,
we know a guy on the inside
we can talk to.
He might be willing to help us
out with the situation here.
[ chuckles ]
You guys are fast.
I'm proud of you.
- thanks, dad.
- okay. Now, here's how
it's gonna work.
I'll have a guy
meet you in the bathroom
in about 10 minutes.
Now he doesn't mind
sifting through the feces,
so don't hold back.
Uh, yeah, here's the thing
about that, dad.
We don't have anything
in our butts.
No. We don't have
anything in our butts.
We're working on that.
But we're still hard.
Yeah. Oh, you should see
how hard we're getting.
Oh, we are getting so hard.
It's, like-- whew!
We actually came by
'cause we need your help.
Yeah.
Let me get this straight.
You come to me empty-handed
and you want my help?
Yeah. And, look, we are really,
really sorry about that, dad.
But if you could give us
some advice on how to handle
a certain situation,
Then we promise
we will come back
with our butts filled.
Oh, so filled.
So filled for you.
We need to find our friends'
father so that we can give
him a serious beating.
Oh, we're gonna
kick the crap
out of this guy.
And check it out.
We can't find him.
All right. All right.
Why don't you just follow
your friends around for a while?
They're bound to contact him
at some point.
When they do,
just jump him.
Beat him
with a baseball bat.
That's pretty badass.
That could work.
Now, you listen to me.
Do not come back here...
Without anything
up those asses!
Okay?
[ together ]
okay.
save the children
save, save, save, save, save
save, save, save, save
save the children
Thank you! Thank you.
Thank you, philadelphia.
The juvenile lupus association
thanks you, and the children
thank you.
Oh, saving the kids, huh?
Yeah, I guess.
Those little angels,
they're the future.
[ chuckles ] that's my dad
up there. He put this
whole shindig together.
Really?
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Well, I mean,
I helped, of course.
I mean, this whole
lupus nightmare has gone
on long enough,
You know?
Yeah.
Ladies and gentlemen,
sometimes a father
has the privilege...
Of playing a little music
with his daughter.
Would you please welcome
deandra reynolds?
[ indistinct ]
I believe the children
are our future
Juvenile lupus association.
What a bunch of bullshit.
Mac, I got one question
for you.
What?
What's the plan again?
Are you kidding me?
I swear, charlie,
you're, like, a retard.
What we're gonna do is we're
gonna bash him with the bat
when he comes out.
You want to huff
some of this glue with me?
No! Put the glue away!
Please. Huff a little
with me, dude.
All right, fine.
Fine!
We just need to
keep an edge.
We got to stay hard, dude,
because you can't do it if--
This is elmer's glue,
for christ sakes, charlie!
if I fail
if I succeed
at least I live
as I believe
no matter what
they take from me
they can't take away
my dignity
because the greatest
Do you have the camera?
Yeah, I got the camera!
I just don't know
what it's for, mac!
I'm gonna bash you with this!
When he comes out,
I'm gonna smash his face.
You're gonna take a picture.
We're gonna show it to my dad--
Show it to your dad.
To prove how hard we are!
find your strength
in love
Whoo!
Oww!
No, dude.
We shouldn't do this.
I'm backing out.
You can't back out.
Frank is waiting in the car.
He's gonna be pissed
if we don't finish the job.
Let frank wait in the car.
We owe this to him.
This guy banged frank's wife.
So did you.
Yeah, but it's different.
How is that different?
I don't know, charlie!
Focus!
[ gasps ]
there they are.
Just relax, dude.
He's hugging them.
They're hugging him back!
- [ charlie ] this is crazy.
We shouldn't do this.
- we should bash all three.
[ mac ] this is it.
Let's go. You ready?
Don't be a pussy.
Let's go.
Oh, my god!
[ gasps ]
Oh. Hi.
Hi.
Can I help you?
Uh, okay.
Um--
[ inhaling, exhaling ]
It's-- it's okay.
It's okay.
I got it.
Have a good night.
What the hell
was that shit?
What did you do?
I freaked out.
You totally freaked out!
You just left me--
I was gonna hit him.
You left me standing there.
I took a picture of the guy.
Hey!
What?
Snap out of it! Okay?
Okay! Yes.
Now we got to think of
something to tell frank.
Okay.
Hey! Look at me.
Yeah?
Ow!
[ inhaling, exhaling ]
Let's tell him the truth.
- blood! Blood!
There's so much blood!
- what happened?
We bashed him good!
We bashed him so good!
I think we killed him.
Drive! Drive! Drive!
[ tires squealing ]
Jesus, children!
This isn't exactly what
mommy needs right now.
No. No, no, no.
Mom, bruce is so awesome. He--
We had the best time
last night.
Bruce is the coolest.
We went to this lupus event
last night. Lupus is awesome!
Amazing.
You should give bruce
another chance.
[ bruce ] barbara.
My god.
You still look amazing.
[ barbara ] wow.
[ chuckles ]
the years have treated you well.
I would have thought
living in poverty
for a quarter of a century...
Would have taken its toll.
Well, when father died,
I was left with all that money.
There's only so much
you can give away before
you finally realize...
It's okay to spend
a little on yourself.
On you.
Yeah, on me.
Father? Wealthy?
I never knew.
I guess it never came up.
So you guys ready?
I am!
[ chuckles ]
I'm up for anything.
Okay.
But first things first.
Oh.
Yeah.
Let's just put these on.
One for you.
One for me.
Great.
Okay, let's go spread some joy.
Right. Uh--
Ooh. Okay. Um, hey.
Hey, pal.
How-- how you feeling?
It hurts everywhere.
Well--
well, it--
everything's gonna be okay.
You don't know that, deandra.
Shut up, mother.
I don't think we should be
lying to the sick children.
I was trying to be encouraging.
What if he doesn't get better?
You're gonna look like a fool.
I gotta say I agree with dee.
The kid's gonna die anyway.
What difference does it make?
I can hear you.
Oh, you heard--
well, you know what?
Disregard that.
Yeah. You know, we weren't
even talking about you.
No. No.
We were talking about
your sick and dying friend
in the next bed.
Mother!
What are you doing?
Nothing!
Oh, my god!
- you can't steal
the children's medication.
- I'm not.
Let me see in your purse!
Open your purse up!
Don't be ridiculous!
[ dee ] really?
Everything okay over here?
Yes.
A slight glitch here.
Um, this is really kind
of bumming me out here.
Yeah, this is not fun.
Yes. I'm not exactly sure what
it is we're trying to prove.
We're not
trying to prove anything.
We're just helping the kids.
Who are we really helping?
Yeah?
I'm not sure I understand
what you mean.
Well, listen, it's one thing
to rock out, raise some cash.
But it's a totally different
thing to put our lives at risk.
Oh, yeah. I mean,
there's all these diseases
floating around in here.
Yes. I mean,
how can we help anyone
if we're all getting sick?
- I mean, use your head.
- plus, it's freezing in here.
You think you could talk
to somebody about cranking
the heat up a little?
- this isn't good for us.
- you're not serious?
I don't think it's a lot
to ask to have them turn
the temperature up.
It's easy.
You just push a button
or, like, crank a thing over.
Are you guys getting hungry?
Oh, yes.
I am starving.
Yeah, I could eat.
Is there a cafeteria
in the hospital?
No, come on. Gross.
I'm not eating in
a hospital cafeteria.
That's a good point.
Brucie, do you know a nice
restaurant in the area?
I'm gonna want
those noses back.
Please.
Give it a rest with
that martyr nonsense.
Yeah. Who is he? Patch adams?
You know who never acts
like he cares about kids?
Dad.
[ mac ]
all right, buddy.
Baking soda, lube, balloons.
This is how it's gonna go.
I'm gonna jam this
into your rectum.
And then, woo!
Like that, it's gonna expand
in your colon, okay?
It's gonna be that big?
Absolutely. You ready?
Drop those pants.
Hey, guys.
What do you think?
That's a good look.
That's a good look for you.
Where're you headed?
I tell you what, I feel like
a hundred dollars.
Ever since you guys beat that
guy up, I got to thinking.
Hey, what am I gonna do? Huh?
Dive into some kind
of depression over this? No.
I'm gonna jump
right back on the horse.
So I contacted that woman
on myspace who claimed that
we had a one-night stand.
Turns out she's single
and ready to go.
Give me some skin.
Good work.
[ knocking ]
there you go, frankie!
- that might be her.
Mac, get the door.
- let me clean this up.
Hide that balloon.
That's gonna kill your date.
- where's my dad?
- so he's your dad now--
- get out of the way.
- daddy.
Don't daddy me. You blew
your chances with this daddy.
You're dead to me.
No. Just listen for
a second here, okay?
No. No.
We've had a change of heart.
We've decided to forgive you...
And to allow you
to be our father again.
I'm not into
being your dad anymore.
Don't want to be your dad.
Uh, kinda giving you
a second chance here, dad.
Daddy, yeah.
- no. I'm over it.
- you can't be over it.
No, no, no.
I'm over it.
He can be over it.
Will you shut up?
What is with you two?
- I am over over over it!
- you're not allowed
to be over it!
[ knocking ]
[ dee ]
I can yell at him!
Shh.
Charlie?
Hey, mom.
What-- what are you
doing here?
- I'm confused.
Do you live here?
- yeah.
- bonnie?
- frank!
How do you guys
know each other?
[ both giggling ]
This is my date.
[ mac ] whoa! Wait a second.
I thought...
You were going on a date
with a woman you had a one-night
stand with 30 years ago.
Yeah.
So if you guys had
a one-night stand 30 years ago,
and I don't--
You know, I don't
know who my... Father--
You could be my--
Dad?
[ voices speaking backwards ]