Hey, you guys,
what are you doing tonight?
What the hell kind
of question is that?
Yeah, you're asking us
to predict the future, Dee.
How can I predict the future?
Well, there's a new martini
bar opening up downtown.
I thought maybe we could do
something different tonight.
Where is this shit coming from?
She just watched that stupid
"Sex and the City" movie.
Oh, my God,
when will that show die?
Never, apparently.
Dee, you tried this shit 30 years ago
when that show first came on the air.
Nobody wants to play
"Sex and the City" with you.
Come on, Charlie.
You know you did it.
- Fess up!
- I did not poop the bed!
- Rewind.
- What?
I'm sorry.
Did you say something about
pooping in a bed?
Yeah, there was some poop
in our bed this morning.
Oh, Jesus.
And Charlie did it.
That is bullshit!
Guys, hold on a second.
Relax!
Walk us through what happened.
Nice and slow.
Well, yesterday we wake up and
there's a piece of poop right
in the middle of
me and Frank, okay?
Wait a minute, so this happened
two nights in a row?
So we threw the first piece of
poop out 'cause big deal, whatever.
Accidents happen, right?
But then this morning, there's another
piece of poop in the exact same spot
Now, Frank says it's not him.
I say it's not me, but you bet
your ass it's one of us.
This is a lot to handle.
Now, the second poop,
you held onto it, right?
Brought it along.
Dee, when we said we can't
predict the future, how could we
possibly have seen something
this awesome coming?
Yeah, we're going to have
to clear our schedules.
What?!
This is going to require
a lot of attention.
You're not going to go out
with me tonight 'cause
these idiots found
two poopies in a bed?
But it's not the poop.
It's the mystery
behind the poop.
It's Always Sunny In Philadelphia 4x07:
"Who Pooped The Bed?"
Synchro : Sososeries
The Bitches Team
www.forom.com/www.seriessub.com
Hey, girlfriend!
Oh, my God, you scared me!
Did I? My bad.
Why did you jump out from
behind a car?
- Were you stalking me?
- Girlfriend, you're crazy.
- Stop calling me "girlfriend."
- So check it:
putting together
a girl night out.
Want you to come.
Oh, my God, why would
I ever go out with you?
I hate you.
I know. I hate you, too.
That's the way girls are.
We're catty.
We backstab and talk about each
other behind our backs and stalk.
Don't you remember how Samantha
and Carrie and the dykey redhead
used to do that kind of fun stuff?
I don't know who you're
talking about.
Sex and the City.
You are the worst.
Look, I know you're going to be
alone tonight, okay?
I read all about it in the notebook
Charlie keeps of your whereabouts.
- You don't have any friends.
- I have a ton of friends.
Name one friend.
Frederick is your cat and he
died three weeks ago.
Look, it's all here in the
notebook, so stop busting
my balls and let's go
meet some men.
Give me that notebook.
I'm not gonna give you the
notebook.
Don't reach for the notebook.
I'll give you the notebook if
you come out with me tonight.
- Fine.
- Fine! See you tonight!
You want me to do what?
We want you
to examine our poopie.
We just want to know
who it came from.
That's it.
I mean... Now, we don't
presume to be scientists.
That's why we brought it to you.
We assume there's some kind of test
you can run with some of these machine.
You don't actually have to do
any tests 'cause I already know
it's Charlie's poop and not
mine.
You have a hole in the back
of your pajamas.
It's not my poop!
You've been sleeping
in a giant dress shirt.
It probably just fell out
the bottom of it.
Okay, clearly, we need to figure
this out before it tears us apart.
The only way for us to get to
the bottom of this is for you
to tear that poop apart and tell us
what's inside of it.
You know, get inside there.
You want me to examine a
plastic container full of feces?
I feel like you're going to
say something else right there
and then you stopped, right?
Please get out of my lab.
That wasn't what
he was going to say.
Man, why'd you have to go there?
Look, it's a simple job.
By the way, there's no
reason to be harsh.
Tiny little simple poop test!
You just missed out on an
extraordinary adventure, pal.
Let's get out of here.
There's other ways to
figure this out.
Pussy!
You got turd?
Yeah, we got a turd.
I'll take a look at it.
Okay, well... it's definitely poop.
Uh, yeah, we know that, guy.
Whoever it was seems to have
been eating newspaper.
All right, well, now we're
getting somewhere.
Which one of you idiots was
eating a goddamn newspaper?
It's gonna go both ways, dude.
- Really?
- I'm sorry, yeah.
What else? What else?
This appears to be a piece
of a credit card.
Inconclusive.
How is that not specific
to one of you?
I wish it was, man, but
that's inconclusive.
But you've got to...
There's a good deal
of blood in this stool.
Of course there is.
Whoever's it is should see a doctor.
Well, don't give us judgments.
Just tell us what's in there.
What else?
- This is wolf hair.
- Wolf air.
Also inconclusive.
Jesus Christ!
There is so much wolf hair in
our apartment right now, man.
But why are you eating it?
Well, you ingest everything.
Both of you are eating wolf?
Have you tried it before?
All right, guys!
This is getting us nowhere.
Can we move on
to the DNA test, please?
That's a good idea.
DNA's good.
Yeah, I can't do that.
What do you mean?
- Aren't you a scientist?
- Yeah, do it.
No, I'm an Econ major.
I just wanted to look
at some poop.
You're not a scientist?!
I never said I was a scientist.
Bro, you have wasted out time.
You have ruined our turd.
That's the only piece of
evidence that we have.
Who is she again?
Oh, that's Artemis.
She's the sassy one who always
plays by her own rules.
Guys are playing hard to get.
I'm gonna take off
my bra, blast my nips.
Okay, let's hold on that.
I think what we need to do
is just talk and have fun.
Bring 'em to us, you know?
So Artemis, where'd you get
that great top?
Burmington Coat Factory.
I got it on sale.
It's irregular.
Excuse me!
Hi, can we get
three Cosmos, please?
Actually, make mine a water.
Water? We're in a bar.
Yeah, well, I have
a drinking problem.
That's a horribly unattractive
thing to announce to everybody.
I'd like a water, please.
She'll take a Cosmo and
she'll just hold it in her hand.
- That's fine.
- That is a terrible idea.
It's a pretty good idea if you
want to get that notebook back.
Yeah, I'll take a Jager Bomb.
No Jager Bombs.
Fine, Irish Car Bomb.
Sake Bomb?
Nothing with "bombs"
in the name, okay?
Please, the Cosmos.
Go get the Cosmos.
Thanks a lot.
Goddamn it!
Hottie alert at 2:00.
Here they come. Incoming.
Okay, let me do the talking.
What's up, ladies?
Not much, just enjoying the view.
Name's Artemis.
I have a bleached asshole.
Okay, it's time to move on to
the reenactment and dramatization.
Jesus Christ, Frank,
you sleep in that?
My legs get hot.
Well, I definitely see how something
could have slipped out of there.
Absolutely.
That would have fallen right
out in the middle of the bed.
What about Charlie's hole?
Just get into the bed, please, and
show us how you sleep, guys.
Well, right off the bat,
I think there's a clear solution
could have prevented
this entire thing.
You guys need to get two beds.
Oh, maybe I'll get two TVs
and two refrigerators.
What are you talking about?
Do we come to your house
and tell you how to sleep?
I sleep in a king-sized bed
by myself.
When I have to go to the
bathroom, I use a toilet.
Look at... He... Dennis on
his bed made for kings
with his toilet made out of gold.
Okay, guys, everybody calm
down, please.
This is not about lifestyle.
This is not about judgments.
This is about truth, okay?
Now, Charlie and Frank, show us
how you were positioned
the night of the incident.
Excuse me. Incidents.
All right, well, I'm pretty sure
I was sleeping like this that night.
It's just, like, no way it
could have been me.
Charlie, we sleep ass to ass,
you know that.
Oh, great.
Okay, clearly, we're having
a problem with honesty here.
Dennis, a word.
I hate to say it, bro, but
I think we're gonna have
to do an overnight observation.
Yeah, well, to be honest with
you, I wouldn't mind seeing how
this whole situation really works.
Fascinating.
Well, this just gets weirder
and weirder, man.
Anything?
Nothing.
False alarm.
Damn it, dude, we can't keep
doing this all night.
Oh, I know. You know what.
Why don't we sleep in shifts?
Yeah, I mean, I'm not saying
this isn't important work
- but I can't keep my eyes open.
- No, I hear you.
I hear you. I hear you.
All right, I'll tell you what.
You go ahead and go first.
I still got a little energy left.
I don't know about
this floor, Dennis.
It's covered in sand or something.
No. It smells like some
kind of spice blend or pesticide,
or some other kind of
sandy poison or something.
I don't know. I wouldn't sleep
on the floor, though.
- You got to sleep with them?
- You got to, you got to.
You sure you're all right?
- Yeah, I'm fine. I got it.
- You sure?
Okay, I'm just gonna sleep for,
like, 15 minutes, right?
And then you wake me up, and
then we'll switch it off.
- You good?
- I'm fine.
My God.
My God!
If we're going to be
meeting sophisticated men,
we need to start
acting with class.
We cannot be telling people that
we have bleached assholes.
He was gonna find out anyway.
Oh, my God.
And you, you shouldn't be
drinking in a shoe store.
You shouldn't be drinking
in a shoe store.
What is the matter with you?
I told you to pace yourself.
I have a drinking problem.
Well, then, you should know how
to hold your booze a little better.
I'll hold your boobs
a little better.
Oh, good one.
Ladies, can I help you?
Hello. We are here for the Manolos.
- And what's your shoe size?
- 13.
We don't carry shoes that large.
Perhaps you'd like to try the
Big and Tall store down the street?
You know what?
I don't like this bitch's attitude.
Did she just try and break
a bottle over my head?
No, of course she didn't.
Girls, I'll meet you outside.
Get her.
Okay. Just the littlest bit snug,
aren't they?
There we go.
Cute, though, huh?
How much?
- 700.
- 700?
Yes, well, I'll tell you what.
You pay for quality 'cause there's
so much crap out there these days.
Man, I am excited to bust my
dogs out in these tonight.
We're going to a French
restaurant... Le Bistro.
It's five stars, so...
I don't know if you've been to it.
That sounds great, but
this has been declined.
Declined?
You're kidding me!
Oh! Makes me so mad.
Like, the credit card companies...
the way they waste your time.
Probably protecting me.
I spent a lot of money today.
Try that one.
Excuse me.
Oh, God.
Did it not go through?
What motive could a man possibly
have for pooping where he sleeps?
- I love that bed.
- Don't buy this act.
Frank, I will jam that poop right back
up your ass where it came from.
You know in that bed...
Guys, guys, guys, clearly, we're
exhausted and full of emotion,
but we should not be
threatening each other with
jamming feces into
each other's assholes, okay?
Wait a minute.
Wait, wait. Hold on a second.
What if we had them
produce another sample,
and we cross-reference the samples?
They'd have to do it in front
of us so that there's no foul play.
I can't go now.
Really?
I could probably squeeze
something out.
I'll get some newspaper.
This is exciting.
This is very exciting.
Why, of all places, are we here?
Because it's your bar, and
we're gonna drink for free.
Well, damn it, waitress,
that is not what I wanted.
How? How do you still not
know what my name is?!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm supposed to
be expected to rember
everyone's name
at all moments of the day.
This is the opposite of where
we're supposed to be.
Oh, Dee, we were just on
the verge of a major breakthrough.
He was turtle-heading.
Turtle-heading!
No, there was no turtles anywhere.
Were you just pooping on the floor?
No, I was not.
That was an endurance contest,
which I won, by the way...
- You're paying for that.
- She doesn't have to pay for that.
- Yes, she does.
- Bite me, asshole.
You have a bad attitude
when you're drinking.
You have a bad attitude when
you're drinking, you huge-footed slut.
You know what?
I'm just gonna go get more wasted,
and then I'm gonna bang some rim, dude.
Really? Could it be this guy?
No, it can't, but it could be Dennis.
Pass.
Whatever. You know what?
I'm gonna take this.
I'm gonna take this, and
I'll see you assholes later.
- That is my notebook.
- Free coffee for a year.
Wait a second.
Where did she get my note?
- You know what? I have backups.
- What is with her?
Something about drinking.
She just won't
stop talking about it.
- What, the plates of shit?
- Somebody pooped the bed.
Whatever. Let's get out of here.
We could use a fresh set
of eyes on this if you don't mind.
No, thank you.
I think that Artemis and I have
much better things to do, thank you.
Actually, I'm just
gonna stick around.
Excuse me?
- You know.
- Are you kidding me?
You know what?
Forget it, okay?
I'm gonna do this by myself.
I'm gonna go find some classy,
sophisticated people who can
hold their booze, who don't talk
about their bleached assholes,
and who aren't
obsessed with poop.
Okay, bring me up
to speed here, boys.
This is an interesting piece.
I love his use of space.
The space... that's what
I loved about it.
What do you think the chunky
earth tones represent?
Look at the rich texture,
the dimensions.
It's almost as if
you can smell it.
Oh, God...
This is the piece
I was telling you about.
It's unbelievable...
and so raw, so base,
so utterly human.
It's almost as if
it exploded out of the artist.
Well... I think it's crap.
Crap...
You know what?
Guys, let's just wrap up the evidence
and start again fresh tomorrow.
You think they'll keep, or
should we put them in the fridge?
They'll keep fine.
You know what?
You guys win, all right?
Are you happy?
Win what?
Heart failure!
Check the circuit breaker.
Nobody move!
Everyone here's a suspect.
Put on another pot of coffee.
It's gonna be a long night.
Four turds, five suspects,
so many, many nameless victims.
The first poop was obviously Frank.
Old and weak, he had
an accident, that's why
he was so intent on destroying it.
There were many turds before
this one, weren't there, Frank?
This was just the first time
you got caught, wasn't it?
And then you went and did it
again the next night?
Or did you?
Two poops in two nights?
Tall order for such a short man.
No. The second poop belonged
to Charles.
He wanted to get back at Frank,
but due to his poor diet,
couldn't produce a turd.
So he called Mac, who jumped
at the chance to see
Frank humiliated one more time.
But Charlie overlooked the fact that
Dennis listens to Mac's phone calls
and he heard every word.
Dennis was jealous that Charlie had
chosen Mac to help instead of him.
He swore to have his revenge.
That's why encouraged Mac
to sleep while he stayed up.
He was going to put the frame on
Mac by pooping next to him.
But he didn't realize that
a futon slept on by the weight of
three men would be off its axis
and slope to the center.
And like a small brown snail...
it crept to the middle between
Charlie and Frank.
Deandra! You wanted in on
this poop war from the start.
No, I didn't.
The outcast?
The slut?
The bitch.
The whore.
The lonely, sad, slutty,
bitchy whore.
You sat on the sidelines while
these four titans battled it out.
You were jealous that a few pieces
of poop got more attention than you.
That's why when the lights went out,
you unleashed some thunder of you own.
Thunder of the...
chocolate variety.
Oh, well, that would be
fine and dandy...
if any of it were true.
Can we wrap this up at some point?
In due time, pretty face.
In due time.
Isn't it true you thought you'd been
pooping the bed for months now?
You chalked it up to your old
plumbing and penchant for spicy foods.
Morning after morning, you'd
bury your poop after you rose
to hide it from Charlie.
But... convinced that Charlie had
discovered his dirty little secret,
Frank pooped the bed again
the next night as revenge,
only a lot more came out
than he expected.
He had gone too far.
I've gone too far.
Due to the size and severity
of the poop, Frank concluded
that Charlie had been pooping
the bed all along.
And so he cleaned up the mess
and wandered the streets,
looking for someone who could
replicate Charlie's small
and malnourished turd.
And that's where he came upon
his old friend, Rickety Cricket.
Get up!
Known the world over for his
ability to replicate any man's stool,
Cricket came back
and committed fecal forgery.
Which leads us to the third turd.
Dennis and Mac thought it'd be
funny to put the frame on Frank
and Charlie,
and so they both pooped.
But, as so often happens, the poop
rolled together and two became one.
A turd merger...
fused together by fear and
hatred... and hair.
But on to the final poop!
A poop that can
be traced back to Dee!
But not to her butt.
The waitress, drunk out of her
mind and furious that Dee had pushed
her back into the arms of
the bottle, pooped in Dee's purse
while Dee's back was turned.
And Dee carried it unknowingly
until she arrived here and the lights
went out and she was startled,
knocking her purse to the floor,
causing the turd
to tumble where it stands
before us, right now.
So, as you can see,
the mystery of who pooped the bed
has been solved.
And yes my friends, in a way,
you're all guilty.
I did it.
- What?
- I did 'em all.
I did all the poops.
- Really?
- Yeah, I did everyone of them.
I even did one, while
she was rappin us, right here.
- Dude!
- Jesus!
God! Why would you do that, dude?
Because poop is funny.
I guess poop is very funny.
- Poop is funny.
- He pooped on the floor.
You know what,
well-played my man!
Well-played!
I hate my life.
Seriously dude, don't ever
poop in our bed again.