Hey.
Hi.
Come back to bed and snuggle with me.
Oh... I wish I could, but
I got to go to work.
But there's cab fare
on the nightstand.
That's the third morning
in a row you've done that.
We're married.
I'm already home, silly.
Right. You're here.
We're married, and that's cool.
I'm psyched, dude.
That's great.
So you're... Yeah, okay.
Well, you know, you could use the
cab fare though to get to work.
Oh, I don't work.
Oh, oh, okay.
I just thought maybe you weren't
going to work recently because
we were going through a little
bit of a honeymoon phase.
But you're saying that
you don't have a job.
No job.
No job at all? Wow.
All yours.
All mine.
All mine all the time.
All the time.
Okay. Except on my work days.
I do have to go to work, you know, so...
That's cool, though.
You can just hang out here, I
guess, and sort of get used to
the lay of the land or whatever...
Although, don't-don't go
snooping around too much.
'Cause this has all happened
really fast and I really
haven't had time to do a pass yet.
Don't-don't look in those drawers.
What's in those drawers?
My sex tapes.
Yeah.
All right, I got to go to work.
I love you.
I love you, too, Maureen.
Okay, look, dude,
all I'm saying is that you
started off our domestic
partnership on some very shaky,
very bullshitty ground, dude.
And I'm saying, Charlie,
you should get over it, move on.
You signed the prenup, case closed.
You told me it was
the phone bill, man.
Of course I signed it.
Why would you think that you
needed to sign a phone bill.
I can't keep track of our
financial comings and goings.
When he hands me something to sign and
it's about money and papers, I sign it.
Hey-oh.
Look who got a brand-new car.
I'm still a little bit
confused as to why in the hell
you two got married
in the first place.
Charlie, gets health insurance
and I get diddly-squat.
He's gonna get some perks.
He doesn't trust me.
Hey, why in the hell are you
bathing yourself in the sink?
Because I don't
have a home anymore.
So this is where I take a shower.
This is where I live, Dennis.
Texting me again.
This is pathetic.
Back me up on this, Dennis.
You got a prenup with Maureen, right?
Uh, no, I did not.
Should I have?
Should you have?
You are screwed.
Typical.
This is so typical.
My God, Dee, you clearly have
something you want to say.
So let's just get it over with.
Oh, no.
No, it's no big deal.
It's just Bill Ponderosa is like
obsessed with me now or something.
I don't know, he's
texting me all the time.
He calls me, like, nonstop.
He bought me a new car.
Dee, are you seriously bragging
about sleeping with a married man?
Yeah, one second you're on your
high horse about how great
marriage is, and now
you're destroying one?
Well, I'm not the one who's married.
I didn't do anything wrong.
You let him buy you a car.
Well, Frank, I'm not going
to go passing on free cars.
Guys, guys, guys, guys, guys, all
this talk about marriage and
Dee being such a whore has got me
thinking... I never got a bachelor party.
We should go to the strip club.
Right now?
Yeah, immediately.
And since you would have been my
best man, you should probably
throw it for me.
Yeah, and I'm still pretty pissed about
you not throwing me a bachelor party.
So this way I figure we'll be even.
I'm ready for this.
Being married to Charlie's
got me all confused.
I got to get my hetero on.
♪ Want to get dirty, dirty ♪
♪ I'm gonna make your body
hot, girl Make you sweat ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I'm gonna give you the time of
your life That you'll never forget ♪
♪ Mm, mm... ♪
I like that move.
What is that?
That's it.
Motorcycle?
That's pretty...
Yeah, not like that, though.
It's pretty good, but you got to use...
...a little bit more shoulder.
I like the way he's
doing it, actually.
Yeah, 'cause I'm like,
I'm bending the bike.
But that's not really
how drive a motorcycle.
Yeah, but you're not really
driving a motorcycle.
It's my thing, okay?
All right.
Well, if you're not going to take it
seriously, then don't... then don't do it.
I feel like I was
doing it pretty good.
I feel like you're
taking it too seriously.
Let's not fight.
It's a bachelor party.
Oh, I got a text.
I got a text from the woman.
"Miss you."
I'll just write, "Miss you, too.
Miss you, too."
Now do I write the word "too" or
should I write the number two?
What's the best way to do that
when we're texting back and forth?
Who cares, dude?
I'll do the word, I'll do the word.
Okay, great.
Frank, what's with the purse?
It's my money bag.
I'm gonna make it rain, baby.
Whoa, hold on.
Make it rain?
What is that... you gonna
chuck money everywhere?
Don't do that.
Will you lighten up?
I'd like to make it rain.
Can I make it rain, Mac?
Why are you asking me?
Well, dude, 'cause I can't
fund my own bachelor party.
That's just tacky.
Fine.
Excuse me. Hi.
Hi.
What is the recommended amount of
money for one to make it rain?
I'd say at least a thousand.
How much would it cost for this gentleman
and I to get a nice couple's dance?
Sorry. You have to be
a couple for that.
We are a couple.
Charlie, documents.
All right, this is
what it was all for.
Mm-hmm.
Look at this... we're married.
Oh, you guys are cute.
You're still going to
have to pay full price.
Screw this.
I'm gonna go make it rain.
All right, well, hang on a second.
Give me some money.
Let's go, I'm your husband.
♪ Ooh, don't say maybe... ♪
There it is.
What is this?
I'm tightening the purse
strings on this relationship
until there's a little
bit of give and take.
You know what, keep your money.
I don't need your little allowance.
Hey, we'll see.
"Miss you more."
That's classic Maureen right there.
She's always got to one-up
me "Miss you most."
Most... can't get more
than most, right?
So that should...
that should be the end of it, right?
So, I hope so.
Oh, man.
You just cannot get enough, huh?
Sorry for just showing
up, you know, but you weren't
responding to my texts.
Oh, I totally get it.
Once you pop, you can't
stop, am I right?
Actually, I came clean to my wife.
And she kicked me out of the house.
Ew. Ouch.
Yeah.
Bet you wish you could
take that one back.
So I was thinking, maybe I
could stay here tonight.
Oh.
You are somewhat responsible for this.
No. No, no, no, no.
Can't you stay in a hotel or something.
Isn't that...?
I would, but she froze my assets.
Yikes.
Shit's getting pretty
real for you, huh?
But nonetheless, uh, I really, like I
said, I don't want you in my space.
So there's got to be a lot of
other places that you could stay
that aren't, you know, here.
Dee, I gave you a car.
You're gonna jam the
car in my face, huh?
Come in.
Thanks.
♪ The boys are back in town ♪
♪ The boys are back in town... ♪
♪ The boys are back in town! ♪
Whoo!
Dennis!
Hey... Hey...
What are you doing?
It is 2:00 in the morning.
I was sleeping, Dennis.
That's cool.
Well, you're up now, baby
girl, so let's do some shots.
No, I don't drink.
You know that.
I think it makes people look ugly.
I...
Maybe I should go to my room.
That is not your room anymore.
It is my craft studio, so
kindly stay out of there.
What?!
Don't freak out, dude.
It's all good, dude.
She turned it into her craft
studio where she makes terrible
sweatshirts out of cats or...
puts cats in sweatshirts, and then...
I'm, like, "Dude, what
the hell did you do?"
Dennis, do not talk to me that way.
I am your wife.
Please show me some respect
in front of your friends.
Uh, you know what?
I'm not entirely certain
that Maureen Ponderosa.
That doesn't even...
I don't know what that... What?
Divorce!
What? What did you just say?
I will divorce you, Maureen.
I'll do it.
Okay, you're drunk.
Why don't we just go to bed...?
I'm not drunk.
I'm more sober than I've
ever been in my entire life.
Okay, I'm a little bit drink.
I'm totally drunk, but
my mind is sober.
And my mind's telling me the
following: I don't love you, Maureen.
I don't love you.
I never loved you.
You're annoying and you're strange.
I don't know what to say.
Don't say anything 'cause every time
you open your mouth, I'm, like, "Ugh!"
It's like her breath...
Ugh!
It's like always so bad.
It's like a dead tooth.
It's the dead tooth.
I'm saying it now. I'll say it.
You have a dead tooth.
You realize that, right?
And I hate it, and it's annoying!
I want you and your boy toy
out of my apartment now!
I'm the boy toy!
You're my boy toy.
You know, I'm not gonna
leave our apartment.
Or should I say "my apartment,"
'cause it's my apartment.
Oh, yeah?
How about if you guys don't leave, I call
the cops and I tell 'em you beat me?
What in the hell are
you talking about?
I didn't touch you.
What...? What are you doing?
What is that?
I recognize that. What is that?
Oh, shit, that's from...
that's from Fear, dude.
Oh, that's Marky Mark.
That's Marky Mark.
That's what Marky Mark does.
He does that, and then, um...
Oh, shit, and then the cops
come, and then he...
Oh, and the police think that
William Petersen, the guy from CSI...
Go. She means business.
She means business.
Shit! Oh, shit! Ah!
Oh, my God!
You are really making
yourself at home here, huh?
Sorry. Want to have sex?
What?! No, no!
God, no!
Please close your legs up.
That's... Listen, I don't want
to get into your personal life,
you know what I mean?
It's not really any of my business, but
this is really bumming me out, okay?
So here's what I'd like to do.
I'd like to talk game
plan with you, okay?
And, um, number one, and most
importantly, uh, the car.
Now hear me out.
It was kinda a gift, so it'd be
pretty rude of you to try and...
I don't give a shit
about the car, okay?
Mm-hmm.
My life is in ruins.
I'm gonna lose my kids.
Okay, great, so we're in agreement.
I keep the car.
That's wonderful.
Now secondly, this is gonna be kind
of hard to hear, but, um... get out!
Get out!
You gotta go back to your wife, okay?
And get out of my place.
Okay, well, then I'm gonna need
the car to get over there.
Okay, well, the car's
off the table, okay?
We just discussed the car, and
we came to an agreement that...
Stop bringing up the car, okay?
So I'll get dressed and I'll drive you
over there, and I'll drop you off.
Okay.
Okay. Well, get up.
No, oh, God, I don't, I don't...
Okay, I'm gonna go in here.
Jesus.
Yeah, you now, I mean, I
wouldn't have imagined the whole
thing going down quite the way it did.
It was a little uncomfortable,
but I'm glad, you know, we got
our little heart-to-heart, or whatever
you want to call it, out of the way.
I feel like now we can set aside
our differences and settle this
whole divorce pretty
amicably, you know?
You think it's gonna
be that easy, dude?
Well, yeah, of course.
I mean, marriage and divorce
these days, it's like a, it's
more of a formality than
anything else, you know?
It's just sort of something
that you do, right?
Don't start with me, Charlie!
You bring nothing to the table!
Nothing!
Oh!
I bring nothing to the table!
This is my money!
You bring nothing!
Frank, okay?
"How did my laundry get so clean?
Oh, oh, who washed all
the dishes today?"
Nobody washes the dishes!
We eat the food directly off the
coffee table, and you know it!
I cannot stand being married to you!
Oh, you can't stand it?
I'm gonna pull the plug.
You gonna flush our
marriage down the toilet?!
Right down the toilet!
Flush it, big boy!
Yes, there he goes!
Flush it down the toilet
'cause I don't care!
Oh, yeah?
I'm gonna pull the plug, but first
I'm gonna draw up some documents.
All right, this is gonna
be an ugly-ass divorce,
and we're gonna get a mediator.
Okay, I got it.
We'll get that idiot lawyer
that always helps us out.
He does good by us.
Yeah, he's excellent.
But he slapped a restraining order
on us, so we can't use him.
Also you need a lawyer, too,
so we should talk about it.
I need a lawyer?
For what?
How are you not grasping
this situation?
Oh, for the divorce.
The divorce, yeah.
You're getting a divorce?
Yeah.
All right, sot's going around.
Okay, I think I know someone
who'll take both our cases.
Is it you?
Is it?
'Cause if it's you,
I'm not interested.
All right, well, I have a
family member who's a lawyer.
I bet he'd do it.
It's coming up here.
This...
yeah, this is it right here.
The Ponderosas' ponderosa.
Ugh!
Could you wait a minute?
I just want to make sure it's okay.
Yeah, you know, whatever it's gonna
take to wrap this up, really.
Whew!
Ugh!
Maureen?
No, it's Dee.
How are things going on your end?
Oh, not bad.
Yeah, not bad.
I'm getting a divorce.
Yeah, I know how that goes.
I got a messy situation
going on on my end, too.
Had to let my guy go.
Had to cut him loose.
I tell you what, though,
I do love the car.
Hands-free Blue...
I can do all kinds of stuff with both hands.
Dennis? Did we get cut off?
Okay, hop in there.
No! Wha-wha-wha-wha-what
is this?!
What are you doing?
Here he comes!
Okay, go, go! Go, go!
What?! Oh, my God!
I'm so glad you called, Charlie.
Your uncle never hears
from you anymore.
Well, you're kind of the only
actual lawyer I know, you know,
that doesn't have a
restraining order against me.
So I sort of had to call you, so...
I miss you too, bud.
Uh... with the touching, with
the touching... none of that.
You're put off by my hands.
I know they're very small.
It's been very hard on me.
It is not... there's nothing
wrong with your hands, okay?
Can we just focus on the law?
Of course.
All right, as far as shared
assets, I'm not seeing much.
I'm keeping the hot plate.
Over my dead body.
Hey, hey, hey, easy, boys.
Don't let the dog off the leash, okay?
Remember, the bigger
man walks away first.
You can have the hot plate.
Hot dog!
Now we're cooking with gas.
Moving along to art holdings.
All I'm seeing is a series
of drawings of elephants.
Hmm...
Oh, yeah.
Well, Charlie did the
elephant drawings.
Yeah, but...
You should keep 'em.
I did those for you, man.
I like 'em.
Well, you should like 'em.
I put a lot of work into 'em.
And thank you for saying you like 'em.
I've seen 'em and I like 'em, too.
Yeah, they're good.
I'll keep the drawings, okay?
If I didn't know any better, I'd say
there's a lot of love in this room here.
Look, Jack, we just want to
get back to where we were.
That's... Sounds like what you
guys want is an annulment.
It would essentially
void your partnership.
Yeah, right, that sounds perfect.
Marriage blows.
Preaching to the choir, fellas.
All right, I just need both
your signatures on here.
All right, that's easy enough.
Easy-peasy.
One... two.
We did it.
That's it.
Your union has hereby been dissolved.
Why did we have to do all the touching
and the hand-holding if it was just...?
It was fun.
Hey, Mac.
Do you mind snapping a
photo for the Web site?
But keep my hands out of the shot.
I just kidnapped Bill
Ponderosa's kids.
All right, are the kids
confined in any way, maybe in a
crawl space or a backyard bunker?
No, they're out in the car.
Have you touched them yet?
Absolutely not.
What...? Who is this man?
No, you don't need to...
What is she, some cheap tramp... huh?
Oh, no.
Bill, oh, my God, you
are such an asshole.
I followed you, okay?
Angel, I...
I knew you were seeing someone else.
Honey, that... Hi.
Hi, there, I'm Dee.
Uh, I understand that.
Listen, I wanted to say I'm
really sorry about the kids.
I tell you what, I did
not mean to kidnap them.
That was all...
that was all this guy.
Yeah, they're not my kids.
Aren't you his wife?
No.
I'm his mistress.
Well, what the hell, man?
I'm taking my car back.
Nuh-uh. That's my car.
Actually, I loaned it to both of you ladies...
Son of a bitch!
I gonna kill you!
What? How many
mistresses do you have?
Mistress? I'm his wife.
Kids, let's go.
Yeah, come on, kids, let's go home.
No, no, no, no, no.
Not you, Bill.
Now I want this to be
over with right now.
So how much does he owe you?
What?
How much does he owe you, whore?
How much does he owe you for the sex?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm not a prostitute.
I think that's... that's clear.
Oh, well, congratulations.
You're the only woman he didn't
have to pay to sleep with.
You must be very proud of yourself.
Wait, no, no.
Oh, goddamn it.
Yeah, well.
The, uh, the gravity of my situation
just set in, so... Let's go get you a
divorce, huh?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
You guys have any questions?
Yeah, I got a question.
What's in the fanny pack?
Oh, check this out, Mac and Dennis.
Just a little victory dance.
Thought maybe we could hang out later.
No.
Oh, Mr. Reynolds.
Oh, uh, I'm sorry, what
are you doing here?
Well, when I heard you were
getting divorced, I-I felt
compelled to involve myself.
I'm sorry, how would you have
heard that I was getting a
listening to you drunkenly
explain all that at 3:00 a.m.
I enjoyed it so much, that I
tracked down Maureen here and I
offered her my services...
pro bono, of course.
Hold on, fellas.
I'm Jack Kelly.
I'm a lawyer.
Hello, Jack Kelly.
The pleasure is all mine.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
The pleasure's... still...
Why don't we just get started.
Aw...
Boy, the old place, huh?
Some good memories here.
All of us.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, um... So I was like...
I'm gonna go, I think...
No, no, no, stick around, dude.
Stick around.
Please don't go.
I don't...
I don't want to, though.
No, you should stay...
I use shea butter.
Assorted lanolin products.
Oh, I'm serious, you
could be a hand model.
You've got the goods.
That was quick, guys.
Open and shut case, Dennis.
Okay.
Did you get the apartment back?
I sure did.
You did?
And you also acquired Ms.
Ponderosa's debt.
Whoo-hoo.
What? You're in debt?
Not anymore.
But you are... about 90K.
This guy seems to think you
don't have a case and I'm
inclined to agree with him.
Yeah. Well, when I found out that Ms.
Ponderosa here had been
cast out of her marital home, I
only thought it was fair that
you assumed her debt in addition to
the alimony payments, of course.
Wait a second... so I got
to pay alimony payments?
Uncle Jack, what the hell?!
I froze up.
He's great.
Oh, congratulations,
Miss Ponderosa.
Congratulations to you!
See you around, Dennis.
Yeah.
Mac.
Hey, Mac, would you mind taking
a shot of the three of us
for the Web site.
Come on, Dennis.
And would it be okay if you put
your hands on top of mine?
Like they're my hands?
Sure, yeah.
Like that?
Yes.
Okay.
That looks like my hands.
For the Web site.
We're lawyers.