Thank you so much for taking
the time to meet with us.
- Yes, this shouldn't take long.
- So...
You'd like to buy a boat.
Yes, we have recently come into
a considerable amount of money.
Now I'm not gonna bore you with details,
but let's just say
that my friends here
set up for a *** adventure...
- ***.com.
- Yeah.
- Actually we're not supposed to talk about...
- That's true but...
Yeah, technically we're doing a couple
of things in the hush hush from Uncle Sam...
The point is we're flush.
We are 25 hundred dollars flush.
So don't worry about that.
So we'd like to take some of that money
and taste a bit of the high life.
We've also talked to our friend here
into throwing
his entire life savings into the venture.
That's right.
You see, I'm in it for the lifestyle
as well as the great investment.
Okay, well, then what is it
you guys are looking for?
Let's talk needs, please?
I'd like to talk needs first.
Now I have the need for speed.
It's very important, it's inherent,
there's nothing I can do about it.
So speed is a must.
Absolutely, but we are also
looking to entertain guests upon
this boat, so...
Yeah, we're gonna throw some
P. Diddy-style parties
up on the deck.
Um, can we talk
shrimp for a minute?
I'd like the boat to be able to haul
in a tremendous amount of shrimp.
Sort of a Forrest Gump-size
amount of shrimp.
Um, you should be writing
this down, I think.
Why are you not
writing this down?
Oh, let me just see
if I have this right here.
Please, correct me if I'm wrong.
It seems what you guys are
looking for is some sort of
P. Diddy-style shrimping vessel.
All right!
That's it!
You're a really good listener,
and I didn't peg you
for one when I walked in here 'cause
of the pinky ring, but that's great.
You know, I've got just the boat for you.
Well, here she is, The
Drowning Sailor.
It, uh, doesn't meet, well,
uh, any of your specs.
Look, I'm gonna level
with you, pal.
We... we saw this coming a mile
away, and we've had our hearts
set on this boat thing for
days now, which, in our world,
is a level of focus in which
I personally have
never experienced.
But I'm gonna go out on a limb here
and I'm gonna say... We'll take it!
Mm-hmm.
What-what-what are you doing?
I was-I was doing a thing.
You were taking a
long time, dude.
You're taking way too long.
We wanted to buy a boat.
Let's get the boat.
I was taking a little while
because I was doing a little
presentation...
Dennis, what if someone walks
down the deck and makes
an offer before us?
Nobody's gonna make an offer
before I finish my thing.
They might have.
We're not the only people in town that want...
I'm confused.
Are you gonna take
the boat or not?
Yes, we're taking the boat.
We're buying the boat.
We want to add a little
fanfare into the situation.
My friends here, they
couldn't wait for that.
Yes, we're-we're
taking the boat.
What a score!
Yeah!
Houseboat, huh?
Yeah, absolutely...
Well, the houseboat offers all
the advantages of a house, but
with the excitement of the sea.
Think of all the fish
we're gonna catch.
It's not just fish, Frank.
You gotta start thinking
about shrimp, okay?
Oh-oh-oh.
We're gonna be hauling in so
much shrimp every day, it's
gonna pay for itself ten times over.
Picture tiny shrimp crawling
all over this boat.
- Every inch of it...
- Guys...
Can we not focus on the shrimp
cause we have so much work to do.
It's a shrimp boat.
I'd like to have at least one
conversation about shrimp.
No. No, shrimp is a very
small aspect of the whole...
Most important part of the...
No, you know what?
I'll tell you what.
Shrimp or no shrimp, I'm
very excited about it.
Yeah.
And I say we take this little
lady onto the sea and get loaded.
Well, slow your roll there, Dee.
The lady's not quite ready
to go out to the sea yet.
There's a lot of prep work
that still has to be done.
So, actually, Frank and Charlie,
I want you to start by scraping
the barnacles off the bottom of
the boat, 'cause that probably
hasn't been done in years,
while Dee and Mac and I go in
to the inside and check out the
decor situation, you know?
One word.
Shrimp.
Okay, yeah.
No, just as I suspected, we got
our work cut out for us, guys.
This isn't Diddyesque at all.
No, no, we gotta get
rid of all this shit.
Are you guys crazy?
This boat is awesome.
How about a little of this?
Huh?
What the hell is that?
This?
That's my P. Diddy boat dance.
Uh!
You look like one of this inflatable
dancing things at the used car lot.
The ones that flail
around in the wind.
No, I don't.
I look good.
No, Dee, that's exactly
what you look like.
I promise you that's
You can't dance for shit!
I can dance, and you don't know
what you're talking about.
I'm gonna bring one of those
in so you can see it.
Okay, why don't you bring the guy
in, we'll have a dance competition?
I'm gonna be the judge
of that contest!
I'm gonna show...!
There's not gonna be a contest!
Stop! Everybody stop! Shut up!
No, nobody's bringing any trashy
inflatable man on this boat.
Absolutely not.
Dee, stop dancing.
You look like an asshole.
We're not there yet.
We have a lot of work to do first.
Okay, Dee, since you didn't
invest any money in this
venture, you're gonna be the one that's
got to do all the hard labor here.
So I need you to get rid of all
this shit, and make the boat
look nice, okay?
Whoa-whoa-whoa.
Hard work?
What are you talking about?
Work first, and then you can
do your weird inflatable
tube-man P. Diddy dance.
Or whatever it is.
You know what I'm looking forward to?
Is catching me some
Delaware River catfish.
Oh, yeah!
They are so tasty!
I used to eat 'em when I was a kid.
You can't buy 'em in
the stores no more.
Why is that?
The goddamned EPA.
They says they're toxic.
Toxic my ass.
I mean, they're just endangered.
They're tasty, man.
Frank. this boat is the best
investment I ever made, man.
I mean, it's huge!
We're gonna pop over to the boat store
real quick and grab some, uh...
Whoa!
What the hell are you guys doing?
- We're loading our gear.
- No, no, no. You should not be loading.
No one should be bringing
anything onto the boat.
You should be scraping, okay?
Yes.
So, scrape.
Oh, well, we're gonna scrape the boat.
We are gonna scrape the boat.
Are you patronizing me?
Don't patronize me.
Don't do that.
No one's patronizing you, all right?
Here's what we'll do:
we'll scrape all these little
delicious oysters or whatever
off the side of the boat.
We'll put 'em in a pot, we'll boil
'em up for before you get back.
We'll cook 'em for you.
There you go.
No, those are barnacles.
Do not eat those.
Do not cook them in a pot
and serve them to us.
Okay, all that.
Honestly, don't eat those.
You'll get very, very sick, okay?
Yeah.
Now that is a direct
order from your captain.
Whoa!
Since when are you the captain?
Well, clearly I'm the captain.
Who else would be the captain.
I feel like I would be the captain.
Dennis?
I don't give a shit.
I'm captain! I call it!
Locked in. Boom.
Scrape. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go.
I ain't scraping shit.
No, we're not scraping!
No, no scraping.
Here's what we're gonna do.
We're gonna fire up the boat, right?
Yeah.
We're gonna take it out on
the ocean, we're gonna get
some oysters. And shrimp.
And shrimpies!
Toss me the keys.
Here you go.
What the hell was that?
Well, it's the keys.
I threw 'em right at ya.
I asked you to toss 'em!
You threw 'em overhand!
That's the way I throw!
Jump in there and get 'em.
I'm not going in there.
I don't sink.
What?
I get in there, I just bob
around like a cauliflower.
Don't give me lines, man.
Jump in the ocean and
get the damn keys!
No, I'm not going in.
Charlie, I'm not going in.
It's your boat. You go on in.
You son of a bitch.
All right.
Yo.
Hey, buddy.
Uh, I got us some turpentine, some
wax and some high-gloss boat paint.
This shit is really expensive.
Oh, dude, you're telling me.
I picked us up some new slacks
and docksiders so we could have
the right look, you know,
and fit in and everything.
We're running pretty low on
remaining dick towel money though.
Plus, we got to fill that thing
up with gas, and... I know, man.
We got to pop by the department
store, pick up the mattress.
I want to get a nice one, too.
You know what I'm saying?
The what? The mattress?
What do we need a mattress for?
What do you mean what do
we need a mattress for?
Why in the hell do you think we just
spent all that money on a boat?
The whole purpose of buying the
boat in the first place was to
get the ladies nice and tipsy
topside, so we can take them to
a nice comfortable place below deck
and, you know, they can't refuse.
Because of the implication.
Oh. Uh, okay.
You had me going for the first part,
but the second half kind of threw me.
Well, dude, dude, think about it.
She's out in the middle of nowhere
with some dude she barely knows.
She looks around and
what does she see?
Nothing but open ocean.
"Ah, there's nowhere for me to run.
What am I going to do, say no?"
Okay.
That seems really dark.
No, it's not dark.
You're misunderstanding me, bro.
I think I am.
Yeah, you are.
Because if the girl said no,
then the answer obviously is no.
No.
But the thing is, she's
not going to say no.
She would never say no,
because of the implication.
Now... you said that word
"implication" a couple of times.
What... what implication?
The implication that things
might go wrong for her if she
refuses to sleep with me.
You know, not that things are
going to go wrong for her, but
she's thinking that they will.
But it sounds like she doesn't
want to have sex with you.
Why aren't you understanding this?
I don't... She doesn't know whether
she wants to have sex with me.
She doesn't know?
That's not the issue.
Are you going to hurt women?
I'm not going to hurt these women.
Oh, okay.
Why would I ever hurt these women?
I don't know.
I feel like you're not
getting this at all.
I'm not getting it.
Goddamn.
Don't you look at me like that.
You certainly wouldn't
be in any danger.
So they are in danger?
No one's in any danger.
How can I make that any
more clear to you?
Okay, it's an implication of danger.
You know what, just drop it.
Let's drop it.
Buy your shit and let's
get out of here.
Oh, Charlie.
Charlie, you got 'em?
No keys. Can't find 'em.
What?!
I found a couple cool things.
What?
I got a tooth.
Ooh, look at that.
- It's like a horse's tooth or something.
- Oh, yeah.
- And look at this ***.
- Uh.
This is a war relic.
This could be valuable.
What the hell happened down there?
Some kind of horse massacre?
Could be.
Could be, right?
Yeah.
Dude, there's so much cool shit
down there, I'm gonna keep
diving looking for it.
I need a flashlight 'cause it's dark.
Flashlight coming up.
Just toss it to me real quick.
Come on, man.
I throw overhand, Charlie.
Ooh!
♪ Stop Drop Shut 'em
down, open up shop... ♪
What the hell are you doing in here?
Just throwing all these old,
like, dolls and compasses and
hairbrushes and shit overboard.
Mac and Dennis are making me clean up.
Well, this is a shit hole, isn't it?
Yeah.
Maybe we should gut it.
All right.
Let's see...
Ooh, ah, here we go.
Now, let's see.
Start with this beautiful baby here.
Whoa.
Crash and burn.
Holy mackerel.
Die, you sucker!
Oh, baby, look out.
Whoa! That ain't good.
♪ Give a dog a bone
Leave a dog alone... ♪
Whoa, Christ.
Think about, like, all the
movies and the books and all
the stories of all the
terrible awful, awful things
that have happened out in
the middle of the ocean.
You know, that's the stuff
that's, like, rattling around in
her head, informing her decision as
to whether she sleeps with me or not.
That's all I'm saying.
It's not like a big thing, or...
Uh-huh.
Look, I need you to
understand this, okay?
You're making it seem like I'm
some sort of monster or something.
Yeah, okay.
Hey, wha...
what is going on in there?
Like this?
It's more like a rolling sway.
Like this. There you go.
What the hell are you
guys doing in here?
Oh, my God, what the hell
did you do to our boat?!
Uh, we were cleaning it.
Wow, wow, wow, what's that all about?
You're just breaking
everything in this boat.
You were supposed to be fixing
it up and making it look nice.
Crew meeting! Crew meeting!
Where is Charlie?
He's in the water.
What is he doing in the water?
Charlie.
Aw, dude, what are you doing?
Oh, hey, guys, come here.
You are not going to believe how
much cool shit is under the boat.
There's like a whole
world of ancient stuff.
There was a horse massacre,
right, in the Revolutionary
times, and then there's
like a pirate ship.
Like, I found all these
old pretty little dolls.
- No. - Maybe like a brush, like
a pirate is brushing his hair...
Killed the horse and
then jumped in the ocean?
Goddamn it, I've been cleaning
up in there for hours
throwing this shit overboard and
you're just dragging it all back up.
You've been dumping the
trash in the ocean?
Why-why-why are you swimming in
the water in the first place?
He dropped the keys in the water.
I did not... All right, first of all,
he threw the keys at me overhand.
You should have seen this throw.
We leave you guys alone for 45
minutes and you destroy the
interior of the boat, you lose the keys...
I can get those keys.
I just need you guys to buy me
some scuba equipment so I can
stay down there longer.
Do you realize how much money
scuba equipment costs?
No. Rent the cheap stuff.
Just rent some cheap stuff, all right?
In the meantime, we'll clear all
this stuff off... we'll start
to paint, all right?
By the time you guys come back,
I promise you, I promise, the
boat will be looking better.
I can't tell.
Is he patronizing me again?
I can't...
I can't even tell anymore.
No, no, what he's saying is
really stupid, but it's sincere,
okay? It's sincere this time.
I think you're just a
little sensitive to it.
Sorry, Charlie.
I'm sorry, too.
That was patronizing!
You can't patronize your captain.
That's a sea law.
Yo, dude.
You realize how much
boating equipment costs?
It's crazy, it's astronomical.
I can't believe how much
they charge for this shit.
You know, Dee, Frank and
Charlie are driving me crazy.
We're spending all of our dick
towel money and they're throwing
keys into the water and losing everything...
And you're not even listening to me.
No, I heard you.
You said a bunch of words, right?
Look at this.
What is that?
It's like some kind of
dock party mixer, dude.
It's a flyer.
Look at these chicks.
And an anchor.
Dude, that's what we need to be doing.
We need to be mixing it up at
mixers with other boat people
and living the lifestyle.
You're right.
Okay, cool.
And then we'll be back
in the high life again.
Yeah.
Like Stevie Nicks.
That's actually Steve Winwood.
Right. Same dude, right?
It's not the same dude.
Actually, one's not even a dude.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
It doesn't matter.
I love that song.
Let's buy that CD.
Well, first of all, I
love that song, too.
That's why I already own the CD.
I own all of Steve Winwood's shit.
You should know this.
And secondly, we have not been
on the same page all day.
We can't be spending money
on CDs that I already own.
We're spending too
much money as it is.
It's bad enough I let you buy that
stupid inflatable guy from the car lot.
Stop it!
Goddamn it, don't!
It's not the puffy
guy... it's this music.
This aggressive music you're playing.
- This is not...
- It's got nothing to do with the music.
Listen to me.
Listen to me!
I'm turning you off.
You're crazy.
Riled you up.
Yo, you guys...
Look at you... fighting with a green guy.
Dudes, you're never going to
believe what I just found
floating off the end of the boat.
Okay, I'm scraping those little delicious
oysters off the bottom, right?
Why is this turned off?
You're back.
You don't even... Well, well, I got
to say, guys, I'm very impressed.
The boat's really
starting to come along.
I didn't think you guys had it in you.
Yeah.
There's a couple more brushes
here and a little paint.
Get to work, we'll do the
trim and then we'll be done.
Us?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
We're not going to be
doing any of that.
No, no, no.
You're not going to
be doing any of that?
What do you mean?
We're not going to be
doing any of the work.
That's-that's what you guys are doing.
That was the whole deal.
No, we got a party to get ready for.
Yeah, so... We're going to do all the
work while you guys go to a party?
We got to socialize.
Yeah.
I could socialize.
Uh, no.
Not looking like you're looking.
You're covered in paint and dirt and
grime and all kinds of shit, so...
You're skin looks like leather and
you got blisters all over you.
You guys look absolutely terrible.
Well...
Well, we're out of here.
So, Charlie, there's your,
uh, there's your scuba gear.
Find the keys.
Just find 'em.
Oh, guys... keep up the good work.
See, now they flipped it around.
They're patronizing us.
Absolutely patronizing us, Frank.
That's right, they're patronizing...
But don't take it to heart,
buddy, 'cause I got something
that's going to cheer you up.
What?
Guess who found the keys.
The keys!
You found the keys!
Dude, they were just
floating under the boat.
They got a little
floaty thing on them.
This is amazing, by the
way... these floaty things.
We should patent this.
Okay, I think this is it.
Now this is much more our speed.
These are the kind of people
we should be hanging out with.
Man, now this is a boat.
Ahoy, ahoy.
Hi, hi.
A couple of fellow yachters.
Saw your flyer at the boat store...
Oh.
Do we have the wrong yacht?
No, no, no, no, come on
in and grab a drink.
We're just getting warmed up.
Okay.
Sure.
Let's just...
Yeah.
Uh, can I talk to you for a second?
Um, this isn't the
crowd I was expecting.
These guys are more barnacle covered
and sunburned than Dee and Frank.
Let's not rush to judgment, okay?
These are real men of the sea.
Maybe this whole thing
isn't about meeting girls.
Maybe it's about having an adventure,
you know, an open ocean adventure.
Take a look at this guy.
How'd he lose that hand?
I bet you it was some kind
of crazy adventure, right?
Let's find out.
Hey, bro, how'd you lose that hand?
Diabetes.
Oh.
Um, that's not, uh, much
of an adventure, is it?
Kind of tragic.
Yeah.
You know, we'll let you get back to...
We're just going to go over to
the bar and grab a drink.
I'd offer to pour you a drink,
but you probably can't drink
though with the...
diabetes.
Diabetes.
Yeah, yeah.
Look, you know what,
I was wrong, dude.
This is a bummer.
Yeah, this is a major bummer.
Let's get the hell out of here.
What do you say?
Yeah.
Hey, listen, guys,
thanks for everything.
I think we're just going
to take off, though.
No, no, no, no, don't do that.
We're just getting warmed up.
We're going to set sail soon, and
we're going to have a couple
of tasty treats out there.
It's going to get nuts out
there, fellas, right?
We're going to be out
on open ocean, right?
Huh?
Anything can happen out there.
No laws, right, boys?
Just us and our tasty treats.
- That was an implication, right?
- That was definitely the implication.
Tasty treats?
Are we the tasty treats?
We're the tasty treats
in the scenario.
Yes, we're the tasty treats.
They're going to take us out
into the open ocean... they're
going to have their way with us, Mac.
We got to get the hell out of here.
Is this how you wanted
those poor women to feel?
No. You know what, I don't enjoy
having this conversation with you.
I feel like you're
lumping me in with them.
Now, gentlemen, the moment
you've all been waiting for.
The ladies have arrived.
♪ I'll be back in the high life again
All the doors I closed one time
♪ Will open up again I'll be
back in the high life again... ♪
Oh, Frank, you are absolutely right.
This is boat music.
Yeah, this is the kind of
music you ought to listen to.
I am learning some amazing
moves from this guy.
Yeah, you're doing great.
You got the moves.
Anybody want any more catfish?
Yo, dude, definitely give
me another one of those.
They're delicious.
And you can taste that
sort of endangered tang.
That's it.
Oh, hold on.
I'm getting a call.
Hello.
Hey, hey, Charlie, did you
guys ever find those keys?
Yeah, man, I did actually.
I did. Can you believe that.
Okay, great.
I need you to grab Frank and Dee
and get the hell out of there
because we're going to be
bringing back a couple of tasty
treats, if you know what I'm saying.
Hey, man, yeah, absolutely.
I'll get right on that.
That's how you patronize
someone right there.
What, what, what, what, what, what?
Dennis being a dick.
Don't worry about it, man.
Hey, this scuba equipment's broken.
It's useless.
The hell with it.
Let's get back to shrimping.
I'm gonna toss this shit.
It's crap anyway.
Ooh, that's not good.
Uh, hey, um, what do you
do if the boat is on fire?
What do you mean?
The boat is on fire.
What?
Oh, fire's getting bigger.
What?!
Fire's getting bigger.
Go!
Fire's getting big.
Bail!
Holy shit!
Find some water.
Find some water?!
What do you mean find some water?
There's water everywhere.
Help!
Help us.
I cannot wait to get you
ladies out into the sea.
It's so much more romantic in
the middle of nowhere where we
can be completely alone, and you can
make rash decisions based on fear.
Right, Dennis?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, wow, whoa, whoa.
I thought we told you guys to beat it.
Out of my way.
No more Diddy boat.
Damn catfish nipping at my heels all the w...
Endangered my ass.
There's a billion of them out there.
Ugh. What the hell happened?
That was a hell of a swim.
Charlie, where's the boat?
What happened to the boat?
It's right there.
This was a terrible investment.
Whew.