93.3 WMMR.
***
We have got to open
up the phone lines.
The first listener who can
correctly answer our stupid
trivia question of the day is
gonna get to come down to the
Flyers game with us tomorrow night
and take a shot from center ice.
Now, if you make it, you win two VIP
passes to the 93-three WMMR ***
***
Dude, nothing
but busy signals.
I'm on hold on all of them.
You're on hold on those?
We're gonna get through.
Hey, who's on the line?
Is that us?
That sounded like us.
Uh, Mac from South Philly.
All right, Mac from South Philly,
you're on with Preston and Steve.
Holy shit! He got on.
Holy shit, I got on.
Please don't curse.
All right, here's the question.
What Philadelphia Flyer holds the
franchise record for goals in a season?
You have 30 seconds. Go!
This is hockey question.
Go! Go! Hockey, hockey.
Uh, where's the H key?
There's no H key?
There's no H key...
What are you talking about?
Is there another way to spell hockey?
There's no H key.
Dude!
There's no H key on this...
There's an H right there.
What would be the next letter?
Why did I put you in
charge of this job?
Oh, forget this, dude.
I got this. I got this.
Think, Mac. Think. Think. Think.
I got to think like that guy.
That guy that sits on the rock.
This dude? The one like that?
Yeah, with the big muscles,
and he puts his on his...
Ah, he's big and green and...
Think, think.
The Thinker?
The Thinker.
Oh, the Hulk.
The Incredible Hulk.
Hulk doesn't think...
The Hulk?
Shit, dude, I know this.
Dude, you got to stop cursing!
Look, you guys can't censor me, okay?
I'm a bit of a badass.
You can't censor him.
All right, let's go.
Answer the question, come on.
Just take a wild guess.
Aah! I don't know.
I don't know it. Damn it!
Reggie Leach.
Reggie Leach is the...
correct answer!
Its.Always.Sunny.in.Philadelphia.S06E04
Send a rush out, baby!
♪ We're going to the beach house
Gonna make our dreams come true
♪ Down at the beach house that's what
we're gonna do, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Ooh, ooh... ♪
This a potentially life-changing
opportunity right here.
Not potentially.
It is a life-changing opportunity. It is!
I'm sorry. How is spending a
weekend at a radio show beach
house a life-changing
opportunity?
Dude, there is gonna be so many
athletes and celebrities at
that beach house.
This is my chance to finally sow
myself into the inner circle.
I'm gonna be like a
local sports legend.
Hey, can we have our phones back?
em about using the minutes on the
cell phones?
They used up all your minutes, right?
Frank, nobody gives a shit
about minutes anymore.
Actually, you know what?
I do give a shit about minutes.
I know I shouldn't, and I think
I'm just probably buying into
the phone company's
propaganda, but there you go.
Interesting.
What is happening here?
Why are you taping them?
Oh, because they got great banter.
They jib jab.
Jib jab, jib jab, jib jab.
I use it for the car...
I jib jab.
...'cause my stereo's busted.
We have a lot of interesting
things to say, so, you know.
Oh, shit. Well, I feel like
the conversation we've been
having in the last five minutes
is a lot more interesting than
the shit they're talking
about on the radio.
Mm-hmm.
Are you kidding me?
It's just moronic commentary and stupid
sound effects, and it's just dumb.
It doesn't make any sense.
Well, we have voices.
We talk about the issues.
You know, I feel like we could
do a podcast, and it would be
a million times better than whatever
that drivel was we were listening to.
Without a doubt.
You know what?
This sounds like jealousy talk.
Yeah.
Mac, Charlie, congratulations on, uh,
your slap shot and the beach house, okay?
Uh, we're happy for you.
You're sad sometimes.
Yeah, why aren't you happy for us?
You're dark souls...
I mean, you know what?
You want to just do
our thing and not...?
Let's do our thing.
Have fun with your important
conversations and your big
issues with your brains and
your smart stuff, okay?
We got hockey to learn.
And we're gonna...
It's gonna change our lives.
Yeah, yeah.
Life changing.
Okay, it was The Thinker.
It's The Thinker.
Yeah.
You couldn't spell hockey.
Right.
Oh, zing! ♪ Bo, bo! ♪
Hold on a second.
You guys are the best.
Do not speak until I
turn my tape over.
Okay.
Aw, shit!
I taped over my
Luther Vandross mix.
Aah!
Okay, dude, now we're
both in agreement.
This is probably, like, the
biggest opportunity either of us
have ever had in
our lives, right?
We are not men who get a lot
of opportunities, Charlie.
No.
The few we've had,
we've squandered.
We've squandered them all.
That's why we've got
to stay focused, Mac.
I mean, this is big time.
This is pro sports, right?
Yeah, mm-hmm.
We got to do this right.
You got to look good.
Yeah.
And you can't miss
that shot, right?
I really appreciate you
helping me, dude.
Absolutely. Well, a little Peewee
Hockey experience never hurts.
You're good.
Okay, so first things first.
Hold the hockey stick.
Hold the hockey stick?
Mm-hmm.
Okay, good, 'cause I was
thinking, I'd have a position
sort of like this.
Why would you do that?
All of my instincts and my
training tell me to use this as
a weapon.
All of your instincts and
your training are wrong.
Hold it like a hockey stick, or
people are going to boo you.
The Philly fans are
brutal, dude.
All right, fine!
All right? Right.
Then you just sort of haunch
down a little bit... Done.
You might want to haun...
What if I do this?a...
That's way stiffer.
That's pretty good
right there, Charlie.
You look so awkward.
Bro, when you tack on mass,
you sacrifice flexibility.
That's just a straight-up fact.
That's insane.
Touch your toes.
What am I, a gymnast?
Yeah... Charlie, teach me
how to shoot the shot.
All right, fine, fine.
Calm down. All right, all right.
Yeah.
What you're gonna want to do is just gently...
gently sort of
guide the puck at the net, like...
you know, like a tiny
bowl of cream you don't want to
spill, and you're guiding it.
I'm not gonna do that.
I'm going to go out there and take
a wicked slap shot, you know?
Really make a name for myself.
Otherwise, I go out there,
I look like a jabroni.
You know what?
Yeah, we might want to work on
some kind of routine, huh?
Thank you. Exactly.
So I'll go out there.
I showcase my weaponry.
Uh-huh.
Pump the crowd up.
Really get the crowd up.
And raise the roof on 'em.
Watch. Uh-huh.
Okay. But you know what?
You can't take a slap shot
before you even know how to
handle a stick and a puck,
so will you just glide one?
Just to get the form.
And then we'll get bigger and
bigger, and eventually, slap
shots, but it starts with
gliding like cream.
Go.
Gliding like a jabroni is
what I'm gonna be doing.
Jabroni. Okay, go.
Well, that didn't do anything.
Well, that was pretty
pathetic, you're right.
Yeah, well, the problem is, I'm
out in the elements, dude.
There's so much wind and sun.
All right.
And this asphalt--
that's not regulation.
No it's not regulation.
So it's not...
All right, you know what?
You want to do this
the right way?
Yeah.
Let's go to the ice.
Let's get some pucks, all right?
We'll slide, we'll take
a few slap shots.
Let's go to the ice.
We'll do this the right way.
This is me.
All right, very exciting stuff.
I think we're pretty much ready
to go here with this podcast.
What the hell is a podcast?
I mean, why don't
you just tape it?
What are you doing?
You don't have to tape
it these days, Frank.
You just record it right
onto the computer.
Hmm.
And, uh, once we start recording,
Frank, we need you to
stop eating those crackers.
It's incredibly annoying, and
it's all anyone's gonna be able
to hear.
So, Dennis and Dee
Reynolds here.
Inaugural podcast.
We're talking technology today.
The big T.
Absolutely.
Everyone's talking about
technology these days, because
it's everywhere.
Oh, it is.
You can't escape it.
You absolutely can't.
So, Dee, tell us what you
feel about technology.
How do you...?
What's your opinion on it?
crackers?
I'm getting bored with this.
I'm going to bring my guest in.
Guest?
I asked Cricket to come.
What?
Cricket?
No, Frank.
You can't just bring
guests in here.
This is our podcast.
I feel like you're
trying to take over.
No, no, no.
You know what?
Actually, this could bring
up a pretty good issue.
If you bring Cricket in here,
we could rail on him about the
homeless issue.
Cricket!
Cricks.
Yo.
There he is.
Come on in, buddy.
We're ready for you.
Hey, Frank, where's my chicken?
This is taking forever.
Come on.
I promised him a
rotisserie chicken.
Let's go.
Chop, chop.
I'm starving here.
What's going on
with your voice?
It's from when Frank hit
me with the trash can.
Wound got infected.
It was a whole ordeal.
Okay, all right.
Well, um... Listen, let's
get into the issues here.
We're going to start
rolling on this, Cricket.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
I am not saying another word
until I get the chicken.
I lied about the
chicken, Crick.
Are you kidding me?
All right?
It was bullshit.
Oh, my God.
Unbelievable.
Why do I even trust you?
All right, wait a minute.
Here.
I do have something for you.
Lemons.
Lemons?
Yeah, you suck on them.
Oh, come on.
At least give me the crackers.
No, suck on a lemon.
Here, go ahead.
Well, they are good for scurvy.
All right, I'll have a few lemons,
but then I'm out of here.
All right, here we go.
So, uh, Dennis and
Dee Reynolds here.
We are talking about the
homeless issue here in Philly.
That's a big issue these days,
and we're here with our friend
Cricket.
He is a homeless man.
Cricket, walk us through
a day in your life.
Oh, day in the life...
Well, uh, the other morning, I
wake up, I find a dog
sniffing at my wound.
He's fully aroused, mind you.
So I'm thinking, "Oh, great,"
you know, "what does
this jerk want?"
Of course I know what he wants.
He's looking at me
right in the eyes.
He does not have to say it.
Not that he could.
Oh, that is-that is tart.
That is really tart.
I mean, does my scar look
like a dog's vagina?
You know, maybe.
I don't know.
I'm not going to sit here and try
to get inside the mind of a
dog.
I mean, that's God's work.
Well, not that I believe in God.
I don't.
Not since that Chinaman
stole my kidney.
Cricket, tell Dee how much
you think she's ugly.
That's not going to
make any sense, Frank.
He doesn't think I'm ugly.
He's madly in love with me.
Don't flatter yourself.
I'm over you, sister.
Since when?
Since I found out
you are a whore.
Will you stop talking about...
This has nothing...
Well, maybe you're a whore, you
stupid, ugly, homeless bitch.
Zing.
A dog banged your
neck the other day.
You're both whores.
Well, a No, no, this
is not good radio!
All right.
Okay, this is exciting, Mack.
This is exciting.
You know, you're...
What are you doing?
Huh?
Would you take this seriously?
I am taking it seriously.
This is your big moment, man.
You got to walk out to center
ice, and you got to be like,
"Hey, USA!
USA!"
USA!
Not like that.
Make it classy.
Okay, but keep in mind I am going
to be wearing the duster.
Well, of course you're
going to wear the duster.
That's going to look awesome.
Thanks.
Yeah. You should probably
also be wearing a wig.
A wig?
Totally.
Long, flowing hair.
That's going to look way more
dramatic, you know what I mean?
Like... Okay, I like the
wig idea in spirit.
Problem is, I'll have to wear
the wig to the beach house so
people will recognize me.
Next thing you know, I'm wearing
a wig for the rest of my life
just to keep up appearances.
Yeah, like Andre Agassi, huh?
Yeah, right.
I don't want to do that.
I don't know.
Let's not rule it out, though.
A good hockey wig could put
this thing over the top, man.
Okay, fine.
All right, all right.
Let's do this, let's
do this thing!
All right, make some shots.
What else are we
here for, dude?
Let's do some shots!
All right.
All right, you ready?
Hoo, hoo, hoo.
Let's see what you got.
Haunch.
What was that?
All right, well...
That would have been cool if
I was standing backwards.
Well, you're not going to stand
backwards, you're going to
stand forwards.
You're going... What the hell
are you two doing out here?
Don't worry about it, bro.
We're practicing... You can't be
out here swinging hockey sticks.
You're not even supposed to
be out here without skates.
Now get out!
All right.
Out!
Okay, we're leaving.
You know what, Charlie?
I think he's right, dude.
Only a couple of jabronis come
out here without skates on.
I got to do this thing
in skates, man.
You know, work up a routine,
really jazz the crowd.
Yeah, can I stop you, though?
Yeah.
You keep using this word "jabroni," and...
it's awesome.
It's, like, the
coolest word ever.
Is that, like, a hockey thing?
Yeah, I don't know.
It's-- I think it's some dego
word, but it sounds like a
hockey word.
It does sound...
You're gonna want to brush up
on your hockey words
at the beach house.
You're going to be hanging
out with the Flyers.
Okay, we are back.
Dennis and Dee Reynolds here.
Uh, we're back to the podcast.
We got a little derailed earlier.
We did.
We did, but that's okay.
We're going to get back on track here.
Let's try and get back on track.
I got a hot topic that I
want to talk about, Dee.
Tell me what it is.
Well, this is something I'm
pretty charged up about.
Mm-hmm.
It's stem cell research.
Good one.
It's a very divisive issue these days.
Excellent one.
People are really going to town,
one side against the other.
Some people are for it.
Oh, absolutely.
Some people are against it.
What are you doing?
That was a duck.
Why would you make a duck noise e e
right in the middle of my thing?
I was doing a thing.
It was funny.
It's a duck noise.
Yeah, but you derailed us.
I thought it upped the
production value.
It's not.
You know, add some sound effects.
Well, don't.
Okay, well... Okay, so stem cell research...
Stop doing that.
Stem cell research is a
very--
Why are you still...
Stop pushing sound effects.
I want to talk about--
Which one was that one?
This one.
It's a laser beam.
Yeah.
I like that one.
You like that one.
Yeah, I want to pepper that one in.
Okay.
Don't do it while I'm talking.
All right.
Well, we'll see.
Hey, Frank!
That's Frank Reynolds, everybody.
I have a great topic for you.
War.
War!
War?
Good one.
Everyone's talking about the war.
And I have the perfect guest.
Okay, all right.
Ben the soldier.
Hey, Dee.
Good to see you.
What are you doing?
No. No, no, no.
I'm not comfortable with this.
happening here.
Is the war happening here?
I don't know.
Let's get into all this stuff.
All right, great.
Ben the soldier's here with us,
folks, and I want to talk to
him, because, Ben, it's my
understanding that there is a
war going on right now.
Mm-hmm.
Am I right in this?
Well, actually, there
are two wars right now.
Two wars?
You don't say.
We're in the midst of two wars all
at once-- Now, the United States of
America is engaged in
both of these wars?
Yes. Yes, they are.
And are either of these wars
happening on U.S. soil?
Ben...
Excuse me.
Let me, let me, let me--
What is your job in the war?
Are you a carrier of-of,
uh, large weaponry?
Let me just-- How about if we talk
about how you used to bang each other?
Yeah.
No.
What kind of technique did you use
and tie-ups and stuff like that?
Frank, Frank.
Tie-ups.
It's not good radio.
'Cause people like sex.
Okay, well, let's... Okay, I just want
to clarify what my producer Frank is
actually referring to is the
fact that Ben, our soldier here,
and Dee used to be lovers.
Don't do that to me.
That's a good one!
That's not funny.
It's not.
You're in the hot seat, girl.
I'm not in the hot seat.
Yes, you are.
Yes, you're in the hot seat.
Ben's in the hot seat.
All right, Mac, so you're
going to come on the ice and
fire out to center, right?
Do, like, a cool turn and
get the crowd going.
Okay, so fire out...
Come on.
Huh?
What are you do...?
That's not cool.
Wait, do you not know
how to ice-skate?
No, not at all, but I figured you would
teach me 'cause we got plenty of time.
We don't have time.
It's tomorrow night, man!
Charlie, you got to help me,
dude, this is my big break.
Come on!
Oh, my God.
All right, we got a lot of work to do.
All right, here, grab the stick.
Ready?
Uh-huh.
And we'll start slow.
Oh, my-- this is going
to take forever, man.
That's good.
That's good, that's good.
I'm skating.
" playing)
♪ Push it to the limit ♪
♪ Limit ♪
♪ Walk along the razor's
edge
♪ Open up the limit ♪
♪ Limit ♪
♪ Past the point of no return You've
reached the top But still you gotta learn
How to keep it... ♪
No, no, no!
♪ Hit the wheel And double the
stakes ♪ Throttle wide open
Like a bat out of hell And
you crash the gates ♪
♪ Crash the gates ♪
♪ Going for the back Of beyond
♪ Nothing gonna stop you
There's nothing that strong... ♪
♪ So close now You're nearly at the
brink ♪ So push it Ooh, yeah. ♪
Okay, next guest.
All right, Dennis, let's
get this over with.
Well, don't bring her in
here, stinking up the joint.
Come on.
Frank said you were
gonna apologize to me.
Oh, who's in the hot seat now?
All right, let's not
push too many of those.
Okay, all right, you're abusing
it, you're abusing it.
No, no, it's good.
It's going to get not funny
after a little while.
Oops.
Let's stop.
All right, well, so let me
understand this waitress.
Frank promised you an apology from me.
And now, you didn't
believe him, did you?
Yeah.
Really?
Okay, well, that makes you
incredibly gullible and stupid.
Oh, oh, oh, don't take that from him.
Are you gonna take that from him?
You stand up for yourself.
I'm not leaving here until
you apologize to me.
You're gonna be here for a while.
She's boring me.
I'll give you 50 bucks if you
take off your top and you drink
soup out of my shoe.
What?
Okay, now, that I'd like to see.
Yeah, yeah, me, too.
What do you say, sister?
You need some extra cash?
No.
500 bucks.
Cricket, bring us some soup.
You'd pay me $500 to drink
soup out of a shoe?'
And take your top off.
Fine, I'll do it.
Oh, nice.
Oh!
But I am not taking my top off.
Well, that's a relief to all of us.
Oh, zing, gotcha.
Couldn't find soup, but I
found some dirty dishwater.
Boom, even better.
Oh, my God!
Oh, now this is good radio!
Holy shit, dude, there's
a lot of people here.
I'm getting nervous, Charlie.
Yeah, you might throw up when you get
out there, you know, from the nerves.
You're supposed to be my coach, dude,
don't tell me I'm going to throw up.
I know when people do that,
so try not to throw up.
Oh, come on, dude.
Mac, Charlie, what's up?
Oh, hey, you guys came to support me.
Uh, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, that's why we're here.
Primarily, yeah, but... But also, you
know, since we're here, we wanted to give
you this tape so you could
give it to those radio guys.
That's our demo tape.
We were recording the whole
thing on a computer, but then
the computer got water
dumped all over it.
It was a whole thing.
Luther Vandross?
Is that still on there?
Oh, that's very off-putting, Dennis.
Yeah, we should have relabeled it.
It's not Luther Vandross.
Make sure you tell him
it's not Luther Vandross.
All right, let's get going.
Shh.
Mac from South Philly, get out here.
This is you.
Here we go, here we go.
Everybody, say a prayer.
Let's do this.
Give him the tape.
What is that?
The future of radio, you jabronis.
Jabronis-- cool word.
Mac, Mac, Mac, Mac!
Mac, Mac!
Mac, Mac, Mac, Mac, Mac!
Wake up, Mac.
Mac, Mac, wake up.
Mac, wake up.
What happened?
Did I do good, Charlie?
No, you fell on your face
almost immediately, man.
Who took the shot?
I took the shot.
Yeah, I-I missed wide
right by, like, a mile.
It was terrible.
Look on the bright side, dude,
I think you're going to be a
sports celebrity after all
'cause they're definitely going
to play that shit on ESPN.