♪ Butt, butt, butt...Open up the
time capsule... Butt, butt, butt
Open up the time capsule ♪
What are you doing?
♪ Butt, butt, butt ♪
I could watch him
do that for hours.
♪ Open up
the time capsule. ♪
What is the time capsule butt-butt?
We're about to open this time
capsule that we buried ten years ago.
Oh.
Yeah.
What'd you put in there?
Oh, man, we just put a bunch of
stuff in here that we thought
would be valuable one day,
like, uh, let's see, we got a
Gregg Jeffries baseball card.
Future All-Star, future All-Star.
It wasn't valuable then.
Uh, we got a Korn CD.
Uh, we got a copy of Cider
House Rules on laser disc.
Don't know why we thought
that would be valuable.
That's a collector's item.
That's gonna be very... Be
very careful with that.
Oh, my God, you guys, this is
a letter to my future self.
What?!
Yeah. "Dear future Dee,
How's Hollywood?
Congrats on all of your success.
Stay grounded.
Enclosed is a check for
one million dollars.
Be sure to give it to Dr.
Larry Myers as a thank you for all of
his inspiration."
Is this stupid?
This is just stupid.
Who's Dr. Larry Myers?
Nobody. Doesn't matter.
Just my high school drama teacher.
This is just... it's dumb.
Like, why would we put such
stupid stuff in here, and also
we bur-buried it, and then we
opened it ten years later?
What, are you supposed to just,
oh, bury it, open right up, and
not give yourself any time to
fulfill any kind of dreams or...
The whole thing's dumb.
Like, Cider House Rules?
Okay.
Hormones.
She's all worked out.
It's the fattening.
What else is in there?
Uh, oh!
Old pictures! Old pictures!
Pictures!
Holy shit, look at that!
Look!
The gang.
Whew.
Who's this jag-off?
Look.
Oh, that's Schmidty!
Schmidty!
He was the fourth member of our crew.
There was another member of the gang?
Oh, yeah, dude.
I miss him, dude.
Why did we ditch him in the first place?
I can't remember.
I don't know.
Eh, he wasn't a good fit.
Remember? You know?
Kind of got on our nerves.
He didn't get on my nerves.
No, he never got on my nerves.
I actually really loved that guy.
You know what, I remember now.
Charlie soured on him, and then
he, like, gave us an ultimatum.
You remember?
And then we all turned on th guy pretty quickly...
I mean, we all agreed he was
out of the... You pushed him out
of a moving car and yelled
"You're out of the gang!"
Now, in hindsight, that
does seem a little rash.
Yeah, it was a bit of a snap decision.
Why don't you call this Schmidty guy
up and see what he's up to now?
You know, I do feel like
we owe the guy an apology.
Yeah. You know what, I'd
love to see Schmidty.
I would, too.
Yeah, but that's a bad
snap decision, you know?
Like, there's a reason
he didn't work out.
We got a good thing going
on now without him.
We don't need a new
member of the gang.
Don't get Schmidty.
I'm really *** to meet this guy.
Oh, he was the coolest.
Seriously.
Oh...
- Hey.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Mrs. Schmidt, it's it's Dennis.
And Mac. You remember us, right?
We're looking for Schmidty. He around?
He's dead.
Oh, gosh, that is too bad.
We're sorry for your loss.
Hiyah!
What's up bitches?
That's Schmidty?
Hey, we thought that you were dead.
- He made me say it.
- I made you say it. listen to you, mom.
You seen that shit?
He jumped down a whole
flight of stairs.
I didn't see you down there, Chuckles.
How you been, little man?
Not that little, you know?
Regular size.
Maybe he, but...
Not anymore.
Put on a few LB's since
I saw you last, huh?
No. Same weight.
Same weight I always been.
Yeah, no, he put on a lot of weight.
No, you tacked on weight.
I tacked on mass, muscle mass.
Who's this old son of a bitch?
I'm Frank.
Frank?
Frank.
I'm Schmidty.
Nice to... put her there.
No!
Don't kiss him.
Hey, uh, so what brings
you dicks here, huh?
Oh, well, Schmidty, um, honestly, we
came around here because we, um...
Go ahead.
...want to say we're
sorry, Schmidty.
Yeah, yeah, we... Can
you take this, Mac?
Yeah, man, I got this.
Hey, man, we just want to say
we're sorry for icing you out in
the past, and we'd
like your forgiveness.
Yeah.
Get on your knees and ask.
Excuse me?
Get down on your knees and ask.
Show some humility, for Christ's sake.
Really?
Yeah.
Ah, man.
Whatever it takes, Schmidty.
Wow, you're really doing it.
I'm kidding.
Ah!
Oh, oh, he's joking!
Oh, man!
Come on, guys, have some dignity,
some respect for yourselves.
You forgive us?
Absolutely.
Classy, Schmidty.
Very classy.
Dr. Myers?
Yes?
Hi.
Dee Reynolds.
I was in the school musical.
Frankenstein.
Yes, of course!
Deandra Reynolds!
Yeah!
Sit, darling, sit.
Thank you.
Listen, I came to talk to you about high school.
I... Oh, uh...
I was drinking a lot back then, so
if I did anything inappropriate...
Oh, no, no, no.
Not at all.
In fact, the opposite.
You were, like, the most
inspiring teacher I had.
In fact, I-I wrote you this check
ten years ago.
In hopes that I can one day give it
to you, as a thank you.
May you rot in hell,
- you retched beast!
- Oh...
- Um, I'm confused...
- Frankenstein.
That's what the villagers screamed at you,
just before you
threw yourself at the funeral pier.
Aah.
You were such a hideous
delight in that show.
Thank you.
Yes, okay.
So you're saying "don't give up",
- I shouldn't give up on my dream.
- No my dear, you must give up. You must.
It's far too late for you.
But it's not too late to teach.
Come speak to the kids, inspire them.
It's an opportunity to share
your unique experiences.
Uh-huh.
The question is: Will you seize it?
Mm...
No, thank you.
Five...
What?
...four, three...
No, I just never wanted to be teaching.
two, one...
No offense.
What are you doing?
Okay, yes.
And there you have it!
A teacher is born.
Well...
Man, this is unbelievable, huh?
Working at a bar, running a bar?
This has got to be, like, the
greatest job ever, right?
It is, man, this is what we do.
Yeah, lot of dicking around, huh?
Hey, um, you're still, uh,
living with your mom, huh?
That sounds kind of lame.
Yeah, well, I mean, it's
the MS that's really lame.
You know?
Oh, your mom has...?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
She's doing all right, though.
I moved in with her to take care
of her and stuff like that.
It's good to really get to know her
before, you know, uh, she moves on.
Oh... Kind of a downer,
that story, though.
Kind of a downer.
What about you, man?
What's your living
situation like these days?
What do you do?
What are you up to?
Uh, it's pretty sweet.
I am.
I'm his living situation.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, we share a bed.
Well, not every night.
That's hilarious.
You know, Charlie and
I used to be roomies.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, you remember that?
Hey, you remember how you used
to try to get me to play all
those-those lame games, you know, those
weird things you'd want to do at night?
Like, uh, Night Crawlers.
- I play Night Crawlers all the time.
- You do?
Frank enjoys this game very much.
Correct me if I'm wrong, but to make
Night Crawlers a little bit better
you should use blankets, right?
You take a piece of dirt.
Exactly, you can use it as a force field,
or as a roaming base.
Yeah, it's kind of a good idea
cause, you know,
- it's an imagination based game.
- It's still imagination based.
Oh, I have an idea.
Dennis, remember you and Mac were
laughing when I did the butt dance?
They love that when I do it.
Guys, watch me, watch me, will you?
Oh, yeah!
5, 6, 7, 8...
* butt, butt, butt *
Oh, Charlie, no...
- Where is this coming from?
- This is embarrassing.
- Guys, be excited!
- Charlie, lemme see.
You're not having fun doing this,
so we're not having fun watching it, buddy.
Watch, it's like this, it's like
I don't know, something like
* butt, butt, butt *
* butt! *
Hoo-hoo-hoo!
Hyah!
Butt dance 2.0.
Beautiful, man.
Schmitdy, know what you got?
You know what you got that Charlie
doesn't really quite have?
You have that "it" factor.
You know what I'm saying?
It's charisma.
It's, like, you got it.
Hey, you guys!
Uh, can I talk to you in the back
office for a second real quick?
I can't believe this dude.
He has not changed in years, man.
Look, you guys need to make
a decision right now, okay?
It is either him, or it is me.
Him.
Yeah.
I was going to say him, too.
Yeah, him, him.
Yeah, you know, it's always been him.
I don't know why I
didn't see that before.
I'm out of the gang?
Him.
Hello, everybody.
Hi, there.
My name is Dee Reynolds, and not
only am I a professional actress
and comedienne, uh, but I also
used to go to school here.
What have you acted in?
A lot of... a lot.
I've acted in a lot of things.
You-you may not have seen
all of them or any of them.
You know, it's not time for questions.
I'll let you know when
it's time for questions, though, ok?
And the phone goes away.
And the phone goes into your pocket
or into your backpack,
but not out, in your fingers,
because I'm talking.
No, I'm a'ight.
Yeah, said the turkey.
Uh-oh.
Oh, no.
Who's she?
She's somebody that'll
zing you back, right?
I'll zing you.
I'll zap you, I'll zing you,
so just know that about me.
You know, I know that, uh, you guys
are 18 and you're seniors, and so...
Okay, what is it that they're doing?
What is this that they're doing?
Oh, they're doing
their coughing thing.
Yeah, I hear that.
All right, kids, settle down.
You can, uh, read, pull out
your phones, whatever.
They do love their phones.
What...? That's it?
You're just going to sit in the corner
and hem away at your sock all day?
No, where...
where is the teacher that I knew?
Where is that inspirational man?
My enthusiasm in those days was
fueled entirely by the alcohol.
Dee, hey!
Come here, come here.
Charlie, what are you...
what are you doing?
Got kicked out of the gang.
What are you up to?
You want to hang out?
No, Charlie.
I don't want to hang out.
I-I have a job.
I'm a teacher now, so I got to get
back to inspiring some students.
Oh, that's pretty sweet.
You want to toss some
inspiration my way, you know,
'cause the guys think Schmidty's
all that and, like, I'm no good?
Okay, Charlie, how about this?
You are really good at cleaning
shit out of toilets and-and
taking trash and throwing it
into dumpsters, so why don't you
get a new job somewhere else
doing those kinds of things and
make friends there, okay?
Okay, Dee, so are you saying
get a job here as a janitor,
and then you and I
can be best friends?
That is absolutely not
what I was saying.
I'm going to talk to the
principal, see if I can get that
job, and then we'll work
on the friendship thing.
Don't do that.
No, don't do that.
Charlie, don't do that.
Oh, Goddamn it, don't do that.
That... this is my thing.
What, what, what, what, what?
Here we go.
Hey, all right!
There's the man.
What's up, buddy?
This place is pretty nice.
Yeah.
What's going on? You guys are gonna try
and bang me afterwards or something?
Very nice turn you made.
Um, we only come here
for special occasions.
- Yeah.
- Good, good, what's the occasion?
Well we brought you to this luncheon, Schmidty,
because we want to make this official.
Mac, do you have the ring?
Ok, great, um...
Schmidty, we, uh...
We missed a lot of good, good years.
- A lot of special time...
- Yeah?
- ...with you. And...
- Thanks.
- You know what, I don't think I can do this.
- It's alright, I'll take this.
- Why is he being a big damn puss?
- Um, Schmidty...
- He's emotional.
- We want you back...
if you'll have this.
What the hell is this shit?
It's a sterling silver clover ring.
When we put all four of them
together, makes a four-leaf
clover, solidifying our
bond for all time.
You're kidding, though, right?
No, we've never been more
serious in our lives.
Yeah.
Yeah, whatever, I don't care.
Sure.
All right!
He said yes!
That's a yes!
We bagged him.
We certainly did.
Oh, food's here!
Food is here.
Oh, no, wait, though.
I didn't order yet.
Oh, that's okay.
I took care of the food already.
Yes, Dennis orders for us.
That is a humongous shrimp.
Well, it's 'cause it's not a
shrimp, Frank; it's a prawn.
Yeah, and I don't like prawns,
so I eat around them.
Well, I'll take your prawns
if you want to take my salad.
Eh.
No?
Okay, yeah, that's what I'll do.
Yeah, you can do that.
Just put your prawns on the salad.
Why don't you just order what you want?
Uh, well, Dennis kind
of has the best palate.
Yeah, I have the most
refined palate, Schmidty.
That's just how we do things now.
You've been away for a while.
It's fine.
No, no, that's not
what I'm going to do.
Excuse me.
Hey, come here really quick.
Um, can I get, uh...
you have linguine?
Yeah, can I get linguine instead?
And, uh, what do you guys want?
Order whatever you want.
Linguine's too heavy for lunch.
No, no, what do you want?
- I want fries.
- Fries for this guy.
I can have fries?
Oh, you don't like your
salad all of a sudden, Mac?
I... Dennis, I hate salad.
You hate salad?
Where is this coming from?
I hate this restaurant.
Yeah, this restaurant blows.
I'll have a ginger ale.
All right, there you go.
Come on, man, get into it.
I'm saying that now.
Can I say that now?
What?
Hyah!
Absolutely, take it.
It's yours.
By all means.
What'd you get, a ginger ale?
I'm a little confused.
Are you telling me that this photo
of Bruce Jenner is your résumé?
Well, when I showed up this
morning, I didn't have a formal
résumé on me, so I was sort
of hoping the photograph of
Mr. Jenner could...
could represent the standard of
excellence I'm hoping to
bring to this position.
I see, and you're looking for a
job as a substitute teacher?
Substitute janitor, all right?
Look, I'll clean this building
so good, you're not going to
know what to do with yourself.
You know what I mean?
And I'm not a proud man.
You know, I'll do the jobs that
the other guys don't want to do.
I'll degrade myself.
I'll make a genuine ass out of myself.
Yeah.
Hey, look, I'll swallow that eraser
whole just to prove it to you.
Uh, no, no.
Please, please, no.
I'll swallow it whole.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
You don't have to do that, but
I-I have to say, I don't think
I've ever encountered someone
who's so passionate about
joining our custodial staff.
The passion I have for the work that I
do is extraordinary.
It probably goes beyond janitor.
Uh-uh.
And I'm serious. I'm gonna
eat that eraser whole.
Oh, no, no, it's not...
it's not necessary.
You don't need to t the
eraser to prove your point.
Uh, you have the job.
Are you serious?
I love your attitude.
It's fantastic.
Sir, I am not going to let you down.
I mean, I'm going to start
cleaning immediately.
Immediately.
Uh, but first, can I eat the eraser?
You're saying you want
to eat the eraser?
Well, I'm asking you if it's edible
because it certainly smells of grapes.
I don't think it's edible.
Can I just test it?
I'd rather you didn't.
I kinda want... I might need it.
All right.
You win this one.
I'll pick up one of my own.
I'll eat that one.
That way everybody wins.
All right, well, welcome aboard.
All right, all right, thanks so much.
Ridiculous. It's ridiculous.
I mean, where the hell is he?
What did we say?
We said 3:00.
So we said 3:00, and it's, like...
Hyah!
What's crappenin', fellas?
Hey, Schmidty, running
kinda late there, huh?
Am I?
I didn't think it mattered.
How could it not matter?
I mean, this is the final phase
of your initiation back into
the gang, so it kinda
matters a matters a lot.
It actually does.
Whoa. Um, where's your ring?
Oh, come on.
You didn't want me to really
wear that thing, did ya?
Yeah...
Oh.
We're sort of sticklers for
that kind of thing, too.
So pop that on.
I will. Okay.
Sorry about that.
Time and ring. Good. Got it.
Yeah.
Oh! Hey, look at this!
Nice setup fellas.
Candles? Where did you steal
these from, huh?
Uh-oh!
When the hell'd you take that?
Don't worry about it, Schmidty.
We got to ya.
This is weird as hell.
You guys see that, right?
What's weird about this?
This is a men's ceremony, okay?
They have ceremonies for
all sorts of men's clubs.
Yeah, the Mafia, the
Freemasons, the White House.
The White House, they do it.
This is cool, okay?
Trust me, what we're
doing is very cool.
Okay.
Mack, why don't we get started?
You'll get it.
He'll understand as the
ceremony progresses.
All right, Schmidty, please have
a seat in the ceremonial seat.
I'll do the candles.
Uh, Frank, please do the candles.
Dennis, the song.
All right, the song.
Uh, (laughs) look at that!
All right, take it, take
it take it seriously.
I am. I'm locked in.
Okay, I will now begin the ceremony by
administering a sweet roundhouse kick
to the bell.
To the bell?
Uh-oh, whiff!
I just missed that.
Dude, you're not even close.
No, Schmidty, this is all
part of the ceremony.
You gotta stretch
before this thing, huh?
Enjoy it.
One last crack, come on.
Oh, man, this is pathetic.
Here, dude, look, it goes
something like this.
Hyah!
I'm excited. I am.
I mean, the first part of the
ceremony was a little lame, but
ending it with a hot air
balloon ride, that kicks ass.
Yeah, yeah, all those things.
Yup.
Frank, now!
Push, Frank, push!
Go, go, go!
I got him. I got him.
Come on. Stop.
Get out!
Come on, Frank, Frank, push him out!
What are you doing, trying to push
me out of a moving car again?
Yes.
Goddamn it, pull over.
Why are you doing this?
I'll just pull over.
Good job, Frank.
Tub of lard over here.
Give me back the ring, all right?
'Cause you don't deserve it!
- Take the ring.
- Get out of here!
You're out of the gang, Schmidty!
Get out! You're out! You're out!
Okay, got it. I heard ya.
Nice seeing you guys again.
Very nice meeting you.
Get out of the car!
I heard you.
I'm getting out, okay?
Now, Dennis, peel out.
I was gonna peel out and...
Don't take the steam out.
Tell people we pushed you!
All right, class, feel free to text or
watch movies, whatever it is you do.
Not today, Doc.
What are you doing, Dee?
I am inspiring you.
Rise and shine, dickwad.
Okay, this is a great teacher,
but he is wasted on you.
Well, not anymore.
We're gonna be rehearsing a little
musical today called Frankenstein.
This is stupid.
Get out.
You're stupid, What?
You heard me.
You get out of here, you stupid idiot.
It's fine with me.
Yeah, good.
And anybody else who doesn't want to be
here today, you can get out now, too.
Hey, you want to go to the mall?
No, no, wait. No, no, stop.
Now come on, you guys!
That's... Not everybody.
Sit back down.
That's just something people say.
You guys are gonna love this.
Okay, let's get started.
Have you seen Dr. Frankenstein's creation
that they all speak of?
Nay, I've heard tales
told of his hideousness.
A monster most foul.
♪ My face composed of
rotten flesh, roar, roar!
♪ A hideous beast with deadly
clutch, roar, roar!
♪ Another's heart beats in my chest
I'll never know a woman's touch... Roar! ♪
And then I retreat into the mist
and Dr. Myers, you are Dr. Frankenstein
so get up here and get acting!
With pleasure, Dee!
Just let me set the
loop, and here I come!
Oh, whoops. That's not...
I am shattered to pieces!
Are you acting right now?
No, I'm not acting, you bitch!
I think I've broke my hip.
Why is this damn stage so slippery?
Charlie boy!
This floor is slippery, man.
Old school slippery 'cause I
waxed it real good with this
awesome power waxer that
the school provided me.
I did this whole place
in, like, two hours.
Oh, nice. Whoa, that's impressive.
Yeah.
Dee inspired me.
She said, "You're an
awesome janitor, Charlie.
"You can make this whole
school slippery."
I said, "Sure, I'll
give it my best shot."
Then she's, like, "Let's
be best friends."
And I was, like, "Sure, I'll
give that my best shot, too."
So we're best friends now.
Yeah, yeah, that's quite a conversation
you had with her, isn't it?
Mm-hmm.
What do you guys want?
Oh, well, we, uh, we came to ya
because we wanted to tell you
that we're sorry for picking
Schmidty over you, and we feel
like we made a big mistake,
and we want you back, buddy.
And, uh, we pushed
him out of a moving car for you.
I can't do it.
What is wrong with you?
All right, I'll handle it.
Charlie, we have an announcement
to make: it's your lucky day.
We want you back.
Yeah.
Gotta say this is pretty
classy, guys, but I wish you
gave me one of these a long time
time ago 'cause I'm a janitor now.