Frank, I'd like to
thank you for giving me the
opportunity of a lifetime.
Whatever.
I hope they have some cool,
exotic creatures for us to
fiddle around with and play with.
Dennis, we're going
to an animal rights event.
There's gonna be all sorts
of exotic creatures there.
You think so?
SWEET DEE: Oh.
They better have some
cool stuff at this thing.
I mean, the money I laid out for this
charity... they could have built a zoo.
Yeah. Actually, guys,
zoos are animal prisons.
See, I've been boning up on my
animal rights literature so I
can have some talking
points with Chase.
He's a big animal rights lover,
and he's gonna be there.
Security is not gonna let you go
anywhere near Chase Utley, bro.
Those creepy letters
you've been writing him?
You've got to be on a list somewhere.
What are you giving me shit for, okay?
Oh!
Dee's the one going after
Ryan Howard all of a sudden.
Well, so what?
Why is that weird?
That makes perfect sense.
I'm a hot, single lady.
He's a hot, single man.
Hot? Dee,
you're pregnant as shit.
Frank, this shortcut sucks.
It ain't a shortcut.
Why in the hell are we in the woods?
Get on the A.C. Expressway.
Goes straight to Atlantic City.
I'm avoiding tolls.
Okay, hold on a second.
You're willing to shell out tons
of money for a charity, and you
can't spare a couple
bucks for a toll road?
What? What do you want me to do, give
all my money to some toll jockey?
Yeah.
Just for riding on a street?
Squirrel!
Oh, thank God.
That was close.
Why did you do that, Mac?
Goddamn it!
You almost ran over
that squirrel, Frank.
So you should have
let me mash it.
*
I can't wait to make my speech.
I'm gonna get up there and lace
into these liberal nut jobs.
What? I thought you
loved animals now.
No. I only donated all this money so I
could make a mockery of their cause.
Animals should be food,
rugs and trophies.
Why do you think I'm
wearing a leather suit?
Are you? Is that leather?
Bet your ass it's leather.
Huh.
I just assumed it was plastic.
Who wears a plastic suit?
I don't know, Frank.
*
All right, listen, I'm gonna call us
a tow truck and get us out of here.
I'm not getting any bars, though.
You getting any bars, Frank?
I got nothing. What gives?
What gives is that we're in the
middle of goddamn nowhere.
What happened?
Are we in A.C.?
No, we're not in A.C.
because Mac wrecked the car, and now
we're stranded somewhere.
Oh, man!
Oh.
"Come to Atlantic City," you said.
"Let us tie you up and put a sack on
your head so you don't freak out.
That'll be a good adventure,"
you said.
Well, I'm freaking out a little bit.
Right. Relax. Relax, Charlie.
This is gonna be a great
adventure, this is exciting.
This is the unknown.
This is all part of it, man.
Well, it ain't a great
adventure to me.
Riding on a private jet, sipping
champagne... that's an adventure.
Then why didn't you fly us
in a private jet to A.C.?
It's only 80 miles.
You know how quick that trip would be?
Be a total waste of money.
See, this is why I don't
leave Philly, all right?
You leave Philly, and
bad shit happens.
I mean trees? Everywhere trees?
What the hell is this place?
All right, I'm hitching
a ride back home.
Calm down, Charlie.
Let's all walk, and we'll
find some help, okay?
I'm not walking, 'cause I got a
baby on board, my feet hurt.
Yeah, I'm not going anywhere
'cause this suit is, like,
chafing me up like crazy.
Oh, Jesus. All right.
Mac and I and Charlie will go
find some help, okay? Okay?
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh,
except I'm not gonna go.
I'm gonna hang back
and oil up my glove.
Your glove?
What is your endgame in this?
I'm gonna have a catch
with Chase Utley.
You... We got... Chase Utley is
not gonna have a catch with you.
Come on, come on.
Don't you say that, Charlie!
Don't you say that!
Listen, listen.
We're gonna find help, okay?
Hurry up, guys.
Hurry up, 'cause I
got to get to Chase.
*
Well, listen.
Sometimes, even I can't control everything,
so when a new experience presents
itself to me, I try to stay
open to it and just say yes.
Say yes, huh?
Yeah.
Hey, let me show you something.
Let me show you something.
Look.
Huh. You wearing makeup?
Yeah, I'm always wearing a
little bit of foundation, but
that's not the point, Charlie.
What do you see there?
Oh, shit!
You got a lesion, dude.
No, it's not...
That's not a lesion.
It's a hickey.
Oh.
You never seen a hickey?
No, I have. Ew! Weird!
I thought women our age
didn't give hickeys anymore.
Oh, no, they don't.
Young ladies do, though, and I
met an extremely young lady the
other day, and she gave me this.
Weird.
No, she was legal.
She was totally legal.
I always check their licenses.
That's not the point.
The point is, how did I
meet this young woman?
Well, I got caught unexpectedly
in a rainstorm one day, so I
retreated into a local theater.
There, I caught a matinee.
And during this matinee,
I saw this young woman.
I introduced myself, and we both
got caught up in the moment, and
we said yes to the new
experience, and that's how I
wound up with this wonderful
and very sexual hickey.
Oh.
You see what I'm saying
about adventure, Charlie?
Yeah, you always say
yes to everything.
Well, no, I don't always say yes.
That's absurd.
I'd be a dead man, wouldn't I,
if I said yes to everything?
Yeah. Oh, shit, dude.
Look at that truck right there.
Oh, yeah.
You think there's someone in there?
Well... what do we say in
this scenario, Charlie?
We say yes.
Hiya.
Sorry to wake you up there.
Sorry.
What do you want?
Oh, uh, our car broke down a
little ways back, and we were
hoping maybe you could help us out.
Oh, I could, uh, radio that in
and get you a tow truck out
here, but I'm about to
hit the road myself.
You can always hitch a ride with me.
Oh. Uh, where you headed?
Atlantic City.
You got any munchies in the car?
I'm grumbling.
No, Frank, we don't have
anything in the car because we
were starving ourselves
for the casino buffet.
It was only supposed to
be a 45-minute drive.
I got to eat pretty soon.
I'm starting to get woozy.
Yeah, I'm starting to get woozy, too.
I've been starving myself
for a few days for Chase.
What?
Oh, I wanted to create that sort
of gaunt, angular look with
my cheekbones to impress him, you know,
give myself a more athletic look.
But... I'm starving.
All right, let's jump into the forest,
and we'll find some food there.
*
We are not killing any animals, okay?
Screw that! I'm hungry.
It's wabbit season.
Okay, fine.
Dee, come with me.
I'm gonna find us something to eat.
Where are you, wabbit?
I'm gonna get you, wabbit.
Oh.
There you are.
What the hell!
Wabbit?
Where'd you go?
Shit!
How'd you do that?
Why are you staring at me?
Why you giving me that look?
Whoa.
We're having a moment here, aren't we?
You boys are, uh...
awfully dressed up.
Oh. Yeah. Yeah, the tuxes.
Sure, yeah, well, we're on our way to
Atlantic City for a charity event.
You kind of threw me
with those outfits.
Don't usually find lot lizards out in
the wild.
Yeah, you know what, I'm a
little behind on my trucker terms.
A "lot lizard" would be a, uh...?
A lizard.
You know, truck stop whores.
- I mean...
- Oh!
Oh!
No, no... no offense.
No, man, none taken.
Because we're not whores.
No, no, we're not prostitutes.
Definitely not a lizard.
Hey, hey, hey, shh.
Hey.
Your secret's safe with me.
Don't worry, too, I'm not a cop.
And I'm not gonna judge you, neither.
A man's got to make a living, and looking
the way you do, I'm not surprised.
I'm not surprised.
Oh, I appreciate that, I appreciate that, but again...
Not lizards, though.
Not prostitutes.
Save your seduction for
someone else, all right?
I do not tangle with lizards no more.
No. Back in the day, sure,
I would've indulged, hell!
I would've let you turn me
into Swiss cheese.
I would've let you make me a...
make me into a mailbox... just
open the slot and put
whatever you want inside.
Oh...
Not no more.
I got a wife now.
So I will not suck you, and I
will not be sucked on... by you.
'Kay?
That's it.
That's a 10-4.
Yeah, we read you loud and clear,
and just to reiterate, we
- don't suck on people... we own a bar.
- So... You run a bar?
Yeah, well, I'm sure you do.
*
It's grass, Mac.
You're eating grass.
Well, look, I see Charlie eating
grass all the time, okay?
Oh, really?
Okay, well, Charlie is not an
example of good health, so...
Look, Charlie is a
survivor, all right?
And that's the way we have to
think... eat anything to survive.
Oh. What is that?
That's a dead crow.
Well, I'm definitely not eating that.
Wait, whoa, whoa. Why not?
Because it is a disgusting
dead bird, that's why.
You eat dead chickens and dead turkeys
all the time... That's so hypocritical.
Okay, that's not hypocritical...
People eat chickens and turkeys.
Nobody eats a crow.
It's a trash bird.
You know what I do think?
I think we're gonna give
this crow a proper burial.
Well, I'm not gonna do that.
But what I will is use it as bait.
Ooh. What if we hide in the
bushes, and then we wait for
something higher on the food
chain to come along and grab it,
- and then we grab that and eat it...
- That's a good idea.
I'm gonna go to the car.
I'm not doing it. No.
I'm gonna go to the car and
I'm gonna get a blanket, then
we can pick up this trash bird
with it, and we'll do my plan.
I'm not helping you.
That's all right, I'll do
it myself... I'll eat alone.
I'm gonna find Frank, I'm gonna
get him on my team, okay?
Good.
Frank?
Hey, Frank, where are you, bro?
Oh, there you are.
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
Mac, I'm having a
thing with this rabbit here.
Whoa, dude!
He's staring right at you.
We've been staring at each
other for ten minutes.
I-I... He's not afraid of me.
He's looking at me like he knows
me, he's looking at me like he
can see right through my soul.
He probably can, dude.
That is the connection
between man and beast.
Animals can see souls.
That is a fact of nature.
Oh!
Deandra, what the hell are you doing?!
Oh, you guys, I got it.
I got it.
We can eat.
We can't eat the rabbit...
He's got my soul.
What are you talking about?
They had a moment, Dee.
They shared a connection.
I know it's cute, you guys, but,
come on, this isn't about
us anymore... I got to feed the baby.
Mac, grab it by the head
and wring its neck off.
I would rather grab your head and
wring your neck, for wanting
to kill this rabbit, all right?
You want to eat it
so bad, you kill it.
Fine. I will kill it.
I'll kill it, and I'll eat it myself.
I'm gonna kill the
shit out of it.
*
Great, yeah, thanks.
No, we were hoping to be dropped
off at a casino, though.
This is just a motel.
I know, and I thought we would slip into
a room, and you... could check my oil.
- Oh. No. Um...
- What happened, man?
No, I'm sorry. No.
No.
Shoot, hell, maybe I knew I wanted it when I...
I gave you the ride.
No, no, no, no, you're better...
Byron.
Remember you changed?
Byron, you've changed... you don't
want this kind of thing anymore.
No, I do want this kind of thing.
No, you don't.
You would not suck me and you
would not, um, be sucked by me.
Be sucked by us.
I take that back.
I don't mean that.
You can't take that back, Byron!
- I didn't mean any of those...
- Look, man, think about your
wife... Remember, you
said you love your wife.
I do, I do, I do.
Good.
I do, but... I got cash
in my pocket, I got desire in my
heart, and I'm a-frothin' and
a-foamin', and I was thinking...
Hey, hey, I got an idea.
What do you say...
we slip into a room and you two
split me open like a coconut?
Oh... Dennis, what do we
say in this situation?
We say no.
Why? No? Why?
It's just... Oh, my God!
Another...
Should've locked my damn door.
I should've locked the door.
Yeah, well, that was
definitely an adventure, huh?
Yeah, well, sometimes the
adventures aren't always good ones.
Yeah, but I said yes to the
new experience, right?
I'm out of Philly, I'm alive, and
I'm not afraid of truckers anymore.
Yeah, well, if anything, you should
be more afraid of truckers now.
But I do see your point.
Hey, listen, I'm gonna try and get
in touch with the guys, okay?
Aw, shit.
Dude, I left my jacket in the truck.
I had everything in that jacket.
I had all my money, I had my
phone... do you have any money?
Uh, yeah, it's all right there.
I put it all on black.
What? No, no, no, no, no!
Black wins!
Baby!
Oh, phew! All right, but that
was lucky, that was lucky.
Yeah, I know, but you know
what, dude, you were right...
I said yes to this little
adventure and I won.
Would you like to bet again, sir?
Yes, I would.
No. No. No.
Let it ride, please.
What are you doing?
Dude, I am gonna say
yes to everything!
We can't say yes to everything.
That is all of our money, dude.
No, it's all my money.
You lost yours when you
said no to the trucker.
What? Did you want to say yes
to the trucker?
*
walk away with a free 18-wheeler.
Dude, we are gonna
lose all of our money.
Black wins again!
Oh, baby! Whoo! Yes!
Yes, yes!
Let it ride, please.
Let it ride.
Okay, okay, yeah, let it ride.
I want to bash you, bunny.
I want to give you one good bash and
eat your sweet, delicious meat.
You can't kill the rabbit,
Deandra... It's got my soul.
It's got the man's soul, Dee.
Maybe I'll suffocate you.
I'll suffocate your rabbit face,
and then I'll just suck all the
- life out of it and then... twist your neck and...
- Look, can we do this thing,
for crying out loud?
Yes, absolutely.
This is absolutely ridiculous,
holding a funeral for a crow.
Yes, that's right, we are.
We are honoring its life.
I want to say a couple words.
Yes, please.
Uh, I've never been good to animals,
wearing a leather suit and all.
And, uh, also, I kicked a dog
in a subway once, it was a real
jerk move, and I'm really sorry I
did it, and I like animals now.
That was beautiful, Frank.
Okay, where the hell are
Charlie and Dennis?
I feel like they're not
coming back for us.
Okay, they're coming back, okay?
Guys... Let's just do the right thing.
Good night... sweet prince.
Oh, God, you-you got to be kidding me.
Come on.
FRANK AND MAC: # Ave Maria... #
Are you kidding me?
I mean, I never thought
I would hold $15,000.
Amazing, bro.
Listen, I thought I was
teaching you today.
Let me tell you something, my
friend, you were teaching me.
I know. I mean, look at
all this amazing food.
Oh, I'm starving.!
*
What is that?
Hi, there.
You two are with the Reynolds party, yes?
Yeah. Yes.
Is one of you Frank?
Oh, actually, uh...
Yes.
Hi, Mr. Reynolds.
I'm Debra.
We spoke on the phone.
Yes. Yes.
Well, now, I know you'd
like to say a few words.
Is it all right if we
have you up to speak now?
Uh...
Yes, it is.
Great.
Yes. Yes, yes, yes.
Mr. Reynolds here is one
of our largest new donors.
Well, it's donors like him that makes
our work for animals possible.
Thank you.
I am Frank Reynolds.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes.
Yes.
That's the word I want to talk about.
But first, let's talk about animals.
Yeah.
If animals have taught me
anything, it's that you can
easily die, and very quickly, under
a bus and on the side of the road.
Yes.
Okay?
So you have to live in the now.
Live in the now!
Mm-hmm.
I'm gonna live in the now right now.
I'm gonna donate another $5,000
to this charity right now.
Oh! Oh!
That's a...
That's too generous.
This is for the rats.
Take it easy.
All right. Oh!
For the rats, people.
Okay. Yeah, yeah.
And I'm done.
Good, good.
Uh, Mr. Reynolds,
there's one more thing.
Per your request, we were able
to arrange a surprise night for
your friend with two true
all-stars of our organization...
Chase Utley and Ryan Howard
of the Philadelphia Phillies.
Oh!
Hi.
Mac, right?
Uh... yes.
I hear you're my number one fan.
Yes, I am.
Hi. Hi.
Hi.
What's up, brother.
All right.
Oh, my goodness.
All right, let's get crazy.
Let's get crazy.
Let's get nuts, you guys.
Go get nuts, guys.
# I had a friend Was a
big baseball player #
Ah.
# Bac Bin high school We went back
inside, sat down Had a few drinks... #
- And you got a, uh...
- Please don't touch me.
# Glory days Yeah, they'll
pass you by Glory days #
I'm gonna need some more of that.
# Of a young Got it.
# Yeah They'll pass you by... #
No Mets fans!
Get out of here.
What are you thinking?
# Glory days... #
All right.
Ooh.
# Ooh, yeah All right... #
# All right... #
Yeah!
# Ooh, yeah Oh, yeah All right #
# All right #
# All right... #
Guys, guys, calm down.
You're gonna hurt each other.
Huh?
No, we're good, man.
We're just having fun.
I just saw you bite that dude.
- Yeah, it was a...
- He took a bite.
It was a fair bite.
Yeah, I do like to
bite him a little bit.
Man, come here, come here.
Wrestle with us, dude.
Hey, yeah.
You guys are wasted, man.
Let's wrestle.
Yeah, you're wasted.
No, we're not.
You're not wasted?
No, no, we're completely sober,
but you guys drank a lot, though.
Yeah.
You guys drink more than
anybody I've ever seen.
Oh, really, dude?
Oh, really?
Ah...
Good work, Charlie. Yeah.
That's what we do.
Well, you know, it's been great, fellas,
but, uh, we're gonna take off now.
Oh!
Really? You guys gonna go?
Yeah, you guys, try not to
hurt anybody tonight, okay?
Nah, dude, nah.
No, no, no, we're good, dude.
We're good, dude.
Get off me, though, for reals.
Okay.
You guys take care, okay?
Yeah.
All right.
Whoo! Boy, that was a...
...hell of a night, man.
Hell of a night, man.
Hey, how much money do we have left?
10,000 bucks.
I got an idea how we
can spend that shit.
Champagne!
Champagne! Champagne!
Here we go, gentlemen.
Thank you, Penelope.
Oh, it's tearing me up inside.
What? What?!
What's going on?
Frank, what are you doing?
I ate the crow.
What... what'd he say?
What?
I ate the crow.
Why?
I dug it up last night.
I thought it would taste like
chicken, but I was wrong.
Oh, my God.
I think I got to go to a hospital.
All right.
All right, look, they're clearly
not coming back for us, okay?
*
Oh.
Oh, man.
Seriously, I'm gonna be sad
when this is all over.
Yeah, well, all good adventures
must come to an end at some point.
All good things are ending.
I shouldn't still be drinking.
Hey.
Mm-hmn?
I just thought of one last
thing that would be awesome.
Give me your phone.
All right.
Oh, this is gonna be...
this is gonna be awesome, dude.
It's just gonna be great.
Look at this.
I know, it feels like we're
walking a lot here, bunny, but I
tell you what, as soon as we get
back to the bar, you can have as
many carrots as your
little heart desires.
Dee, first you wanted to kill it, and
now you're bringing it back to the bar?
Yeah.
I named him "Peter, Peter, Nickel-Eater".
'Cause last night in the car,
he tried to eat a nickel.
It was the cutest
thing I've ever seen.
I say you bash its
brains in right now.
I'm done liking animals.
This crow is eating me alive!
Frank, you are sick because
you ate rancid, maggot-filled
meat, not because of animals.
And, Dee, you've got to
set that rabbit free.
Really?
Yes! It needs to live in the
wild, where it can be free and
safe in the loving embrace
of Mother Nature, okay?
Trust me, Peter Nickels-Eater
is gonna be much happier.
Yeah, all right.
You're right.
Okay, buddy, I love you, but
go back to your family now.
Go on.
Okay.
See? He's happier already.
He's gonna go back to his mother
and father, and he's gonna have
a wonderful life.
God... damn it!
Goddamn it!
Okay, nature is bullshit.
I'm done with this.
I told you, animals suck.
Oh. Wait. Was that a text?
You getting reception?
Yes, I guess I'm getting
reception... I just got a text.
Oh, it's from Dennis.
Ooh.
I think he sent me a picture.
No.
No!
Oh! You guys, you guys, a car!
Hey!
No.
Hi-yo!
Hey! Wait-wait-wait-wait!
Wait!
Oh, good.
Hey there!
Y'all need a ride?
Yes. Yes.
Yeah.
Must be hot, huh?
Hey you. Mr. Hottie. Come on now.