I know, but I can't believe I
never even noticed this place before.
I walk by it all the time.
How could you notice it?
There's no sign outside.
Yeah, what's up with that?
You think it like blew down
in a storm or something?
No, no storm.
I think the owners did it on purpose
'cause they think it's cool.
Yeah.
They blew on their sign until it came
off 'cause they thought it was cool?
I mean, who does that?
No, no, nobody blew anything.
Hey, Dee, how did you find
out about this place?
Somebody sent me a
link to their Facebook page.
Facebook-- that's why
everybody's here.
What the hell is this?
What?
Is this water?
No, it's gin.
Aw!
Gin?! I hate gin!
Get me a beer!
Beer!
It's a gin bar.
All they have is gin.
Are you kidding?
What?
You mean to tell me there's this
many people in this joint--
all they serve is gin?
The only reason that people are
here, is because Facebook
tells them to come here.
This is the kind of shit
we need at Paddy's.
Paddy's got no Web presence.
You are absolutely right.
The whole world
is connected now.
It's all connected by Bill Gates
and that rain man, Zuckerberg.
He and his Jews have connected the
whole world, and now they're
toppling regimes.
And Egypt and Japan and the Jews
are all peaceful together...
I understand the spirit
of what you're saying.
Yeah.
Facebook is connecting
everyone these days.
Even people in the Middle East.
That's what I'm talking about.
Hell, and look people are showing
up to a bar that doesn't
even have a sign, and serves
only one old-timey disgusting
drink that nobody likes.
Goddamn I hate gin.
Dee, you bitch.
That's the thing.
This place has got a
good business model.
We have to emulate it.
That's absolutely right.
We have to get rid of all
the beer in Paddy's.
We have to blow the sign off of
the building-- you know, maybe
I'll do the blowing,
that's fine.
Charlie, Charlie, stop,
stop, stop, stop.
Do you think a human being can
blow a sign off of a building?
I didn't until Mac said it.
I never said that.
A man cannot blow a
sign off of a building.
In Charlie's defense, you could loosen
the screws, get up there and blow...
We are talking about
the Internet.
You are derailing
the conversation.
Shh!
Ugh. Ew.
What the hell was that?
Okay, don't worry
about it, okay.
Guys, we got to get on this.
He's absolutely right.
No distractions.
Paddy's needs to get connected.
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Look at the Gin Bar's
Facebook page.
They have like 50,000 friends.
Crazy.
Links to Twitter viral videos.
Their Web presence
is a amazing.
We could do a viral
video for Paddy's.
Well, we can't afford not to.
That's right.
We'll do a really cool video of
how we serve gin in spaghetti
cans or something like that.
And we take the sign down.
Frank, you're getting hung
up on the wrong things.
The old booze and the no sign
have nothing to do with it.
Yeah, what kind of a douchebag
walks into a bar just
because it doesn't have
a sign outside of it?
That's stupid, Frank.
Use your head.
But that's the most important
thing-- exclusivity.
Weird drinks, no
sign, that's cool.
Maybe so, but I like
Paddy's sign, so it stays up.
I got the sign down.
And there's no way a man could
have blown that off of our bar.
There's just no way.
You're totally wrong
about that, Mac.
Yeah.
I never once said that!
You did not?
Okay, forget it, forget it.
Charlie, we're doing a viral
video thing now, okay?
All right.
Can I stop all this
for one second?
I don't mean to derail us,
'cause this is very, very
important stuff, but, um, I'm getting
a little hung up on something.
The guy that shushed us last night--
is that bugging anybody else?
I've been thinking
about that, too.
Have you been
thinking about that?
I really have.
What are you talking about?
You were in the middle of
telling Charlie to keep quiet.
I was telling him to be quiet,
I was telling him to be quiet.
I tell everybody to be quiet.
I don't shush them
like they're animals.
I use my words.
Whatever.
I'm going to go get
the video camera.
Yeah.
Yes.
Guys, you're normally very excited
about making videos, all right?
Guys, let's just focus.
We have bigger fish to fry.
Yeah, let it go.
I can't let it go.
I can't let it go either.
I won't let it go.
I'm irritated by it.
I'm not going to let it go.
Uh, yeah, but the viral video
thing is very important.
We'll get to that.
And we'll pop a shush on the
guy and we'll be right back.
Let's... Yeah.
You can just find the
guy on Facebook.
That's where you find
people these days.
You aren't going to find
the guy on Facebook.
There's three billion
people on there.
Are you crazy?
Yeah, you don't even
know the guy's name.
We don't know his name.
Go on Facebook, magically find a guy.
Facebook.
Found him.
Really?
Yeah.
He was friends
with the Gin Bar.
Holy shit.
Yeah, that's him.
That's him.
Facebook is amazing.
Right?
We are all connected.
Okay.
Yeah, we're connected.
So let's get back to business.
Uh, viral video.
Yeah, but now that I'm seeing his face...
Mm-hmm.
I got to be honest...
It was very annoying last night that.
It pissed me off, all right?
Maybe we can just, you know, send
him a friend request and then...
Yeah, see if he responds.
And then we'll get back
to what we were doing.
Okay, yeah, distracted.
Did he respond?
Not yet.
How long does it usually take?
You know, it depends on
if he's online or not.
Refresh.
No.
What if you hit it faster?
I mean, here's the problem with,
like, Facebook and Twitter.
You know, everyone says, oh, it's
changing the world, but not
in a good way, you know.
We're not connected with
each other anymore.
Tweeting-- that's not
having a conversation.
What is that?
I know.
And then these people who do
that shit, they hear you having
a real conversation with your
real buddies, your real pals,
and they get all jealous and pissed
off and they want to shush you.
Yeah, right.
And you know what else is
bugging me about this guy?
I cannot get past the fact
that we're perfect strangers.
He doesn't know me.
I mean, for all this guy knows,
I'm a psychopath with a trunk
full of chainsaws, right?
He shushs me 'cause he doesn't like
the volume of my conversation?
Next thing he knows he's chopped to
bits in a basement somewhere, you know?
Was that worth it?
No.
And I could be a man with a
fist full of hammers... Right.
...and a trunk full of
duct tape and zip ties.
You know, this guy
doesn't know me.
Is he crazy?
It's very upsetting to me that
he didn't consider any of that.
Yeah, well, this is not a
considerate man, Charlie.
This is a rude man, and they are
very seldom the same people.
Yeah.
Uh, sir?
Yeah?
Can we get you for a second?
We've got a...
What can I get for you guys?
Well, we're looking for a man.
Yeah, this guy was
a real douchebag.
He was in here the other night.
Yeah, douche-y looking.
Kind of douche-y.
Yeah, I wish I had a picture
of the guy, but we don't.
Oh, he's a shusher.
Oh, yes, right.
This is a douchebag who goes around
shushing people that he doesn't even know.
Yeah, people who could
have chainsaws.
Or hammers.
I mean, is any of this
ringing a bell to you?
No. Sorry.
But I don't really see
what the big deal is.
The big deal.
You don't see what
the big deal is?
The big deal, sir, is that a grown
man shushed me and my friend here.
We demand satisfaction
from this person, okay?
We got to find this guy because
we've got some important shit
that we're trying to do on
the Internet, or whatever.
We have much bigger
things going on.
The sign is down, okay?
The sign is down.
He took our sign down.
It's never been down, you
see what I'm saying?
No.
I'm getting frustrated.
I'm also very frustrated.
Look, how would you
like to be shushed?
Don't think I'd care.
Shh!
How'd that feel?
I mean, I was finished speaking.
Well, shh to you!
Again, I was done, so...
You're speaking too fast.
Stop speaking in such
short sentences.
Then we can shush you in the
middle and you'll know how it feels.
Okay, do you guys want
a drink, or what?
Yeah.
Yeah, we want drinks.
Absolutely.
Okay, two house specials?
Shh!
Specials, yeah.
Yeah, two house specials.
Got interrupted.
How'd that feel?
On your away.
I think you got him
with that one, though.
I don't exactly
feel good about it.
No.
But he had to know how it feels.
Yeah, but you nailed him.
Thanks, man.
Hey, you know, I think I know how we
can get a picture of this shusher guy.
What you thinking?
Refresh.
Goddamn it.
Why won't this guy
be our friend?
It's like an online shush.
You know, I... Okay, Paddy's Pub
has over 30 friends at this point.
Why will this guy not
accept our friend request.
He's too good for us?
Don't complain, just
hit refresh again.
You son of a bitch!
I got the video camera.
All right, Mac, say,
"I got infected."
What?
Say it.
I got infected.
Get that away from me.
Deandra, okay, now here we go.
Say, "I got the bug."
No, I'm busy, Frank.
Say, "bug."
Bug!
What are you doing?
I'm shooting the virus thing.
What virus thing?
The virus thing that you guys
said we were going to infect all
our friends with on
Facebook or whatever.
Oh! We got him!
We got him?
We got you, Dylan Toback!
You giant douche!
Are you guys gonna help me
do the virus thing, or what?
We're busy right now, Frank.
Yeah, we're doing the
shushing thing first, Frank.
But you said the virus video
was the most important thing!
No, no! No!
We said the viral video is very
important, and it is very
important-- but we're
on to this now.
You know, we'll do it later.
Why don't you get it started and then
we'll come and fix what you did, okay?
All right, but hurry up.
Oh, check out these updates:
"I am a man-whore.
I hate women.
I am a liar."
He admits that he is a liar.
Son of a bitch!
Uh, looks like he is shopping for a
silk sash at Tootie's, on South Street.
A silk sash at Tootie's?
What an asshole.
Hm.
Okay... Daddy got a new plan.
Mm-hmm.
Daddy got a new plan.
Let's head down to Tootie's and we'll
fire a shush right in his face.
We'll shush him real quick.
But we won't tell Dennis and
Charlie, 'cause they mocked us.
Eventually, we'll tell
them, though, right?
Well, we won't tell them right
now, but we'll come back
and we'll jam it in their faces.
Freeze!
Yeah, once we shush him.
Okay, let's go.
Okay. All right.
Great idea. Great idea!
I want to make sure you got
the nose right, though.
That's the most important part to me,
because it was an annoying nose.
It was an... It was a nose that
you wanted to smack, yeah.
And then, give him, like, almond eyes if you...
You've already said that.
And don't compliment the man.
It's not a compliment from me, 'cause
I don't like people with almond eyes.
I find it creepy.
All right, well, can we just
take a look at the drawing?
Because we kinda need
to get out of here.
You've done an excellent job.
Really good! Wow!
And what is your technique, sir,
because I want to learn that.
That is... You know, the only thing
that would help this, is if you had
him do this gesture...
Oh, my God.
- When the man assaulted us...
- Mr.
Reynolds, Mr.
Kelly, I'm Detective Larson.
I'm gonna need to clear something
up on your report here.
It doesn't... Yeah, we're good.
We're good, actually, 'cause we got...
It says here this was filed
as an assault, but the only
thing that you're claiming was
that this man shushed you?
Yeah.
But it was an assault.
Shushing somebody
is not an assault.
There was more to it than...
He-- yeah-- it wasn't just shushing, though...
Yeah... And the reason it was an
assault was because he was
shushing our cries for help.
Right. This guy was raping us...
Well... wha...?
He was raping you.
Yeah, well, yeah... Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
The both of you?
No. You can't rape two guys.
No... no, no, no.
I wouldn't even necessarily classify it...
You know what happened was
that he only raped
my friend here.
I actually shook
him off in time.
The guy never quite made it inside
of me but, my friend here, yeah...
So he was only raping you?
Yep.
Yeah... yeah.
He, like, really, kinda made soup
of your insides... No... n no, no.
He barely, he barely made it in
there, so, trust me, I'm fine.
Yeah, but he bit his dick.
Not-- what?!
No, he did... He, he...
the reason we were going to file as a rape was
because he did make it inside
me, but, like, just barely.
And the guy was
super-small, so I'm fine.
And then I did get away.
Well, don't-don't-don't
write any of this down.
Look, can we just
drop the case?
Yeah!
Right?
We don't need to... We just need the drawing...
I don't even think about
that, because if we have the
drawing, we can find the guy.
We can dole out the justice,
and I'll mend this guy's...
And then this never needs to
go in any files anywhere.
If you and Mr. Reynolds are
filing a false police report,
there's no way in hell you're getting
out of here with that drawing.
All right, Charlie.
I got another plan.
How's that?
That's perfect.
That looks exactly like him!
Yeah, I mean, he wasn't in a dune buggy
and he didn't have... No, he was not.
...a propeller on his head, like that, but...
I like the shushing, though.
You nailed the shushing!
Tootie's... Tootie's...
This is it.
Ew!
Is that him?
That's him.
That is him.
Let's do this.
Hey, Dylan Toback.
Oh! Hey.
Sorry about that, ma'am.
Hi, ma'am.
Uh, we thought you were
this guy, Dylan Toback.
He shushed us and...
And we were gonna shush him back, yeah.
Yeah.
We didn't think you were a man, per se...
I did.
Okay, I did, too.
I did because of your hair.
Here's why: it's the hair and it's
the cardigan, and it's the build...
It's the way you stand,
and the broad shoulders.
But that's okay.
That's okay.
There's nothing you
can do about that.
Have a nice day.
I'm still confused.
I'm very confused.
It's sort of a
transgender situation.
Are you guys
looking for Dylan Toback?
Yeah. Do you know him?
He posted on Facebook
that he was here.
Well, can you guys
keep a secret?
No!
Yes. Yes.
Yes, I can... yes, yes.
Yes, yes.
That wasn't him, it was me.
I started a Facebook
page to get back at him.
I'm his ex-girlfriend
and he was the worst.
He was always, like,
"Sally, send me money."
"Sally, mail me hair."
Mail him hair?
Weird, right?
Yeah, and then he posted a bunch
of naked pics of me online,
and that was the last straw.
Oh, my God!
That's disgusting!
Naked pics online?
Where? Where did he post those?
I don't know.
One of those disgusting
ex-girlfriend porno sites.
Aw, those disgusting
ex-girlfriend porno sites!
I mean, there's so
many of them, though!
Which one?
Which one did he post it on?
Do you know where
we can find him?
Oh, I can give you his address.
I don't give a shit.
Really?
Great! Great!
Also, put down one of the sites that was...
Listen, do you want to come
with us, and maybe
get some payback?
- That's... well...
- Here's the thing: he's never actually met me.
Well, the pics I sent were a
little more flattering than I
actually am, and so we just sort
of had this online relationship.
Mm! Mm-hmm.
But the hair I mailed was mine.
That was real.
Okay, you know what?
This chick is
douchier than Dylan.
Let's get outta here!
Yeah.
No, I'm not even gonna look
for those nude photos.
I might.
I might, though.
Come on, man-- this
guy's been in here.
He's got the annoying nose that you
wanted to smack... Evil almond eyes.
I'm sorry, guys, I've never seen a
cartoon character in here shushing
people before.
Well, he wasn't in a dune buggy, he was...
Look, use your imagination.
Yeah, he's not a cartoon
character, okay?
Would you just take
this seriously?
I don't see how I could
take this seriously.
He's not helping.
No.
He's not going to
be a help to us.
You're just going to be difficult,
so just go get us more gin drinks.
That's all you're good for.
More of the gin.
God. All right...
Here's what I'm gonna do, Charlie.
I'm going to write "Rude man who
shushes, please call" at tat
top, and then, at the bottom,
I'll put my phone number.
Right.
Right? And then we'll make a
shitload of copies, we'll put
them up all over town, and it'll
act like a wanted poster.
Okay, wait, so you want
the rude man to call you?
No, I want people to call
me about the rude man.
But, if the rude man calls
me that works, too.
That works, too!
All right.
That's gonna work.
Now, hold on a second-- you're
cool just putting your
personal information out there?
Yeah! I'm absolutely cool with that, man,
because I'm saying "connect with me."
Right.
See, that's what we're talking about--
people just don't connect these days.
I'm saying call me, let's
have a phone conversation.
Yeah, don't tweet.
Don't just tweet me, don't shush
me-- you know, let's connect.
Let's have a
connection, you know?
Don't be rude!
Let's talk about rude people.
Let's talk about people who
do rude things, you know?
Mm-hmm.
I guarantee you, people
will respect this.
Okay, one little
roadblock, no big deal.
But let's shush this guy and
get out of here, because it's
starting to get complicated.
Yeah. And what was
happening back there?
Sending nude pictures
of yourself?
That's just stupid,
and that's desperate.
Yeah, and hair?!
I mean, sending hair--
that's just demented.
Well, the hair I don't
really have a problem with.
What are you talking about?
What is the point of that?
You send your hair to a guy
and, you know, you just give
that guy a sense of you and your smells...
and... you know... Oh! Oh!
Goddamn it!
We're looking for Dylan Toback.
Is he around?
Oh, Lord...
I knew this day would come.
Um... come in.
Okay, but listen, we don't
have a lot of time, okay?
Um, a few months ago, my
daughter Jamela bought me this
brand-new computer, and she put it right here...
Speed up, speed up, speed up!
Okay, so, ever since Jerry
got put on life support--
Whoa! Slow down, slow
down, slow down!
Ew! I didn't see him there.
I've had nothing but
time on my hands.
And I've been so
lonely, you know?
Okay, well, does any of this have
anything to do with Dylan Toback?
Oh, why is she doing that?
Um... I am Dylan Toback.
No, no, no... Mm-mm, mm-mm, mm-mm...
Don't say that!
We don't have time
for that, okay?
Is anybody online the person
who they say that they are?
Okay, do you know how to
find the real Dylan Toback?
Well, what I'm saying
is he doesn't exist.
I made up the name Dylan Toback.
I've made up dozens of names.
I'm really good at it.
My real name is Catfish!
What the hell is happening here?
Here's what I gather.
I think she went on the Gin Bar's
Web site, found a picture
of that guy and then made up a whole
name and personality for him.
So we don't know the guy's name.
No.
We don't even know
if he's on Facebook.
Nope.
How the hell are
we gonna find him?
I don't know.
Well, how did you find me?
Was it that Sally?
Because that bitch been
getting on my nerves.
So you know Sally?
Oh, uh, Dylan knows Sally.
No, he doesn't, 'cause Dylan
isn't real, and you know what?
Sally isn't Sally anymore;
Sally is now Dylan.
And what about the nude photos? I mean...
This is not about the nude
photos, Mac... Shh! Shh!
Don't you shush me!
Don't you shush us, goddamn it.
Don't disturb Jerry.
Disturb Jerry? I'm disturbed.
He should be disturbed.
This whole thing is disturbing,
and if you shush me
one more time I will put you in the ground.
Do you hear me?
Okay you know what? Dee, Dee!
We're losing focus, all right?
Let's just get back to the bar,
we'll find the nude photos...
Oh, yeah, yeah, let's-let's focus on the...
Well, hold on.
Don't you want your hair back?
- Is that your hair, Dee?
- Oh, come on.
You're Carl Lundegard?
Yeah.
I mean, what is the problem?
Are we not putting these
in the right part of town?
We put them in every part of town...
Oh, oh, here we go, here we go.
Okay, come on.
Hello?
Saw that guy you
were looking for.
You did?
Yeah.
Oh, that's great, okay, can you
tell us where exactly the... Shh!
Uh, no, oh, you do not! Oh!
You... ugh! He shushed me.
Another one?
Yes, another shusher
shushing me on the phone.
All right, maybe the poster is
the problem because it says
"Rude man who shushes
please call..."
Right.
So rude men are calling
just to shush you.
This is prank calls.
Am I gonna have to change my phone number?
I mean, that's...
Yes, because you never want to
put your personal information
out there in the world.
It's like... People abuse it.
Yo! Did you find the guy?
No. He's unfindable.
We just hit a bunch of dead ends, right?
The guy is a ghost, I'm telling you.
I know! We tried to track him down on
Facebook, but it got very strange.
Like, it was just a bunch of girls
pretending to be boys, and
Dee banged a o fat old black
la, and then sent her hair.
Okay, that's not... Hey!
I did the video, and I sent it to all of Paddy's
Facebook friends.
You did?
Yeah.
Frank to the rescue.
Oh, ho! Frank saves the day.
All right.
Good work, Frank.
Nice.
Check out what you got here.
Welcome to Paddy's Pub...
the oldest pub in America.
Well, that's not true.
Right.
No, I lied.
Everybody lies on the Internet.
He's right. Everybody out there is lying
to get what they want; why can't we?
Totally.
We have a variety of old liquors
served in strange containers.
We are packed with
celebrities-- the fun ones.
We also have cockfights
and strippers.
And guess what?
We don't have a sign, so
good luck finding the place.
But if you do, you'll be lucky.
'Cause we also got donkey
shows, Motley Crue and cake.
Awesome, awesome.
Okay, okay. Frank!
That's awesome.
That is awesome.
I got to hand it to you, I
think I would go to this bar.
I would definitely
go to that bar.
This is the best
part, coming up.
So, spread the word to all of
your friends: At Paddy's Pub,
- you're guaranteed to catch a...
- Virus!
Just ask this guy.
I got infected.
Get it away from me.
Or her.
No, I'm busy.
She looks like she caught the...
Bug!
So spread this video to all of your
friends, because it's a computer virus.
Virus!
Take it from me.
I am a doctor... Dr. Toboggan.
Mantis Toboggan.
What?
You sent that to all of
our Facebook friends?
Yeah.
They're gonna think they have
a computer virus, Frank.
Wait, you're the ones who said
we needed the virus video.
I said a "viral video,"
Frank. Goddamn it. Goddamn it!
Oh, my God, we never should've
left him in charge.
See, the problem is we
got focused on the guy.
We didn't help him with his...
This whole thing is a total mess.
I mean, absolutely nothing
good has come of today.
- No, we wasted all of our...
- Excuse me.
This is a bar, right?
We noticed you guys didn't
have a sign out front.
Thought that was pretty cool.
You guys open?
Yes, we are.
Charlie, lock the door.
Come on in.  Oh...
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com