ALL: Reunion! Reunion!
Reunion! Reunion! Reunion!
Reunion! Reunion!
CHARLIE: Go! Chug, chug, chug!
(guys cheer)
MAC: Whoo!
SWEET DEE: Yes!
Fight song! Go!
Fight song!
ALL: ♪ "Let's go to the downtown..."
♪ Is our motto show DENNIS:
♪ Let's go, St. Joe's ♪
♪ Go, St. Joe's! ♪
Screw it.
That's a stupid song.
Oh, man, this reunion is
going to be awesome, dude.
I am going to fire into that
school, and it is gonna
propel me back into the mid-'90s when
Dennis Reynolds was a golden god.
Yeah. Oh, I'm so excited to show
these douche bags my new back.
No brace, fools! Baby got back!
♪ Oh-oh, baby got back. ♪
Dee, what are you doing?
Baby, got back.
You know that one.
Sir Mix-a-Lot.
♪ Baby got... ♪
Sir Mix-a-Lot was not talking
about women whose backs have
recovered from horrific
spinal disorder.
He was talking about gorgeous black women
and their big beautiful black butts.
FRANK: Black butts are good.
Whatever.
They're good, right?
Guess what. Baby got back, and
I can't wait to shove it
into these fools' faces,
so let's get going.
Whatever. I don't give a shit.
Let's just do what we always did
before every school-sponsored
event and let's...smash 'em up?
Let's smash 'em up!
Oh... Smash 'em up!
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Hey, right?
I got these.
What, what are you
doing there, Charlie?
Huh? Oh, I'm packing a couple
extra pair of underwear in case
I get an atomic wedgie.
It's not gonna happen, dude.
We're adults now.
I'm not taking any
risks here, all right?
And if it does happen, I'm gonna
get high, I'm gonna go to the
bathroom, I'm gonna huff stuff.
No, Charlie, you don't have to
do things like that anymore.
You don't need to huff shit or eat weird
things to get people to like you.
Nah, I think he does.
You guys were pretty much
nothing in high school.
If he wasn't the class clown and
you didn't sell drugs, you'd
definitely be nothing; nobodies.
Well, if shit happens, I'm
going directly to Plan B.
We're not gonna have
to do Plan B, okay?
You know, I'm gonna come right
out and say that I'm not
doing Plan B regardless of
what happens with you guys.
I'm only here for Plan B.
Oh, shit.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Faculty or alumni?
Neither one.
Well, you can't go in.
No, but we're friends.
We're buddies.
We hang out together.
We do everything together.
I don't care.
Okay, look, I'm gonna go inside
because, Frank, I can't
have you ruining this for me.
But what am I gonna do?
I don't know!
Hang out in the parking lot and
drink beer till we're done.
We smashed all the beers.
Oh, no, actually, I have a few more.
You guys want one?
You can't bring those inside.
Well, then guess what.
All right.
Smash 'em up!
(all laugh)
All right, turkey.
See ya, Frank.
See ya, jerk jerky.
Oh, yeah, baby, this is great.
This brings me back.
I'm anxious, I'm excited, I
can't wait to see the waitress.
Charlie, give it a rest.
I know, but we've been clicking lately.
This is gonna be a good night for us.
Like, remember how she was
the coolest girl in school?
What are you talking about?
No.
Well, she was definitely the
prettiest girl in school.
She was not. She was not, no.
Maybe the most forgettable
girl in school.
Yeah, which, by the way, is the worst
thing you could be in high school.
Totally insignificant.
Either way, good feelings
are gonna get sparked up.
I'm gonna see her, she's gonna see me.
You guys, you guys, you guys.
What?
Brad Fisher. Brad Fisher.
He is not gonna be happy to see
me after that present I gave him.
Uh, what present?
Oh, the box of hornets.
Ooh, that acne really
came back, didn't it?
Yeah, it sure did.
The guy looks like shit.
Mm-hmm.
All right, I tell you what.
Why don't you guys sneak past him, and
Mac and I will pick up the name tags.
Really?
How does that sound?
Yeah.
Okay.
We'll meet you inside.
All right, go, go, go.
All right, come on.
Hey, hey, hey, it's
Brad Fisher, all right!
How you doing, buddy?
BRAD: Not great.
Oh, yeah, well, the acne definitely
came back in full force.
Yeah.
That's a shame, but I have products
that will clear that acne up, man.
It's not acne, actually.
No, no, it's hornet scars.
Ooh! Ouch. Yikes.
I don't think I have any products that'll,
that'll take care of hornet scars.
That's more of a...
Plastic surgery situation.
Yeah, plastic surgery
would do it, though.
Yeah.
But lasers... Lasers would do it.
They'd blast those monsters...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You guys seen Charlie around?
Charlie Kelly?
Yeah.
No.
No, we don't, we don't
associate with him anymore.
All right, I'm gonna take off.
Okay.
Messy.
Ooh-hoo-hoo.
Let's stay out of that.
Yeah, let's stay out of that.
Let's just grab our name tags, huh?
I don't see 'em over here.
Oh, here we go.
Okay, we got Charlie, we got
Dee, I got myself right there.
Yeah.
And, uh, I'm not seeing yours.
Yeah, I grabbed mine already.
It's in my pocket.
Oh, did you grab it?
Yeah.
Oh, okay, well, pop it on.
Uh, I'm probably not gonna wear mine.
I mean, who wears a name tag, right?
That's not cool.
I'm gonna wear mine.
I'm seeing everybody else wearing their
name tags, so just pop that on, buddy.
Nobody calls me this anymore.
And I feel like it's
gonna confuse people.
It's not, because everybody
called you that in high school,
so pop it on because it's
definitely a rule and they're
not gonna let you inside without it.
It's been so long.
It's probably not even
my name legally anymore.
You're gonna have to pop it on.
(sighs) Okay.
(heart pounding)
Good. Well, okay, Ronald McDonald.
Don't call me that.
Well, it's your name.
So, Ronald, I'm gonna take a
little lap around, get people
abuzz about my presence at the reunion.
And I'll meet up with
you guys later, okay?
(chuckles)
No one, no one calls me... ♪
♪
Is he looking?
Who? That guy?
Yes, is he looking at my back rig now?
Do you see the waitress anywhere?
Come on. Shut up.
He's not looking at your back, Dee.
Are you sure?
Why are you so obsessed with this guy?
It's Adriano Calvaniste, Charlie.
It's the guy who coined the
name "Aluminum monster."
Really? That's him?!
Yes.
That's cool.
I want to meet him.
You have met him, Charlie.
He called you Dirtgrub and
he made you eat spiders.
Oh, that guy!
Yeah.
Oh, he was, like, so cool.
He was, like, way above me.
Yeah, him and his cronies
all thought that they were
way above you and everybody else,
but I've got a plan to get revenge.
I'm gonna sew myself
into their inner circle.
Cool. How you gonna do that?
Well, I'm gonna lure 'em in
with my good looks, and then
as far as I remember, all you
really got to do to get in with
that crowd is be really
cruel to people.
Right.
So I'm gonna gain their trust and when
the moment's right, I'm gonna strike.
Oh, cool, all right.
I'm doing it for us, Charlie.
Oh, okay. Thanks. Yeah.
Mm-hmm. Is it, is it him?
He's coming over.
All right, do you see a spider I can eat?
I can eat a spider.
No, stop. Charlie, keep your
mouth shut, keep your...
ADRIANO: Hey, um, excuse me, but
aren't you the aluminum monster?
Yes. I mean, no.
People don't call me
that anymore, but yeah.
Nor should they.
I mean, wow, you've, uh,
you've really transformed.
You look great.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
Thanks.
Hey, Dirtgrub.
How are you?
That's so cool.
You're so cool, Adriano.
Yeah.
Hey, um, why don't you smell this?
Well, it's probably poisonous, right?
Probably, but, you
know, smell it anyway.
Should-should I smell it?
Smell it.
Come on.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, Charlie!
What are you doing, dude?
Oh, he wanted me to smell a pen,
and I was going to smell
the pen, because it's Adriano...
You don't have to do that anymore.
Hey, Ronald McDonald, right?
No, no.
For your information,
nobody calls me that.
Right, right.
What did we call you?
Ronnie the Rat.
Ronnie the Rat, yeah, I
remember, yeah, yeah.
Why did we call him that anyway?
'Cause he was a nark and a
tattletale, and he became the
main drug dealer when he told
on the other main drug dealer.
Right, yeah, yeah, I remember.
Well, looks like the rat got a
little too much cheese, huh?
Fat.
That's not funny.
I put on mass.
We eat a lot of cheese.
To put on mass.
Didn't you also give
everybody ringworm?
No, no.
That was a rumor.
I only gave ringworm to Charlie.
I got it from my dog Poppins,
and then Charlie and I were
wrestling every day because
we were trying out for the
wrestling team, and then, you know, we
just sort of passed it back and forth.
We passed it back and forth...
Although then we did try out
for the wrestling team, and then
I do think a couple of the guys
got it on the team, so yeah,
you're right, you're right.
Wow, yeah, yeah, no, that is really gross.
I mean, that is...
Yeah, that's about as low as it gets.
They probably still have it,
'cause they're so gay together.
Totally.
Hey, Dee, why don't you come back to
our table-- you know, have a drink?
Oh, yeah, okay.
Yeah?
That sounds cool.
See you later, Dirtgrub
and Ronnie the Rat.
Hope you suck each other's rotten
peckers until you get mouth cancer.
Mouth cancer.
Can I come to the table?
No!
For some reason, homophobia, it's
just, it's awesome to these
guys. I'm sewing myself in.
I'm doing this for us, okay?
What the hell is she talking about?
She's going to strike
when the moment's right.
She's doing it for us, dude.
Really?
Yeah.
Did you thank her?
Of course I thanked her, absolutely.
Oh, what's up, boys?
Hey.
All right, I got your name tags.
Oh.
Hey, did you get on Mac about his?
Yeah, he's got... It's not that...
It's not funny.
That's so funny.
Adriano came over,
blasted him about it.
Oh he did?
Oh, good, oh good.
So Adriano's probably going
to tell everybody about it.
That's going to get
around the whole reunion.
It'll get going round
and round and round.
Probably not.
Probably getting old already.
So listen, guys, this is where
we part ways, all right?
So do do not talk to me for the
rest of the night, and know that
I won't be talking to you,
because you lower my stock.
You guys get it.
I'm going to go post up one of
these tables around here, let my
loyal subjects come and kiss my ring.
Listen, don't laugh when
people make fun of me.
Yo, Stash.
Stash.
What's up, brother?
Dennis.
Sit down, man.
Let's catch up a little bit.
Okay, all right, I'll
catch you later, man.
Hey, if you see any of the old crew,
let them know I'm posted up over here.
I don't think they know I'm-- I'm here.
Dennis.
What are you...?
I snuck right by that security prick.
Look, I got myself a name tag.
I'm Nicki Potnick.
Remember the time he crashed
my car into the tree?
He went crazy and the tire went down...
We had such a good time.
Okay, Frank, first off, Nicki
Potnick is a girl, okay?
And secondly, she's not 65 years old.
I don't want to talk to you.
I don't want to be around you.
Go find Mac and Charlie.
Go, go, go.
Why-- why are you sitting
at a table with no people?
I thought you were cool.
I am cool.
I'm the coolest kid here.
I'm just, you know, posting up,
and they're going to come to me.
I don't know what's going on.
MAUREEN: Hello, Dennis.
Whoa.
Oh, goddamn.
You're late on your alimony.
Can we not talk about
alimony payments right now?
We're at our reunion.
Didn't think you'd run
into your ex-wife, huh?
No, I didn't think about it, Maureen,
because I don't think about you.
Really?
No.
What do you think about this?
Oh, it wafted over here.
The dead tooth-- it spurted
in my nose, it stinks.
What is that supposed to be?
That's where your monthly
payments are going.
That's a diamond tooth, Dennis.
A dead tooth, Maureen.
With a diamond in it.
Put a diamond on anything
that's dead, and it's still
dead, Maureen. It's rotting.
Get it out of your face.
Look, I don't want to talk
about these things, all right?
I don't want to talk to old men
who are pretending to be women,
and-and ex-wives, all right?
I can't be seen like this.
Hello, bitches.
Oh, for...!
That's right, I'm off the wagon.
Yeah.
You know what, Dennis?
I went to go find my name tag--
they didn't have one for me.
Oh, really?
All right, see you later.
Yeah, I went to go find my name
tag-- they didn't even have one.
It's like-- it's like
what, I never existed?
I mean, who cares though, right?
'Cause it's high school.
Who cares?
(laughing)
Me, too.
Here we go, grab it.
Oh, yes!
Shots for everybody. Shots for the cool...
Oh, Rickety Cricket, everybody.
Look at this.
Rickety, rickety, rickety.
(blubbering)
(all laughing)
Rickety Cricket!
Cricks, how are you?
All cleaned up huh,
except for that tooth.
Well, actually it's Father Mara again.
Is it?
I cleaned up, yes, and I was
welcomed back into the cloth.
God had a plan for me.
Took me into a deep valley, but
now I'm soaring on eagle's
wings, so praise Him.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
All that, street rat.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I tell you what, Crick,
should I put my balls on your
chin now or later, huh?
Huh, huh?
Down the hatch, everybody.
Down the hatch, everybody...
but you, Father.
All right, well, nonetheless, I
say to you peace, peace be to
you, Deandra, okay?
That's weird.
And peace be to you, my lady.
And to you, my son, peace be to you.
To you.
Hey, hey, everybody, remember me?
Probably not.
Sat behind you in Spanish, remember?
Sat... sat right next
to you in Algebra one.
Who the hell is that?
Oh, I don't know.
I've never seen her before in my life.
Dee. Dee, you know me, Dee.
I know Dee.
Me and Dee, we go way back.
Bad choice on the dress,
know what I mean?
I know you, bitch.
Oh, hey.
More shots, more shots, more shots,
more shots, more shots, more shots.
I'm the queen of the night.
I'm the queen of the night,
right, cool table?
♪ ♪
Wow, I just shook your dead tooth wife.
I mean, I had to wash
my hands and face.
I am trying to shake you, Frank.
It just smells so bad.
Please go away from me.
Please get away.
Yo, Dennis.
Oh, shit.
It's Tim Murphy. Son of a bitch.
Who's Tim Murphy?
Tim Murphy is the asshole
that slept with my prom date.
Dennis Reynolds, what's up, man?
Oh, hey, Tim.
This is my wife Christie.
Dennis and I used to be
really good friends.
Oh, hi. Nice to meet you.
Nicki Potnick.
Shut up.
Oh, hey, honey?
Yeah?
Let's go dance.
Why don't you go ahead.
I'm going to hang for a bit.
Oh, okay.
Nice to meet you both.
Oh. Va-va-voom.
Anyhow, I saw you
standing over here alone.
I wanted to invite you
over to our table.
Oh, I won't be going
anywhere with you, Tim.
Okay, why?
Don't you play coy with
me, you little bitch.
I'm going to stay right here, and I'm
going to wait for my minions to swarm me.
And swarm they will, Tim.
Alone you'll be.
Ha.
Such sad little games we play.
Right, Tim?
Right.
Same old Dennis Reynolds.
You look good, Nicki.
Thank you, Tim!
Mm.
Thank you.
Seems like a nice guy.
He's not. Go!
Go away from me!
We just got to get our mojo back.
Yeah.
Get some drinks in us, and...
Confidence, yeah.
Six beers, for the two of us, please.
Drink tickets for the
two of us, please.
Oh, all right.
Here.
Dude, this is only four.
That's all they gave us, bozo.
Well, that's only two per person, bozo.
Well, how am I supposed to get drunk
off of only four beers? I, I...
Is there any way you can work something out?
Or... Two tickets per person, guy.
I didn't ask you, pretty boy.
It's a conversation between
me and the longhair.
Okay.
None for him, or the fat bitch.
(laughing)
You making this about weight?
He's gained a lot of weight.
I'm not going to take some
shit from some bartender.
You're a bartender.
He doesn't know that!
Hey, did you guys see
Ronald McDonald's his name?
(laughing)
Hey!
Eight beers, my friends.
What's up, buddy?
How are you? Boom!
Hey, buddy.
Whoa.
I thought it was only two per person!
The, uh, computer lab printed
out like a hundred of them.
Way more than I need.
That's awesome.
Can we get a few of them?
No. No way.
I, I'm sorry I brought it up, man.
Yeah.
Hey, Adriano, can I get
some more of those tickets?
Yeah, you bet. Here.
Help yourself.
Awesome.
Son of a bitch!
He just gave them to that guy.
Well, that guy's cool, so...
Okay, I got an idea, man.
I got a, I got an
excellent plan, Charlie.
We're going to get everything we
need, we're going to get our
confidence back, and we're going
to fire back into this room.
You ready?
Okay, good.
Here we go.
I want those guys to like us.
Follow my lead.
Okay.
Adriano made fake tickets.
Those tickets are fake!
Don't rat on him!
But he made fake ones, and he
gets to drink and we don't.
That's not fair!
Bro, I'm sorry.
If those are fake, you can't
get any of these beers.
Come on.
(Mac laughs)
You got in trouble.
You got in trouble!
Wow. Ronnie the Rat strikes again, huh?
Thanks a lot, douchebag.
You're the worst, Dirtgrub.
Yeah.
I didn't have anything to do...
Don't sell me out.
See what you did, man?
We're supposed to be on
the same team, Charlie.
Aw... see, high school sucks!
You know what?
I'm going to go to the bathroom,
I'm going to find stuff to huff,
I'm going to get high.
If I'm the Dirtgrub, I'm going
to be the Dirtgrub.
(Mac sighs in exasperation)
We're going to go into Plan B.
Because I brought Dee's old back
brace, and I got it in the car.
So, we can implement... Not now, Frank!
A little rehearsal or something.
No, Charlie, dude, you
don't have to do this.
We can find another way.
Yes, I do!
I'm just the Dirtgrub, okay?
Everyone wants the Dirtgrub,
I'll give 'em the Dirtgrub.
I'll get high, I'll get sad.
People can laugh at me.
I hate high school, man.
Charlie, Charlie, don't put the
bleach and the ammonia together!
It's going to knock
the shit out of you.
Don't tell me how to
mix my own inhalants!
I know how to do inhalants.
Charlie, it's going to
knock you unconscious.
Okay, I know how to do
my own inhalants, okay?
I don't need that from... God.
Whoops-a-daisy.
That's it.
All right.
Well, let's just wait till he wakes
up, and then we'll... Oh, wow.
What do we got here?
Ronnie the Rat and, uh...
Hey, look, everyone, Nicki
Potnick made it to the reunion.
(laughing)
Hello.
Looks like you had a rough
couple of years, there, Nicki.
Uh, yeah. I'm a guy now.
Mm. Right. Yeah.
What are you guys doing, perving
out on Dirtgrub over there?
Yeah, probably.
That's what these gay guys do, they just...
knock each other
out with poppers, and then find
some kinda rabies-infested
rodent to tickle each
other's taints with.
(laughing)
No. No, that's not what
we're doing, all right?
We are grown adults.
We are respected businessmen now.
You did kind of rat me out there, Ronnie, so...
Yeah, so, I guess it's time
to pay the piper, Rat.
And, uh... old man I don't know.
Whoa! No, no!
What the hell are...?!
(yelling)
Ah!
Ow!
I've been waiting a long time for this.
You know me!
Oh, God!
I'm a grown, goddamn man!
(yelling)
♪ ♪
You should stay away from those people.
I mean, they-they will ruin your
life like they tried to ruin mine.
Oh!
You guys just missed something
so awesome that we did.
Heed my warning.
Hey, how you guys doing?
Yeah. I'm here.
Can you believe I came to this thing?
Yeah, I was posted up over there, I
guess you guys probably didn't see me.
No, we saw you.
Oh, did you?
Oh, okay, well...
no reason to be intimidated.
You know?
I'm a human being, after all.
You know, just a... just a man.
Actually, we're good.
Uh, no, Tim. We're not good.
And you're definitely not good,
because you haven't had the
chance to hang out with me yet.
Um... my wallet's missing.
Oh my God, my necklace is missing.
Come on!
My gold chain's gone.
Have you seen my necklace?
Oh, my.
And with all the security.
The fact you even need it...
Wait a second, Mara.
What is that around your neck?
Hmm?
Oh, that's, uh... probably just a ar that...
What the hell?
Ah.
(people exclaiming)
Ah!
I've sinned!
My God, you are covered in ringworm.
It's her fault.
She told me she loved me.
We were supposed to
be together forever.
Calm down, Cricks.
What's he talking about?
Dee, were you two together?
No! Me, with him?
I... what are you, crazy? No!
Yeah, I told him I loved him once,
but that was like four years ago.
You two probably have
ringworm together, don't you?
No!
No, of course I don't have ringworm!
No no no, stay away from me!
To think I was going to let you jack me off...
Wait wait... you were?
Unbelievable.
Get this asshole out of here.
Come on.
No, no!
Come on, move, come on.
Hey, you know I don't
have ringworm, right?
You guys.
No, we don't have ringworm.
I don't have ringworm.
No, no, we're cool!
Yeah, we're like the... Oh, really?
Oh, son of a bitch.
(sighs)
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com