You were disrespectful to me.
That's the past.
God, get a life.
This is my life, bitch.
You bitch!
Aw, you slut.
Ah, hold still,
Charlie-- you're flickering.
Sorry, it's... I'm trying to
get you good images, but I keep getting
shocked a little bit.
Well, don't let
that affect your work.
No, I'm really trying not to.
It's just that, you know, I have to run
the wires from the other building...
Building and, you know, there's
asbestos in the ducts, which...
Good for breathing, so I'm tired.
Why are you watching this crap?
Come on, turn the TV off.
Let's go out, let's do
something-- I'm bored.
Hey, let's go dancing, huh?
I want to do something.
Dancing?
We're watching Real Housewives.
You know, there's nothing
real about this shit, Frank.
You know that, come on.
Real women don't even look like that.
Hey, guys.
That is what real women look like.
Dee, are you sick?
No, I feel great.
Oh, I haven't had a chance
to shower for a few days.
I've been gaming like a loon.
You've been what?
Gaming-- I've been playing
this online video game.
It is awesome.
Charlie, speaking of which, you
want to come play my avatar for
a little bit while I run some errands?
I don't want my crops to die.
Nah, I'm kind of busy working
for the guys at the ele...
Shit!
Yes, he's working for us.
He will do nothing of the sort.
We're going dancing. Come on!
What if I give you three bucks?
Hey, you're our employee.
You do what we say.
I pay your rent.
Do not drop those wires!
Hey, Charlie, to live is to dance.
Let's go.
Charlie, what if I gave you five bucks?
You owe me five bucks!
Ah, shit! Screw it!
Son of a bitch! Shit!
All right, I'll tell you what.
I'm gonna go with Dee, okay?
But I'm getting sick of
this shit, I really am.
You treat me like a dumb-dumb
and a grunt, and I have
potential, you know?
I can go places, I can do things.
Who knows?
I might even rule the world one day.
Rule the world, huh?
Yeah, if that happens, I'll blow myself.
Sync & corrections by
Okay, so it's called
TechPocalypse, right?
And we're post-apocalypse, and
we have to rebuild civilization.
This is me, ZingingCutie23.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, slow down!
ZingingCutie 23.
Are you pretending that
you're 23 years old?
- No.
- It seems like it.
No, I... It's... I... It's a
random number that I picked.
It's a random number?
It's a number to put at the end of that.
You know what?
Just watch over my tribe, and
make sure nobody, you know,
takes it over, and I'll
give you your money, okay?
Okay. Okay. Wait.
Hold on a second. What is that?
That's you.
You're one of my subjects.
That's me.
Why am I in the game?
Is that Mac?
Of course that's Mac.
You guys are all here.
See, Mac's my handmaiden.
How do you do?
And Dennis is a midget blacksmith.
Frank is a mutant half-donkey.
And you're my jester.
Why am I eating out of a trough?
Made sense.
Are you kidding me?
So let me get this straight.
You've been playing this game
for, like, a week straight just
so you feel like you lord over all of us?
Is that what this is?
Charlie, do you want
your five bucks or not?
I want my five dollars.
It's just pathetic, Dee.
Okay, well, maybe it is.
Maybe it isn't.
I really do need the money, though.
Yeah, well, then get to work.
Can you give me an advance?
No, not in advance.
We'll see how well you do.
All right, I got this.
I got this.
Yeah.
See, this is what I'm
talking about, guys, huh?
I mean, playing online video
games and watching stupid
reality shows-- that's not real life.
It's keeping people from
experiencing real life.
Yeah?
This is real.
It's real, but it feels weird as shit.
There's nobody else in the bar dancing.
We're setting the tone, Frank.
Yeah, we will lead, and
others will follow.
I'm stopping.
Oh, come on, don't stop.
Look, all right, let's go do
some shots, and that will get
you guys fired up, and we'll
come back out, and we'll do some
more of this or whatever.
You know, you can do the move, and...
well, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Hey, uh, bartender, three
shots of whiskey, come on.
Hey, I know you guys.
You're the donkey man and
the princess, right?
We don't know what you're talking about.
Take a hike, Bozo.
Geek.
Check it out. Look at this.
This is... this is you, right?
This-this is Frank and-and Mac
from ZingingCutie's tribe?
What the hell is this?
This is Dee's online video game, and
she's created characters for all of us.
She's humiliating us virtually.
Who cares? It's a video game.
What do you mean, who cares?
This is starting to piss me off.
Stop getting invested in fake realities.
Let's live real life!
Well, Dennis, my anger feels very real.
Are you feeling it?
Yeah, well, it's not real.
It's not.
I-I-I... I'm angry.
Okay, it's not real, and you
know what it also isn't?
It also isn't epic, okay?
And you know what is epic?
Doing these shots, going
out there and dancing.
Come on, do it, do the shots.
I'll do the shots.
I'll just do the shots.
How about that?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, somebody got a smart phone.
Okay, you know, I tell you what, Carl.
Let's settle for a C trade.
We'll call it a day on that.
I got to run.
ZingingCutie44 is back, so I'm out.
Changed your name.
What the hell are you doing, Charlie?
I told you to just feed my crops.
I did, I fed your crops, and
then I gathered some rocks, and
I built a little wall around your tribe.
Then I used the leftover rocks to dam
the river so that you could fish.
Now you're doing well in the game.
You sucked at it, all right?
All you did was spend your money
on stuff you don't need, just
like in real life.
I don't do that in real life.
Yes, you do.
What did you get at the store?
I bought a smart phone so that
I can play the game on the go.
What's going on with the fingernails?
Well, I had those done like Flo-Jo.
Why?! It's craziness.
I just thought it would be funny.
I... Dee, this is your problem.
I could take this money, I
could feed myself for a month.
I would buy milk, I would buy
flour, I'd buy vitamins, I'd
boil them down to little energy balls
to sustain me, but whatever. Forget it.
Enjoy your game, enjoy all your new
followers, and you're welcome.
Oh, shit!
Charlie, you got me 31 new followers?
Yeah.
That's amazing!
Hey, do you want to maybe team up?
No, 'cause I don't want to be a slave.
Come on, Charlie, please.
I need you.
It's, like, when I'm doing good in
the game, I'm doing good in life.
Oh, I want to make fun of you
for saying that, but I kind of
know what you mean.
It's like I'm thriving.
You are thriving.
Yeah, I did feel that, and I...
You felt that?
I did, I felt that, you know,
and I never get to thrive.
I want to be the guy
who thrives for once.
Right? Me, neither.
All right, I'll tell you what-- make
me your king, and let's get rocking.
Ew, no. I don't want to do
that 'cause we'd have to be
married, and that would be awful.
Oh, okay, I'll see you later.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Sit down, sit down, sit down.
I'll make you my king; just
accept my request to consummate.
Consummate? What is that?
Have sex.
Oh. So, um, we should have sex then?
In the game.
Yeah, in the game, sure, yeah.
Yeah.
Either way.
Uh, so, push enter hard, or one,
like, slow push, and you do your
thing, or a little circular action?
Just push the button, Charlie.
Just push the button.
That was good, right?
Was it?
I think.
You see me, Frank, you see me coming?
I see you, I see you.
Oh, here comes another guy.
I'm gonna fight him.
Mac attack!
Fight!
I lost again!
Goddamn it, how do I keep losing?
I'm huge.
Stop fighting every guy in the game.
The fighting is the best part.
It's the only reason I'm playing.
Oh, my God, will you guys please shut up?
I'm hungover as shit.
We're playing TechPocalypse.
Mac is a soiled fool, and I am a
gorgeous girl with big cans and
I'm banging all the fishermen
in sight for fish and I'm also
being catty with all the women in the
game, like I'm a Real Housewife.
Look, Dennis, I-I'm six-foot- ten.
I have always wanted to be six- foot-ten.
Hey, look, Mac, you're five-
foot-nine, and Frank, you're a
man-- an ugly, old man!
You're not understanding this,
Dennis, but I think I have
something that could help you
wrap your head around it.
I've never had my hair cut in a bedroom.
Well, one thing I've learned
from cutting hair all these
years, Danielle, is you don't
have to go to a high-end salon
to get a high-end salon-quality cut.
Little spritz?
Why are we watching Dennis' sex tape?
Shh.
It's cold.
I know.
Well, we'll make it hot in a
minute, don't worry about that.
Well, don't... Well,
it's always-- there's
always so much, so much preamble.
Okay, here we go.
Okay.
Oh, oh, um, all right.
All right.
Whoa.
Now, Dennis, how does this make you feel?
Powerful.
Yes, of course, but how does
it affect you sexually?
I'm very aroused right now.
I, too, am aroused.
I'm starting to swell up.
Yeah.
See, now all three of us are aroused,
and there's not a woman in the room.
See, this is no different
than sports or video games.
It's all a virtual experience.
No, no, no, bullshit, this was
real, okay, this happened, I
did this.
All right, I drew this woman in,
I styled her hair, I entered her
with almost no resistance.
I did these things.
You say it's real, but
what even is reality?
Yeah, who knows?
We don't even know if we're in this room.
We could be in a turtle's
dream in outer space.
What are you talking about?
I'm gonna go out into the real world
again today and have real experiences.
I'm gonna draw those
people in to me, okay?
A turtle's dream.
That's crazy, lunacy.
So, tell me something, Queen
of Thrones, how about we stop
being enemies, we start
becoming friends here, huh?
Charlie, I just got a new nose and I'm
flying to Miami to get my lips inflated.
Can you hang on one second?
What, Dee, what are you buying?
How are you paying for that?
We have plenty of money.
I know we have money.
We have money because I...
All right, you know what?
Yes, fine, buy your lips, buy your
noses, buy whatever you're gonna buy.
All right, don't interrupt me
when I'm running our tribe,
okay, 'cause that's kind of a big deal.
I know, I'm sorry.
All right, so don't interrupt.
Okay.
Do me a favor, refill my
bowl of energy balls, okay?
Please make yourself useful.
Sorry about that, Queen of Thrones,
let me step into my office here.
Hey, bitch!
Frank, you are SweetPeaches69?
How did you get so many followers?
What can I say?
Some girls are more popular than others.
Are you wearing a mink coat?
What, this old thing?
Guy gave it to me for going down on him.
I've been getting a lot of gifts lately.
I just got sent a whole box
of peaches-- real ones.
I'm eating like a goddamn islander.
I'm living a pretty
classy life these days.
Ooh, you should come to my party.
I'm gonna meet a lot of
my online friends there.
It's gonna be a very classy
affair, but you can come anyway.
Well, look, we can sit here, we
can talk cheesesteaks all day
long, but maybe you and I could
get together at my bar, settle
this thing once and for all.
Charlie, we got to talk.
Whoa.
We're going to a party-- a real
one-- Frank's throwing it.
Yes, I know what's going on.
I know everything that's happening.
Do you know he has a bunch of followers?
Do you know that he's parading around
in a mink coat, and he humiliated me?
I'm a queen, okay?
I should be the one wearing mink and
I should be throwing digs at him.
You know what I mean?
I should have a lot more followers.
You want mink, Dee, you want a mink coat?
You want a nice, real mink coat,
not a virtual one like Frank?
Don't dick around with this.
Are you serious?
I am dead serious.
I trade with a guy online;
he has a clothing store.
I'm sure I could give him some
crops, maybe a follower or two,
and he'll give you a mink coat.
For me?
Would you like that?
I would love that.
You, you would like that, wouldn't you?
You know how that's not gonna happen?
What?
It's not gonna happen if I'm
not playing the goddamn game!
Because when I'm not playing the
game, people are attacking our
tribe, okay, and that's a lot of
pressure, that's a lot of stress.
It's too much for you.
And we could lose everything, we
could lose everything that we
have worked for-- everything!
I wasn't thinking.
No, you're not really the
thinking kind, though.
I'm kind of the thinking one in the
relationship, so... Right, thank you.
Be pretty, you know, talk to me right.
Yeah.
Get my energy balls.
Unbelievable.
Hey, Charlie, we need to talk, dude.
Well, well, well,
if it isn't the soiled fool.
Frank told you about that?
Uh, no, everyone's talking about
it online; it's hilarious.
You destroyed your computer,
you bashed it to bits.
I'm assuming it got you in the eye--
is that what's going on there?
It bashed me back a little bit.
Yeah, you should win those
fights, you shouldn't lose...
I did win, I did win, it just
got a couple of good shots in.
It did, yeah.
Hey, Charlie, hey, listen, I
want to tell you something.
Um, Dee... Yeah?
You're not going to offer our guest any?
Of course I-- of course,
that's what I was doing.
Yeah.
Hey, Mac, hey, did you, did you
want an energy ball or two?
Yeah.
Go ahead, have as many as
you want-- is that enough?
That's-- yeah, that's good.
There you go, okay.
Okay, you need to fuel up.
Have a bunch of balls.
Yeah, I do, thank you.
Okay, thank you.
Okay-- don't touch.
No, now I know.
Right, yeah.
I didn't mean that.
And stop groveling, just...
Let me know if you need...
You're not pretty when you do that, so...
Wow, you, like, totally
psychologically, like, annihilated her.
Yeah.
You're good at building,
I'm good at destroying.
We should totally team up.
Wait, you know what?
Can you do me a favor?
Can you watch her for a little while while
I go meet a girl that I met online?
A real girl?
Yeah, a real girl.
She's probably fat, right?
Probably very fat, yeah.
If she's got any fat
friends, I'm, I'm in.
If she has any fat friends,
I'll let you know.
Or ugly.
Yeah, or ugly.
If they're sick, that's fine, too.
Yeah, or ugly or sick or, or male or
female or whatever it is that you like.
That's not the point.
Like, the point is, you
know how women get.
You know, she catches wind that I'm
meeting a girl, she's going to go...
Oh, totally, totally.
I hate women.
Yeah, I-I know that you feel
that way, but do what I'm asking
and then I can help you
out with the game.
Okay, do what?
Watch Dee.
Oh, okay, yeah.
Hello, hi.
Anyone?
Come on, hello, hi.
God, it's unbelievable.
Does anybody want to experience this?
Anyone want to experience me?
For real?
Oasis Sensory Deprivation.
Enter a new dimension.
Change your perception.
Experience a new reality.
Stop getting invested in fake realities!
I'm six foot, ten.
You're five foot, nine.
What even is reality?
This is real.
How do you do?
We could be in a turtle's
dream in outer space.
What is real?
Is this real? Am I?
Who are you?
Oh, I'm you.
Huh.
That's an amazing accent.
I like yours as well.
I think I know what reality
is, but maybe I don't.
Everything in life is becoming
more and more virtual.
Aw, don't be such a wanker.
Life is all in your mind.
If you believe it to be
real, then it's real.
I'm so confused, British Dennis.
You create your own reality.
I've known beggars to be kings
and kings to be beggars, all
because they believed it so.
It's your choice.
It's my choice.
It's your universe.
It's my universe.
And you are God.
I... am... God.
Oh... oh... oh, no... okay.
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
Charlie?
Hey.
Julie, right?
The Queen of Thrones!
The second most powerful
player in the game.
And you are the Mighty Rat Slayer.
'Tis I, 'tis I!
It's nice to meet you!
Yeah, I'm sorry... I'm sorry, I
haven't had a chance to tidy myself.
You know, when you're playing the
game, you get caught up and...
Have a seat! Have a seat!
Wow, this is... It's cool to meet
someone from the game, you know?
I brought you something.
You did?
It's nothing, really.
It's just, um... the best
cheesecake in Philadelphia.
You dog!
Uh, I'll be the judge of that, all right?
You little rascal, you.
Uh, I don't normally meet
people from the game, but you
seem like such a nice guy.
Thanks, yeah, yeah, you know...
This is embarrassing, but I got
you something too, you know?
I don't want... I don't want to
make you feel weird but here.
Oh, how thoughtful.
I wonder what it is.
It's not much.
Just a box of spiders.
What the hell?
Well, while we've been sitting
here, my followers have
burned your land, they've raped your
people, and they've destroyed your tribe.
You thought you could make a
move on me, Queen of Thrones?
Well, you were wrong.
What?
I just wanted to have lunch with you.
Oh, right.
Oh, let's have lunch because we're
hungry and we want to eat food.
Bullshit!
You think I'd give up all this for lunch?
You stupid, fat pig.
I'm not fat.
No, you're not fat, but you were...
you were supposed to be.
My friend Mac said you would be fat.
Whatever.
You're a dick.
And your breath smells like dog food.
Whatever, you bitch!
I got the power now!
I'm doing good in the game,
so I'm doing good in life!
Oh, look who's here.
Well, it's nice that you came.
A little overdressed.
You said that this was a
classy affair, Frank.
It was a classy affair
until you showed up.
You bitch!
Where are your 101 Dalmatians tonight?
He's better at the zings than you!
All right, Dee, give me your
phone, give me your headset-- I
got to get back online ASAP.
I just made some big things happen.
Big things, baby!
Boom!
No.
She's not with you anymore, bro.
Hold on. Shut up.
Wh-Why is the soiled fool talking to me?
I don't need you anymore, Charlie.
I'd like a divorce.
Ooh! Juicy!
Wait, what are you talking about?
I know you were gonna leave me
for the Queen of Thrones, so
I've slept with Mac to humiliate you.
She's humiliated you and
herself by sleeping with me.
I'm good at the game now.
Oh, my God, Dee, you stupid idiot.
Do you... do you have
a brain in your head?
I was tricking that girl, so
that I could destroy her tribe.
We're the most powerful tribe
in the whole game now!
What are you doing?!
Uh... you know, I-I guess
maybe I hadn't really thought
the whole thing through.
No, you didn't think!
Because you don't think!
You're just a stupid
kept housewife, okay?
Zing it, girl!
Frank, shut the hell up!
How dare you all conspire against me?
How dare you?!
You know what, I want everyone out.
Everyone get out of my apartment, okay?
No, not you, not you, and not you.
The three of you, sit!
Get out!
Okay, I think we can all agree
that this game is the most
important thing that ever
happened to us, right?
Absolutely, yeah... It's very important...
That's the truth.
It's a hugely important thing!
So because I'm a nice guy, you
know, 'cause I'm a cool dude,
I'll let you live, all right?
But, Mac and Frank, you got to give
me your shares of Paddy's Pub.
Done!
What?
Yes!
And, Dee, you're gonna have to
do all the Charlie-work in the
bar from here until-- oh, I don't
know-- how's eternity sound?
Stop... This
game has gone on long enough.
Uh, shit.
Are you doing an accent?
Yeah, I was doing a British acc...
It was a British accent.
That was British?!
Yeah, I had it so good in my
head-- uh, I was doing a really
good British accent.
Doesn't matter. Anyway... Charlie,
you think you have all the power?
Well, you don't.
You see, the only thing
bigger than a king is a god.
You think you're a god?
I'm the one who's thriving, Dennis.
I mean, look at me.
You look like you're
covered in Hawaiian Punch.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Eh.
I am the god of my own universe, Charlie.
I decide my own reality, and I've
decided all of your realities as well.
So, you see, I unplugged it.
You... unplugged reality?
I don't understand what he's saying.
Me neither.
I just... I deleted all of
your characters from the game.
What?
I erased all your... people.
H-How did you do that?
Well, it was easy.
You guys all have the same
password, "paddyspub."
Oh, that's my password for everything.
Mine, too.
Why would you do that though?
Why would you delete our characters?
Because the goddamn game
was irritating to me.
I thought it was really stupid,
and it really is just, you know,
sort of that simple, so I
ended the game, you know.
That's the end.
Doesn't have to be a whole big
thing every single time, you know.
That's life.
That's just sort of how-how shit goes.
Sometimes things just sort of... end.
♪ All night long ♪
♪ All night ♪