Pretty crowded tonight, huh?
Yeah, well, it's Gugino's, you
know, best restaurant in Philadelphia.
To our monthly dinner.
Oh, monthly dinner, baby.
I tell you, I've been looking
forward to this for... 29 days!
Me, too.
I did my hair good, and
I wore two colognes.
Is that what that is?
Mm.
That was an interesting
choice, but I get it, dude.
You're excited.
You are excited about tonight.
Hey, hell, I'm excited tonight, you know?
Not terribly excited about being
near the kitchen, though.
Really? It's where the action is.
Maybe we'll get lucky and watch
one of these dumb-ass waiters
spill spaghetti sauce all over himself.
And fall down or something.
Okay, all right.
Well, let's not be childish.
Let's-let's keep it classy.
You know, let's... Classy.
I can do classy.
I can be classy.
Did you invite Frank and Charlie?
No, I didn't.
Hi.
How many will you guys be?
Two. And give us a nice table.
This is a big night for us.
We're celebrating our anniversary.
Or the anniversary of us moving
in together, which is like an
anniver-- it's been a long time.
Anniversary is what it is, really.
Well, great.
Uh... oh, okay, oh, okay, uh...
You can just hand that to me.
I was trying to feel your breast.
I got that.
Yeah, but he was trying to
feel your breast and give you
the tip so that we got a good table.
I want a good table.
Oh, hey. Hey, hey, hey!
Mac and Dennis are here.
Should we sit with them?
Really?
Mm, Charlie, this is our night.
Yeah, but we could all
celebrate it together.
That'd be fun.
We can do our thing.
They can do their thing.
I'm sure at some point they'll
come over to pay tribute.
We can say hi to them then.
That's weird.
I know Charlie sees me, but they seem
to be sitting at their own table.
Well, good.
Good, they should sit at their own table.
Look, I'm sure at some point they'll
come over and they'll pay tribute to us.
They know it's our monthly dinner.
We can say hi to them then.
Yeah, still, seems kind
of awkward, though.
No. Look, we spend every
waking minute together.
It will be good for us to
keep our distance for once.
It's one minor coincidence.
Doesn't go any further than that.
Goddamn it.
Sync & corrections by
Of all the goddamn nights.
Can't believe they haven't come
over to pay me tribute yet.
I was here first.
I know they see me.
They're probably over there
right now making fun of me.
I get it, guys.
You know what they're doing?
They're calling me "Scarecrow."
'Cause I'm all alone in the cornfields,
scaring away the other birds.
Real funny.
You know what?
There's no shame in a woman, an
adult woman, taking herself out
to dinner, enjoying her own
company-- I'm not gonna leave.
I'm not gonna leave because I
don't have to, and also I can't
because I have a Groupon for this
evening that expires tonight.
It does expire tonight, doesn't it?
Uh, yeah.
I... Yes, it does.
I'm sorry.
Are you going to order now?
Well, I'm trying to have
a conversation with you.
Why don't you sit down
for a little while?
Take a break.
Oh! Are you almost off?
Are you off soon?
Should you sit and have
dinner with me tonight?
No, got a long shift.
Uh, I cannot do that.
Uh, maybe I could at
least get a drink order?
We're really busy tonight.
Does the Groupon cover drinks?
Nope.
Just the tap water, then.
I can't believe this.
They still haven't paid tribute.
It's been ten minutes.
Not a wave, not a nod.
Have you seen them do
anything to acknowledge us?
I thought we agreed that we
would not let it get to us.
It's not getting to me.
It's just, you know, a little
bit rude, is all I'm saying.
It's, you know, irritating.
Whatever, I don't care.
I'm... I'm over it.
'Kay.
How good is their table, though?
Oh, um... Don't-don't
look directly at them.
Jesus Christ, just, you know,
glance around the room a little
bit, and just, you know, land on them.
Glance around the room?
Yeah.
Too obvious!
Well, how do you want me to look at them?
With your eyes, just look with your eyes.
Be subtle, be small.
My eyes, they slant down.
I don't have a good peripheral.
Okay, can you just be subtle?
It's a good table.
How'd they get a better table than us?
Uh, I don't know.
Dennis, can we just focus on us?
Yeah.
It's our monthly dinner, all right?
Don't let them ruin it.
Okay?
I have some issues that I want to talk to you...
Aw, shit. Really?
No, I... Look, let's-let's keep things
light; I don't want to get all heavy.
Let's not let tonight become more
unpleasant than it's already become, okay?
I mean, already I'm irritated.
I'm... I'm already sitting in the
wobbliest chair in the entire restaurant.
All right, well, we'll just ask
the waiter for a book of matches.
I don't want to sit on a pile of matches.
Look, I'll just scoot back.
It's fine. It's fine.
Oh, but now I feel like... you're
sitting so far away from me.
It's gonna be fine!
This is a perfectly suitable distance
for us to have our monthly dinner.
Goddamn it.
I am so sorry.
Are you?!
His chair's wobbly.
Oh, okay.
Let me get you a book of
matches to put under there.
I don't want to sit on a pile of matches.
Dennis, it's not like your
chair's gonna catch on fire.
Oh, Christ, I'm not worried about
my chair catching on fire.
Look, sir, can you just get
us a better table in general?
Unfortunately, no.
We're fully booked tonight
due to a Groupon deal.
Oh, that sounds excellent.
We'll have one of those.
No, we won't.
We don't need a coupon.
Frankly, I'm disappointed in you people.
This is Gugino's.
You're supposed to be the nicest
restaurant in Philadelphia.
Here I am, a regular, a full-paying
customer, and I'm sat by the kitchen on the
wobbliest chair in Philadelphia.
You know, forced to eat dinner with
this swarm of coupon-waving trash.
This is crazy!
You know what?
Forget it, doesn't matter.
Get me a pile of matches to
sit on-- that'll be fine.
Okay.
No, wait, wait, wait.
There's more.
There's an old, short, fat man here.
He's sat with his young sleeping partner.
Bring them a glass of
the house red from us.
Of course.
Although the table did just
order cocktails, so maybe...
I don't need their entire life story.
Just go get the wine.
Well, that was a nice gesture.
Was it?
Charlie.
Hmm?
Stop looking over there.
Can we just go over and say
a quick hello, all right?
Then it's done with.
There's no more awkwardness.
Charlie, I am the oldest
one in the group.
If anybody's gonna say a quick
hello, it's them to me.
I just feel like it's gonna become a
bigger deal than it needs to be, you know?
Then forget it.
Yeah?
This is our night, Charlie.
All right.
Listen. I prepared a few
words for the evening.
All right?
Okay.
All right.
Charlie, I want to talk
about where we are.
Where we've been.
And where we're going to be.
Where are we going?
Don't interrupt.
Living with you has... changed my life.
I-I used to be unaware...
Hi, sorry to bother you.
What are you doing, man?
I'm in the middle of something here.
Get out of here!
Of course.
I just wanted to deliver a glass
of our house red from the two
gentlemen near the kitchen.
Beat it.
Well, great.
See, there's your tribute, Frank.
Awesome.
Now can we go over and say a quick hello?
No, no.
I'm in the middle of
saying some words to you.
Yeah, but you said 'em, and they were weird, like...
All right, you know what?
How about I just stand and I bow?
No. Ignore them.
This is ridiculous.
I mean, that was a very nice gesture.
Was it?
One glass of wine for two
people, and house red?
That wasn't nice.
They're just trying to agitate us.
Mm.
Well, two can play at that game.
Hey.
Ooh, hey!
You, help.
Over here.
Me?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you, please.
Help. Help me.
Sit, sit, please sit.
Help.
Is everything okay?
No, everything's not okay.
There are men here, and
they're watching me.
Oh, shit!
Shh!
Just look at me, just look right at me.
Everything's gonna be fine, but
I'm in a lot of shit. Okay?
So I need your help.
Oh, good.
You have a friend.
Hi.
Can I take your order now?
Yes.
I'm not with her.
There is some shit going down right now.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
He's just...
Please, let's order.
Look, you told me you was in trouble.
I don't know what's happening here.
No, it's okay, I'm fine.
Do you want to split an appetizer?
No, I don't need this shit.
Well... oh.
You know, if you just order, we
can get your food out really
quickly, and you wouldn't have
to be embarrassed about being
here alone for very long.
All right?
I'll tell you what I'm gonna do.
I-I'm gonna go ahead and order when
I'm goddamn good and ready to order.
Is that table having a meal
consisting only of loud noise,
screams, and hollers?
Uh, they seem to be
celebrating something.
Ooh, could be a tactical victory.
What do you think?
Sure.
Whoo!
Okay, how's the chair now?
Still wobbly.
Why don't you just get me a new chair?
I don't think it's the chair.
You don't think it's the chair?
Well, maybe my old pal, uh,
Abraham Lincoln begs to differ.
Oh, okay, yeah, uh... You
can just hand it to me.
Hello.
Your waiter.
Great.
Hi.
Can you get him a new chair?
Sure.
Oh, oh!
Maybe this George Washington
will make it come here faster.
Okay.
This wine is for you.
Ah, management sent us a
bottle to accommodate us.
Actually, it was your friends
over at the other table.
And they wanted me to relay to you
that it's our most expensive bottle.
They said to say that.
That's a classy move.
I'm gonna stand up and bow.
No. Do not stand and bow.
Let me think.
We've got to do something in return.
Mm-hmm.
I'll tell you what.
We'll send it back.
You know?
We'll say, we don't want that.
You know? We'll-we'll tell them
that, uh, what is it, Chilean
wine is out of season, and that their
taste in wine in general is very poor.
No, that's... we got to
be more subtle than that.
I don't want them to know that
we're thinking about them.
What are you doing?
Are you staring at them?
Yeah, dude, Charlie's
looking right at me.
Stop it.
Dude, stop it.
Okay, stop looking, stop... All
right, you know what, goddamn it?
I'm just gonna pour the wine out.
Goddamn it!
That son of a bitch is
pouring out my wine.
Look... can you just let it go, Frank?
Okay?
You're ruining this night for me, okay?
I-I'm sure he had a perfectly good
reason for pouring out a glass of wine.
I want to go over there.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Just like he had a perfectly good
reason for not inviting you to dinner.
He had a good... Wait.
What do you mean by that?
Don't make me say it, Charlie.
I know you're not as dumb as you seem.
Well, let's just say that I am.
Those two guys don't give a
shit about you, Charlie.
You bought a business together;
they made you a janitor.
Eh, they didn't make me a
janitor; there was a... Mm?
Oh, my God.
It's time to fire back.
Aw, I gotta get over there.
Hi, ma'am.
Sorry to bug you again.
Oh, my God.
I'll just take a plate of spaghetti.
Oh, great.
Didn't expect that.
Uh, actually, I was coming over to
see if I could take your chair.
What? No.
What for?
I'm trying to accommodate
that gentleman over there.
Oh, goddamn it.
Uh, that's a dig.
All right, fine.
Take the chair, but I tell you
what, when you're over there?
Tie his shoelaces together.
You want me to... tie a
customer's shoelaces together?
Uh... Look, I'm in the biz, guy.
I'm a waitress, okay?
Look, let's team up and
stick it to that guy.
It'll be hilarious.
I would lose my job.
Uh...
"Oh, no, I-I would lose my job.
And I wouldn't be able to work
at Gugino's anymore, and my
family, and they'd be so disappointed
'cause they're currently so proud of my
accomplishments."
I mean, God, lighten up, guy.
I'm gonna take the chair.
Fine, take the goddamn chair.
Just don't make a big scene.
How's the new chair?
Oh, it's terrible, Mac.
Thank you for asking.
It might be worse than the first one.
I mean, I cannot find a single flat
spot in this entire restaurant.
Maybe that's it. I'm just... Goddamn it!
This entire night is ruined.
Dude, stop it!
Okay?
You're the one who's ruining this.
I am enjoying myself.
I'm enjoying our table.
I'm trying to start the conversations.
I wore two colognes.
Oh, I'm very aware of how much
cologne you're wearing, Mac.
It's overwhelming me.
I mean, every time the goddamn kitchen
door opens, it wafts into my face.
Hey, I like the way I smell.
And I like me.
And I haven't even gotten to
talk about what I wanted to talk
about, which is an issue that
has been weighing on me, so I'm
just gonna say it, okay?
When I wanted to get the karaoke
machine for our apartment, you
laughed in my face.
That's what this is about?
Yes.
The karaoke machine?
Mac, you can't sing.
It's not about singing!
Okay?
It's about you always putting me down, and...
you know what?
I don't care; it doesn't matter.
I'm out of here.
Where you going?
I'm gonna go sit with Frank and Charlie.
Do not go to them.
No, sit down, sit.
Sit!
Say something nice to me.
What?
I'm not going to sit down until
you say something nice to
me for once in your life.
Your hair looks small.
Oh, for... Okay, okay, okay, man.
All right, sit down, sit down.
Sit.
Please sit down.
Okay, listen, listen.
You remember that night
at Dooley's pool party?
On that fine summer eve, when I
did that double jackknife twist
and blew everybody's tits off?
You remember that?
And then I went down on Chrissie Orlando
on the trampoline later that night?
You're just complimenting yourself.
No, listen, I'm going
somewhere with this.
The only reason I was even able
to attempt that amazing feat of
courage was... because I knew if I
failed, you would...
Everybody.
Hello!
All the patrons of Gugino's, listen up.
Hi, everybody.
Frank Reynolds, Charlie Kelly.
We would like to make a toast.
Now, in front of you, you each
see, you have a glass of sambuca?
You see this white, beautiful drink?
Yeah. Okay, everyone got it?
Yeah.
Dude, everybody has sambuca but us.
Now we have an American hero
tonight, so quick round of
applause for our troop here.
Nice-looking fellow.
And to anyone who does not have a
glass of sambuca... Look around now.
You'll see them.
Those people refuse to drink.
Yeah. They don't know how to pay tribute.
They hate America!
They hate the troops.
Mm.
They hate the people who
work hardest for them.
They turn them into janitors.
Mm, mm.
It's not right. Aah!
Damn 'em to hell.
To the troops!
To the troops.
Cheers.
To America!
Good job, fellas.
We did it.
This is unbelievable, Mac.
You know, and they totally
ruined our heartfelt moment.
Now, there's a way we can get it
back-- if you just kind of jump...
No, you fool!
That time has passed.
Can't you see they're humiliating us?
Just tell me what you were gonna tell me.
I'm not gonna stand for this.
I'm not.
Just, Dennis... Come on, man!
Goddamn it!
Ma'am?
Uh-huh.
Please return to your table?
Oh, you know what?
I'm gonna sit next to the hero.
I used to date a troop.
He was crazy for jean shorts.
Attention, uh, attention,
everyone, please.
If I could have your attention
momentarily. Thank you.
We do have an American
hero in the house tonight.
A strong man, a brave man.
He's the kind of man who
knows exactly who he is.
He doesn't hide under a toupee.
He faces his challenges, instead
of just retreating to the
sewers... nude to forage
for rings and coins.
Or to the toilets.
Or to a life filled with rats.
He's the kind of man who gives
me the courage to do an amazing
double jackknife twist, which I did.
Most of you people wouldn't
even attempt that.
I did it.
And to go down on Chrissy Orlando
on the trampoline later,
on the very same night, which I also did.
And I licked her asshole a little bit.
It was pretty good.
It was all right.
It wasn't great.
But it was fine.
And I knew that it was gonna be
fine because this guy would be
here to catch me if I faltered.
Yeah. The world is a safer
place when he's around.
♪ Did you ever know That you're my hero?
'Cause you are the wind
Beneath my wings. ♪
Thank you.
Thanks.
Wow, dude.
I mean, that was so touching.
Oh.
That's an amazing thing
you said about the troop.
Now, can we get back to
the karaoke machine?
Because I... I was talking about you.
That was about me?
Yes. He wasn't there when I
went down on Chrissy Orlando.
I did not get that at all.
I'm sor... Dennis, that's really sweet.
Thank you.
I'm sorry. What's happening?
Is it freezing in here all of a sudden?
Yeah, and it's... freezing.
Air is blowing directly on us. What...?
I mean, what is happening?
Those goddamn sons of bitches.
They turned up the A/C.
Because they knew we were sitting
right underneath a vent.
And they're trying to freeze us out.
I didn't have your back before,
but now I'm gonna be the wind
beneath your wings.
I'm gonna smash this over
their goddamn heads.
Yes, Mac. Yes! Yes!
I'm gonna blast 'em with
this fire extinguisher.
Okay, I'll toss hot soup in their faces.
I'll pinch their dicks with this lobster.
Let's do it.
What are you people doing?
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Son a bitch!
Hey, his shoelaces are tied together.
What?
Oh, my God!
Somebody tied his shoelaces together.
His shoes are tied.
Spaghetti-O, the waiter.
I've wanted to see that all night long.
Yes. Yes. Oh, my God, who do
we have to thank for this?
Who?
Oops.
Deandra did it?
Oh! Dee did it! It was Dee.
Dee.
Have you been here this entire time?
Yeah, the whole time.
Oh, great job, Dee.
Great job.
Oh, Dee.
Hey, clash. Salud, huh?
Salud.
Guys? Guys, I'm really hurt.
Back at the table!
I want to hear some jokes
out of you tonight.
You want to try this coat on?
It's gotta look good on you, dude.
Put that hat on.